Thank you for watching, please subscribe and hit that like button!
Static on the screen
Everybody smiling
Like they know just what it means
We got candles in the basement
Secrets in the walls
A velvet rope at midnight
And a voice that softly calls
Nobody's exactly normal
That's our favorite thing
We laugh like saints with eyeliner
Casual Conducting Psychic Prison, Somewhere In The Candles
Mump Behind The Secret Door
A Hidden High Priestess Knows A Little Something More
She Never Makes An Entrance
She Just Suddenly Appears
Vexes Everybody's Chaos With The W-
Shit like the sweet forbidden hymns like he dreams
I see the game
Something that change everything
The wise man acts at once
What the fool does?
Finally, translation
I'm already finished while you're still starting
This isn't a battle, it's a foregone conclusion
You can throw stones, but I'ma still ache
Every ripple you make just shows where you break
And comprehend what you can't see
Can't begin what I've already pinned, see?
Isn't defeating your ass
my fries are so hot. Where are my fries? My french fries. Where'd I put them? Hold on,
they're with my alcohol. Oh, here, here, here. Hi. How's everyone doing? Oh my god, one person?
Everyone is left when I came on. Okay. Why? Fuck you!
So if you don't like it, see me, my French fries?
Here we go.
Make it smaller.
Too small.
There we go.
Can I get it over to the left?
Oh, that's better.
Okay.
There we go.
Doing good.
How is everybody?
I have the link up.
Everyone wants to come up.
Mm.
Sunday, I took a pretty good day
Got thing out in some shows and I
Had a lot of work done
Projects I'm working on I got a lot of stuff done with the codex
I'll be updating it soon. Hi. Okay. No one's talking
Well, no one's no one comes and no one's talking to her
I was gonna have the night off
So I'll give it like five minutes, but I did buy alcohol
Windry
I was on Sam and tonight. It was actually not too bad of an appearance. I
Didn't feel kind of bad because I might have thrown a few people under the bus just trying to make a point
Hey, what's up Jesus Christ? How are you?
But uh
Yeah, I mean Tommy James came and he was like, oh
Hey thing that is how are you Tommy James came and he said, oh, I'm sure like, you know, psyche's gonna see this video of
You know of Brandon
And he's gonna change his mind
Now, I watched the videos and I'll give my opinion.
I think some of them were pretty jokes and bad tastes.
I think some of them were a little bit more serious,
but at the same time, I didn't see anybody being hurt.
I didn't see anybody.
I didn't see like certain things happen.
And so it's like, I mean, it was all over like, you know,
internet and...
I don't know. I just didn't, I think that he's a victim of maybe trying to be silenced a little bit
because he does figure, he does find out, you know, anyone that goes after him, you know,
he kind of goes after her and like, well, if they have something in their criminal background, he'll,
he'll, you know, he can figure that out. But at the end of the day, I think that I don't think he's a bad guy, so
Do you see him here?
No, he'd be friendly.
Or, just like you can,
you don't like him block him or something like that.
But yeah, I'll be controversial.
I'll just continue to be controversial.
I never saw such a problem for anybody else
ever having a problem about guests.
It's kind of crazy.
Bean gang said it's on site.
What does that mean?
What's on site?
Oh, because I mentioned his child abuse charges and that he actually had as opposed to like, you know
accusations
Well, I'm not saying I think it was just like maybe not his kid was we're gonna seat belt or something
I don't think it was like that serious, but
At the same time, it's like, you know, you have a lot of double standards in the community
I think so on site what he's gonna do on site kill me
Well, we have now we have the record of that so thank you for revealing yourself be the Andy. I
Mean I need to do is kind of be friendlier to me like yeah, we're not you but you know he should have
Why why did you why did you mean it's like wow? He's just he started the bitching about so it's really like you know at the end of the day
It's really not about people just like bitch and I think it's like entitlement to be on the show. It's my show. It's like
No one else has any problem with anybody else running their show. I have the most liberal fucking show goons
Okay, are you threatening me or are you threatening me? Are you threatening the greatest portfolio? No, I don't know the goons. I don't know
I'm gonna get some
Whoever he sends to kill me. I'll charm I'll charm them and probably give them a blowjob
So it won't work it won't work
But anyway
Anyway, okay
In a day, it's like all it's all I'm trying to do is expose a little bit of hypocrisy, you know, I
Mean there's people with serious charges that it's like you're gonna go on the boulevard
Or you got goons on the boulevard. Oh, I don't live on the boulevard though
What my sunset boulevard? Oh, no
Oh, I'm done bud. Okay. Well, everyone take a note that I'm being threatened by this beanie Andy person
Let me see what it looks like hold on. I'm gonna just take a screenshot of this picture right here. Okay. Oh my god
It's like a koala bear
Oh
Are you a dog or like a some kind of
Monster or something. What is that? What the fuck is that? Anyway, you look like a little panda
Anyway, I'm not afraid
I'm done, but you're done, but you're done, but you know, I know witchcraft, I know a spider
ritual, I will take care of you at night, I know, I know a baked bean ritual that will
have your whole gang in a, into a lot of that morning, okay?
In the ground up has ghosted anything about the brand and stuff goes. No, not really
Why does he know something more I
Mean I watched a few I watched and I watched it. I didn't want to watch I didn't want to watch take that much
I just kind of like watch it. Hey, what's up? What's a motor motor guys? How are you?
But I just watched enough to get the idea of
It, you know, I watched the big and patriot thing. I watched he was in a backyard of the lady
I watched him on some
on the monkey app a little bit, and I watched him
talk about, make some bad taste jokes, I think.
I don't think he was serious.
I think, I don't think he was serious.
Why would anybody be serious saying this?
They'd have to be really mentally ill, actually,
to be saying that, but I don't know.
You know, there's really, there are really,
I remember this book when I was little,
it was called Dirty Jokes, and it was like from the 70s.
And it had jokes about,
Dead babies and stuff like that. I mean it was like and it was just like as a kid
I was like, oh my god, I thought it was kind of funny as a kid because it's like so shocking, right?
And so maybe I think there's some kind of it was not and may as maybe not funny, but it's like
I don't know. Who knows? I don't think that he is a dangerous person, you know, unless you, like,
maybe if you, if you, if you, like, go after him. But yeah, he's edgy in those circumstances, a troll.
Just a troll? I think so. I think, I think it's a little bit of a troll. Yeah.
I don't think there's something to it because unless there's like a conventional illness, which I like I
Kind of listened to some of his other shows today, and he's really a really smart guy actually knows a lot about history
I think I don't know if he was a military or something
But he has some kind of some kind of like specialist background
And he's actually really smart and and also when he was on a show too like explaining himself
I really felt he was genuine in the way he
I don't think he was like just making things up to like distract or like getting your people's mind
I felt like he was even if he wasn't even if it wasn't the whole truth. It's not good
I know I wasn't good, but it's like did he like like just like I said, you know
There's people with actual criminal records for violent offenses that are that have no problem
Going on panels and so he has no
Um, no record for this.
And even if there's some questionable things in his past recorded, I mean, it's like, you
know, that's never good.
But the end of the day, I don't think he ever hurt anybody, which is like really my standard.
It's like, did he hurt anybody?
Did he, it's not the same thing.
So, so child, a child abuse charge that somebody has for child abuse is less than whatever,
whatever he did as a joke or.
As a troll or whatever, right? I mean, it's like that's what I'm trying to kind of figure out
Because it's like no one has a problem. I mean any kind of problem with the other person. So
Endangerment it was it okay child endangerment. Yeah, well
Yeah, it wasn't for like I didn't say it was any kind of sexual thing. I thought it was the
Kind of a child. Yeah, maybe not and we could have been like good kid wasn't wearing a seat belt or something like that
I don't know or not in the car seat, you know something like that. I don't I don't know
I think it was something that not not too serious, but
at the same time
What he really did was not that serious like in my opinion, but
So I don't know I
Know I'm gonna basically
Whether I like was to denounce it right away, or I'm like it wouldn't matter. I still get called the same things
And so might as well just go with my heart and say I'm I'm more prone to
believe people can
improve change grow and
I'm I believe and I don't believe anybody should really be silence, especially if they might have some interesting things to say
You know, why would you silence those people?
Because
Maybe they're trying to silence him because they don't want there and I think that's fine. Maybe why there's been such a
No, no, you can't be in you can't say it because it's like he's because he's
He's he's talked about people, but they all talked about him. And so it's like isn't it kind of like
All spare. I don't know
You know, we can have different opinions about it, but
You know, yeah, I kind of I kind of think he's kind of cool
And so I don't know
He probably won't I don't know how often he'll
Hi, what's up? What's up team Kisco? How are you? But I think even that guy Ron
I never talked to Ron really, but I liked Ron on Sam and because Ron was like
Kind of had my back tonight and he's like so it's their issue. I have no history with any of yeah, exactly
Just waiting for my nap. We'll wait. Well, good morning. I'm a good evening
Okay, I'm sorry that was my that was my uh, that was my Alex
But um, yeah, I mean it's like basically we can just like I mean here's what I wouldn't do
I just like Paige said last night page says she doesn't want to listen to other what other people are saying
She's gonna judge people like how they're in their interactions. I know you don't have to be cool with it
No, you bet it's like at the same time does he deserve to be crucified over it? I don't really think so
I think it's like a little bit of an exaggeration
and a little bit of like a peer pressure kind of thing.
And people are just saying terrible things.
Like Tommy James was so polite on my panel,
but then he goes on Kate's and they're like,
oh, you know, I'm charging for songs, I'm grifting.
I'm like, you know, sort of disgusting and just nasty
predator protector and blah, blah, blah, blah.
So, yeah, no one has to be cool with it, but it's like,
You believe I do believe in maybe redemption forgiveness and stuff. So
Whatever you want to do if you want to block him personally
But uh, you know, I didn't mod him just so he's
Kind of say it feels like he at least can like
I'm sure I'm sure it's kind of hard, you know, being just like go go away. We don't want to talk to you
Go away. You're bad. You're bad. You're bad imagine. It's like it'd be pretty it's like, you know
Yeah, I get a little bit of that treatment, but it's like imagine that guy and it's like
I just feel I feel more empathy and sadness about it then I
Don't know
Kind of like want to be the place where people couldn't I
Don't know go it's nice. It's not like it's like we're in the same room
It feels like we're kind of in the same room sometimes, but
You know, we're all safe in our own houses in our own
Environment he was paying you're paying a hundred dollars an hour from movers
Seems like fair pay
Yeah, you don't see it going. Well, okay
Well, I think that has a lot of whatever if my channel goes down if I go down with the ship, whatever
I can go to kick like he is and he looks like he's having a pretty good time over there
I don't know. I'll go to fucking kick talk and get glazed and get it get 10,000 likes a day
And I'll just be happy
Instead of just like begging for a dollar and 10 and 10 likes and on this show for hours and hours and hours
Just brutally getting trolled and made fun of and just like the worst. They treated it basically pretty bad
Rather, you know, maybe I'll like it better, but I'm doing some I do have this catalog
Hey, we've been guests here. Well, who's this? Who is controlled? Okay. Hold on one second
Hello
Hello, who's this this vanguard?
Hello, who is it? I am kid. It's vanguard. It's a vanguard. I hear your voice. Hold on. I am good
You're controlled. What is that picture? Is that like a penis? Oh my god. Oh, no, it's not. It's a dog. Okay
You control
How much control do you think you have when you call my dog a beavers?
You c-
Well, he's a wiener dog, a wiener dog.
Yeah.
It's Van Gogh. No, that's not a weenie dog mate. That's a fucking stuff. You're bull terry
Pitbull, it's like what pitbulls are from right? You can't see the tree. You can't see everything about it. You
Was that your is it is it is that your dog or is that just a dog?
My dog
her name
Her name. What's her name?
Mate mate mate do I deserve they call you what?
Mate, I'm telling you how many times have I told you my dog's name. I'm not gonna tell you
Lady bird. Lady bird. Remember that, Prince King of the Hills.
Anyway, thank you. Thank you. Where have you been? Where have you been?
I've been here. I've been right here. I've been in my, you know, yeah. Been home. I've been,
I've been everywhere, man. I've been everywhere.
Fucking nice one. Can you do me a favor? Can you sing the soggy bottom song, please?
Yeah, that one the soggy bottom from a brother where art though. Yeah, okay. Hold on one second
I don't remember the lyrics start to think that okay goes ah, okay it goes like this it goes I
Don't fuck it. I don't fuck it the harmony, right, but I got you go. Ah
Oh, let me hear the harmony. I'll remember it
Oh my gosh, I can't get it there, I just need to hear a little bit of the harmony, so I don't totally screw it up, okay.
Got it.
I got him, I'm going out of key.
Hard to sing.
Hold on.
Yeah.
Okay.
I am a man of constant sorrow.
Oh my God, I can't even sing it.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, I'm, where's the lyrics?
Okay, I got the lyrics here.
It goes, I, oh my God.
Okay.
Um.
Of constant sorrow I've seen trouble all my days. I've been farewell to Kentucky
Place where I was born and raised the place where he was born and raised
Why quite a while I can see the siren song
What are the sirens and they sing the song and like
first little baby I don't know this little baby's right let's put another way let's put another
way can you remember the very other popular song where the other guy who was in prison
Oh, that was a KKK song. Remember that one when the KKK was singing and dancing and stuff?
What is the KKK?
They are the Ku Klux Klan and they have a book called The Glory.
I thought it was the modern Republican Party.
Well, pretty much the same thing. Without the hoods.
You know and they are actually they're like I don't like the Knights Templar a little bit
They're kind of like you know these and well, you know why they were those scary outfits
You can see in the silly ass. Can you ask a serious question? No, thank you. Of course
Why did you think my beautiful dog look like a dick?
Because it
Does I just see the I see dicks everywhere?
Look
Good hi axe. How are you? I'm good. Do you like my picture?
Well, do you know you know what I believe about EI, you know what I mean about
You're really bitching me big clips made this, okay?
Before you insult me about my AI make
So can you apologize to me please? No
Why not?
For what?
Because you said my beautiful female dog dog
There is a dog and it's not yeah
What is it? It was controlled and I thought you control your
Is that one thing you control you control?
me
Bankers like you're like snorting you're like
Right come on right say he say welcome back welcome back. Can we ask you two factors?
How many black heads did the AI?
Incorporate how many Brett brought blockheads
Black heads made the spots
How many oh, okay. Well, I don't know big clips made it you have to ask
Yeah, but look at this one. There's another one. I have have you seen this one, too
I there's another great one. He made it. I mean some people some people would probably be insulted by it
But I take it with a grain of salt because it's you know, it's better than like being called Cyrax or something
But here's the other picture. See if you like this one. How is this one? What do you think?
How's that one so you couldn't sing soggy bottoms?
Man of contents are
Okay, better it was better than the first time
I'm kind of remembering
You know what do you know what?
Do you know what a Coachella is?
Coachella, yeah, it's a music festival in California
What about a multi chambered what?
Is that like a chamber pot?
Wow.
With like two chambers, one side for the P, one side for the pu-pu.
It's multi-chambered.
Or is that like your stomach?
What's a sea animal that sounds like your coachella?
Is it, okay, does it sound something like maybe this?
Do you really have, like, access to that much piety?
Peyote, yeah, actually when I went to Amsterdam I did peyote at the hostel they gave me these cackles
I made a tea out of it, and I tripped my balls off. Yeah, it was great
You've got more access to peyote in fucking California. They've got
Weiner doesn't look like a weiner guys. It looks kind of like a weiner dog
I'm sorry. What dreadful artwork is that? A bay? Yeah, I know. Bay, bay, bay. Did you see, did you
see that you went to a place in Amsterdam, red light district? Yes, I was in a, I was in a
Well, yeah, oh my god. Well, it was 2000 year 2000. And so, um, cannabis was legal here. I've had many years there, mate. I've spent many years there, mate.
I used their fucking, bubbly, bubbly machines. I used their volcanoes. I went upstairs, downstairs, back stairs, and also...
You were going to the sex shows? You ever go to the sex clubs? I got kicked out of one.
Can I tell you, I bought a ticket there once and then I was called a professor and had a tenure.
You bought a ticket there and they called you professor?
Who's loyal?
You don't want to tell you who loyal is.
Full to doa who's loyal to full to doa
That person
Yeah, I mean
Come on
Yeah
Hey, how are you doing? How's it going? I'm good. Just popped in to say hi. You don't have to kick off your other guests
I'll just he was like talking over all of them back up, but here's kind of
That's Vanguard. He's from England. Yeah, I think I know who he is. Yes
Alexander me is
How you do
How am I doing? I am chilling. That's how I'm doing there. There's a lot going on revolving around psyche this weekend
We're almost in the start of the week, right?
Look, I think it's a bad boys club is becoming a thing. I
Like working it. I like how you chose to make someone a mod. I didn't even know until watching and what was it?
Imagine being a janny clip
and um a certain um addict who i'm just waiting for oh i shouldn't say what i'm gonna i'm not
gonna say it okay try to tell you about i thought that it was very hypocritical on their part
but yeah i'm loving it i'm loving it so alexander alexander when was the last time you said the
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
I only used the word twat because I think that people on the other side of the pond like to use that word, but I could be incorrect.
I'm having so much fun tonight.
Do you like my dog?
Alexander, do you like my dog?
Do I like your dog yeah, here's his dog. I can I can see it. It looks like a nice dog
It looks like a very regal dog actually like he's getting ready to hunt something
Like maybe what what what you called my dog a meal
I said he looks regal.
He's a female.
Oh, a female?
Well, how would I know?
You know, I said it looked like a penis.
He's like, oh, it's not a penis.
Yeah, but yeah, I'm just going to just see penises.
Well, a female could be regal, you know.
But I didn't know it was a female.
I mean, to me, all the dogs that look like that,
I always assume to be male because I'm not a dog aficionado.
No, definitely not. You've definitely both of you do not have the eyes of you do not have the eyes of the vanguards
I don't I plan to get a dog at some point, but um, it'll be it'll probably be a male dog not a female
Yeah, you need a nice guard dog
put this way, put this way, put this way, again, the eyes of the vanguard, um, Alexander, um,
Sykny, can we talk about California here, please? Sure, what's over in California?
Have you been to California, vanguard? No, definitely not. Okay.
Well, come out and visit. I you know, I guess
Expensive it is but you know, that's why we got a crowdfund a party. It was initially gonna be
Good times Palooza in Michigan, but he stepped down. So I guess now
We got it to psyche Palooza, but we're gonna do it in the Joshua tree area
Raise money
we're gonna fly out prize winners fly out prize winners to what are you going to
fucking hire a fucking g6 or what
Well, no, you're gonna have to get on like a peasants plane
To get here, right? That's that's gonna be what we try to do
I don't I don't want travel peasants me. You're gonna get a g6 for me
We both have the same birthday we're gonna make magic happen
We don't even have to have the same friend group nothing
We're just doing shit
So Alexander, can I absolutely talk about the lubrication that's gonna go on this fucking event please?
Lubrication what KY jelly? What are you talking?
Who said that?
I mean drinks or alcohol. Yeah, I think it means alcohol. Oh, well, I mean I some of everything
I mean it depends on the person
I guess people want shots some people want wine that would be me
Some people want some shots of the boring shit
Do you have my?
People would want THC drinks, maybe.
Some people would want mushroom-infused drinks.
I mean, it's California, so you never know.
California, no doubt about it.
People might want human-infused drinks.
I mean, are we going to get some Adrena Chrome?
Oh, my god, that was quite a party.
Well, I mean, hey, I mean, look.
Did you see? Did you just see
that? I don't remember what I
come from. Children. I don't
know. How dare you? How dare
you? You're **** What? You
**** What? I'm going to
It would be already bottled and stuff like that.
Someone in the chat is saying, I'm trying to be sophisticated.
I'm actually trying not to be sophisticated.
I'm working on it.
I'm trying to, you know, take it down quite a few notches.
If you can give me some tips.
Alexander, can I ask you three questions, please?
Okay.
How would you find religion?
How do I find religion as in what my religion is or what do I think about various forms of spiritual?
No, no, no, what I said is how do you find religion?
Like how do you find God are you asking?
No, I said how do you find religion? Okay? Well, I'm gonna answer it in the way. I'm interpreting the question
I found religion through tragedy, trauma,
and basically wanting to end it all and realizing that I was a fool to think that life was as hard as I thought it was.
That's how I found religion.
Hey Gotti's in the chat. What's up Gotti? How are you in chat? Good to see you.
Oh dear, we've got no feet fucking stinky feet fucking goatee here. Fucking good.
Gotti's here. Kind of nice. Yeah, he says hi.
I love Gotti. He's my favorite guest on The Psyche Verse Show.
If it wasn't for Gotti, I don't think I would have been, um, effectively recruited into the cult that, you know what?
That's not a very good distracting tactic. I'm asking you questions.
Come on, I have two, three questions. You only answered one. You only answered one question. Come on.
Meeting our system and we'll be okay.
Yeah, right.
Sorry.
Are you turning red?
What is going on?
You only answered one question.
Why do you have that picture behind you?
Big Clips made.
It's one of Big Clipses.
And I finally came to enjoy them.
And I like this one especially.
It's not.
Well, look, let me tell you.
For it to be a caricature, it's actually not a bad.
I mean, if.
If, if like the teeth were whitened or something.
Yeah.
If I didn't have teeth.
come on you're supposed to have very white nails come on you come from California you
come from California you're supposed to have very white nails there
I don't know. I don't. I don't
know. I don't know. I don't know.
know. I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I don't
So, what side of the Americas do you like, east or west?
Topography-wise, I love the west side of the United States because I love the mountains.
The ocean is a better quality of ocean.
I like the canyons, I like the desert.
Oregon, or California in the
morning.
No, she knows what I meant, but
she's not answering it. She
knows what I meant.
No, I thought you meant like
what I told you what I like.
I'm from
West Coast, but people wise, I
like the East Coast better
because, well, my, my dad was a
I grew up around more east coasters probably than west coasters. I think I probably embody
more of an east coaster mentality. I'm a real asshole when I think about it. West coasters,
they are too, but they hide it better and that's nice.
Yeah, you've ever seen the Saturday Night Live sketched the Californians and it's the kind of like it's on Saturday live and they're all like
They're like all blonde and they're like
Having wine all the time it's like they are everybody on the what on the west side even if you're black somehow they're blonde
It's crazy. I don't know how that is but it happened and it's a wonderful thing. You know everyone
Everyone if they want to be blonde should have their blonde moment just so they can have it because
They people need it. Are you saying that Hitler should have been blood? He was a redhead. That was his problem
Yeah, was he a real ginger?
But you're asking Vanguard not me. What do I know? I mean, I mean either because it's like, um, yeah
I don't because yeah, he he also I mean there's been saying that he was vegetarian. He might have been
Gay or like, you know, at least like, you know, he was very into fashion. That's why the troops
look so
Can I just say three things but I wasn't allowed to say three things before
Hugo Boss was very popular in the fascism regime.
Oh my god, you just kind of trailed up there, Vanguard. Are you okay?
Vanguard, are you awake? Vanguard, wait, you're on the show. Come on.
All I heard was Hugo Boss.
And maybe that's all I needed to hear. I don't know. I don't know
fashion
Does fashion feed?
No, I say it very clearly
Fashion is a very
specific regime shall I just see it's a very popular fashion
because the kids nowadays they don't have a sense of style they don't know
what's going on we need more fashion yeah
agree well because again they got well
Um, I don't I don't mean I don't know if I'm like that like fashionable fashionable or not
But it's like you are fashionable because you don't see you're you're interesting to me because
You deprive yourself yet you
Can I just ask, can I ask you a serious question before you, you go any further, Alexander?
Well, you're gonna anyway, so you might as well. Go ahead.
Um, why does site keep going left and right behind the mud green eyeball?
The green eyeball, yeah, you can see that, see my little green eyeball right there, there you go.
It just keeps going. Yeah, I'm kind of like, kind of, I'm in a good mood today.
I'm actually in a really good mood today.
Yeah, I've been feeling better today, I have ups and downs sometimes, but I'm at a high point right now.
I had a good weekend and...
Well, you know yesterday I was kind of like like oh my gosh
I'm just getting so sick of streaming and like you know and and I felt like I was like
Well, you better not get sick of it now you put it all the work
I mean you're just gonna start it. Don't be a quitter. What are you talking about?
I know I was like now I can't quit like
Yeah, and so and you know I still got my channel and
And wow it make my I've been working on the codex and stuff and you know crystal Marie was
I mean come on the green eyeball. I mean how many fucking wrinkles on the left hand side the right hand side
The codex is like it's I think it's looking better. I worked a lot on it and I think I'm
I'm getting there on it and it's it's it's looking pretty good about half a million
half a million trans
That are all searchable now and
It's all right, right, right first of all, can I just say psyche to interrupt? I do apologize for that
Go to the smelly feet. He's having a good day
He's having a go at you. Okay God, you're being mean to Vanguard. Come here God if you feel like it
No, no, just give me kisses
Oh my God, you're so sweet. There you are.
I love you so much.
My little baby.
And there's Rudy right here.
A little orange, a little ginger.
And a loll's over there.
No tricks, but I did have a cat named Tux that comes by at night now.
You know it's interesting the so but I I still have hope that tricks will
maybe reappear, you know, sometimes cats do the whole thing.
I think you're gonna see, well, you already know my thought on it,
but I think you're gonna see Tricks again, but I think,
because think about the situation. Like, I don't remember much of my drunk and less talk with you,
but I remember some, and I know I was, I was giving you my thoughts on Tricks,
but I mean, think about it. Tricks was second generation in your household.
Yeah, because Lola is mom. Maybe he didn't want to be momma's boy anymore.
Right, they were chasing each other, they're all over there.
Can we ask you about tricks, please? I'll remember.
Yeah, go ahead, go ahead, go ahead.
Um, um, who bought you your last Pashmila?
Well, the last cat was I think the last cat that was brought to me was Lola actually and then she
About you made I was torn about Alexander's last
My last scarf
My mom my mom is who bought my last one. Yeah
Well, why are we why are we going from scarf to cat? We were talking about the intergenerational
drama which became a trauma for Psyche when it came to tricks deciding to leave the nest
because it's possible he was tired of Lola nagging him.
Yeah, she went a little bit and they because they didn't get along after you know
He had it's a certain size
She would just swat him away when he would try to you know feed feed
But like recently he was just chasing around the house and he was actually born under the TV set a couple years ago
You know and so I had him from a tiny. Oh my gosh
She kisses kisses kisses. So um, so yeah, I mean I had him from a tiny little they look like little mice when they're born
It's like so and I was like what?
Why isn't the cat like eating them because they're so they look like little mice when they're born and then they turn into these cats and stuff.
But um, yeah, he was he's a beautiful little cat. He's very friendly.
To be honest, to be honest, I haven't said anything. I was asking an honest question that came into my mind because I am the vanguard.
And I just asked it.
So how dare you? How do you?
Well, Vanguard, did you get, did you get, did you ask her three questions, Vanguard, or did you, or did you ask two, I forgot.
That was amazing.
I've only asked two so far.
One more.
Are you ready for your third one?
Yes.
Alexander.
How would you find capitalism?
Well, that's similar to the other question asking how I found religion. I mean, what do you mean by that question?
Like what do I think about it? What do I?
Want to gain from it? Do I want to destroy it? Like what do you what are you wondering?
well
Capitalism capitalizing on something to gain from it is capitalism, isn't it? Yes
to
What is Capitalism?
Well, I think capitalism should all revolve around me.
I think that really I should be the only capitalist and I should divvy out, you know, whatever resources are that I'm in control of to the masses, I'll put the people in charge that I feel should be in charge.
And then I think the world would be a better place.
That's what I really think about it.
Now, will that ever happen now?
But that's my thought.
If I ruled the world.
Yeah.
Well, thank you for answering my three questions.
Thank you.
OK.
Yeah, Vanguard, you had either three wishes or three
questions, and you asked the questions.
And so there you go.
Mm.
Oh my gosh. Thank you for the questions. There are no questions.
It was. So how was your weekend? Did you have a nice weekend? Um, I um,
Me? Uh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I did. I got a lot done, surprisingly, and um, I'm gonna have a little
bit of a busy late afternoon tomorrow, but then um, things go back to normal and um,
Preparing for a few other things I'm doing this year that I'm keeping secret
Somebody was asking me earlier if my list of seven names is still applicable. Yes, it is
Are there people who are exonerated from that? Yes, there are is it fair? No, it's not but it's my world
It doesn't matter
That's it, that's all I'm doing
Mm-hmm. What are you doing?
Well, um, let's see. Yeah, I I uh, you know, I had a pretty good stream
I'm assuming it lately in the middle of the night and uh, and
Do you want me to get my dog out there psyche?
Can you show your dog in on camera?
Me they've already showed you it
We see the picture. Well, if we can see it
What's gonna happen this week? So it's 426. Okay, so it's almost May. Okay, almost May, May Day.
It's spring and I don't know the spring is a great. I love when I love spring. It's a great while I was born in winter
I'm always like a winter born, you know, we're born. We're like we're born
Actually, this January 7th is right in the dead of winter. It's right in the middle of winter. It really is. Yeah
It's chill background music unfortunately, she doesn't have very good background music like it has these like kind of like
weird
So so youtube sorry a certain mountain youtube won't let me change my avatar
YouTube won't let you change your avatar like uh
But on the stream yard. Wait, I think you can change it on pan. I can change it for you
Can I change it for you? I can actually do it. It's all goatee's fault. Goatee's got the smelly fish
smelly fish
It's all your fault goatee. It's all yours
Two days later, they imploded the Tropicana Hotel.
Oh yeah.
Well, so you know, the guy that like,
there's some guy that like I've tried to
on a live Trump or something,
but he's from the city I was born in.
And so the FBI was over in the city this weekend.
Like-
You better be careful, Psyche,
because that one guy who also had an issue
kind of looked like you a little bit,
they're gonna find you for some reason.
And
try to do something to you, not like there would be any reason as to why.
Right, come on, come on, Alexander, Alexander.
Okay, I'm a blogger, a blogger?
A blogger is another one, it's because you guys have a certain kind of face.
Alexander, Alexander, are you trying to claim Candice Owens' fucking immunity?
Me? I hope I can. That would be great. Look, if I can get the power of Oprah. Candice Owens.
Who else? Who's Oprah's friend?
Gail, Gail, Gail.
Whoopie Goldberg. Who else? Who else?
Can I grab it?
Come on, Whoopi Goldberg, in the previous book.
Candace Owens, Candace Owens, Candace Owens, come on.
I mean, come on, come on, come on.
I'm working on it, because if I'm going to be a leader of hers,
I'm going to have to hold on to all of them.
Let's just see this.
I just want to go home.
Oh, my name is Eric Kirk, and I want to go home.
What is that from?
I don't know.
Oh, Charlie Kirk's wife, I guess, right?
Is that Charlie Kirk's wife?
Well, did you not see the White House press correspondence dinner last night with the fake fucking wood?
No, I wasn't watching, I'm just over, and until I'm an hour, I don't really care.
And Erica Kirk ran off with her cameras and went, I just want to go home.
Erica Kirk is dangerous.
That woman, I can just tell some things about her.
She is not who she seems, but she is very well placed.
Yeah.
I just remember when she like was on the coffin,
like touching like his hand, like his hand on the coffin,
like on Instagram that she put it on a couple of days
after he passed away and she was crying on top of the coffin
with totally his hand or something.
I was like, that's kind of bizarre.
Look, she put it on Instagram.
She's bizarre.
She is a very bizarre woman, and she is not
who we think she is.
And there's not going to be.
I've been telling you this for years,
but you've all called me a cunt for saying so.
why are you blaming me i haven't even known about you for years i've known about you for a couple
of years but not for years put it this way i've told you donald trump succumbed for years and
you all hate me for that come on over
okay well I mean what are we gonna do they're all reptilians they're they're
here to extract our blood because they want our emotions and that's how they
get high you know for them it's like I don't know methamphetamine yes can you
ask are you still playing the piano
Alexander yes I am and I'm still pretty horrible at it
Then can you play it I don't have it set up right now
I I actually have barred myself from the piano because guess what?
What I'm getting a guitar for me to butcher that now
So, that's going to be what's
next. We all have any
instruments at my disposal.
I respect you. I respect you.
Neither can I but can I just say
when it comes to the piano, did
you ever try something like
spectacular like piano concerto
When I was a little girl and I did like piano recitals and my mom made me go to piano lessons and whatnot
I did a lot of very classical music
Bo, I was wrestling in Schubert
Schubert, do you know Schubert?
No, but I know about Cubert
Yeah, that was a fun Atari game actually my mom would want me to play band of the opera on piano and so I got very
I love that musical. That's a really that's a great musical
Yeah, and I did play you know what do you know what was the best musical ever?
Have you ever seen Barbara Strids on the infidler on the roof?
No
Did she play fight? What was her name? Fievel? Or Fies? Fies?
I can't remember, but it was Fiddler on the Roof, wasn't it?
Fiddler on the Roof. I don't know. I never saw it.
Now they have Diddler on the Roof starring P Diddy.
It's up for real. It's a really, really...
Like a Diddler on the Roof, aka Vanguard's Life Story, got it?
Don't fuck!
If you don't want to rap about it, I don't know.
Well, fill her on the roof.
Fill her on the roof, fill her on the roof.com.
You know what, I've seen a play called Chorus Line, and that's really good.
They sing one singular sensation, then that's where that comes from.
Mate, if it wasn't Fiddler on the Roof, mate, it was called Yento.
Yento, okay. Yeah, Yento, that's what...
But also, you know what's one of the weirdest musicals in it was also a bad movie was Cats and because the cats just don't look right.
They're like, they look kind of disturbing. It's like.
Well, they were people. I mean.
Like when Mike Myers was the cat in the hat, that was like a horror movie.
Did you want to see that? That's bizarre.
And then I mean, I don't know it's like humans just don't look great as cats and it was kind of like a weird movie
I don't but I'm I didn't like so I don't really do
Thunder cats under cats. Oh, yeah, they look pretty good
But um
The opera then we'd like get the sound why you know
Pumper
And all that work
What was the female tiger's name that you'd like to be on guard?
You get a crush on him?
Me, me, me, me.
I didn't like any of the mitts.
I was too old.
I was like, what the fuck?
You talking about your budget?
The fuck?
What the fuck?
Then her cat's a Broadway musical.
Yeah.
I actually, I saw Tommy on Broadway.
There's a musical.
First of all, first of all, can we ask you a huge question, please?
Yes.
Me or I was on...
Why, why do domestic cats...
No, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no, she's gone, no
Yeah, I think it's Roger Daltre starting it and they got Tina Turner in it. They've got um
Anne Robert. Come on. I'm not even going to not even going to not even going to ask the question
What?
Do you like the music? I'm playing some nice background music. The background music.
No I mean you keep nodding your head. You look like a fucking lizard at the moment. Look at you.
Did you ever see um what else did you ever see that um there's a show called dinosaurs
But there's also a show called land of the loss and they had like this this character named was that Harry Harry characters name
It was called me
Do you know do you know the best thing that ever existed on fire earth?
well sex
Women no the best the best thing that ever thing that is a thing that is
No, the best thing
What freedom best things in life are free, right?
The best thing that ever existed on planet earth
Was
What is the best thing on Planet Earth?
The thing, right, he's sort of got it right, it's not the thing that, the thing is, like
that twat from Deira Kiris, that fucking twat from Kenaria, right, that twat, but have you
ever seen an octopus before?
An octopus?
Is that the best thing in the world, the octopus you're saying?
I don't get it. Are you saying pussy?
The Octopus can think in so many levels to actually change its body colour to situations, etc, etc, etc.
That fucking invertebrate can, shall we say,
I think most vertebrates.
It's like a big brain, actually.
If you look at it, a big brain almost.
We have a guess.
They are octopuses.
They say like, if there's any animal
that initially was from off world on earth,
it would be the octopus.
Right, it's very alien looking, right?
Is this Joey on the panel?
Why do they attack you, Sonky?
Why do they attack you, man?
I'm so tired of them attacking you.
I know, but who is who attacking you today?
Those cowards.
Those cowards, those cowards.
Well, it's okay, it's okay.
I mean, I just, it makes me stronger, okay?
Say hi to the, say hi to our family.
Continue on, I apologize.
How are you doing?
Thanks, sweetheart.
How are you doing, Alex?
I've been doing good, sweetheart.
I'm good.
Oh, dear.
Yeah, well I had this picture of Joe it's like someone sent me this picture of Joe with is like the top of his head shaved off
Well, let's keep that. Let's not do that. That's not I'm gonna show it real quick. Here it is Joe
Let me take a look real quick. Let me see real quick. Here we go. This is
What the fuck is that
So there we go
So Joe was someone made someone was talking bad about me
I know I got some people upset right now I'm triggered and I'm like, you know, but you know at the end of the day
It's like I just
It's like when somebody's being happy like psykias, why do they got to be jealous and bring his happiness down with their anger?
It's just I'm tired of it. You understand? I'm tired of it can't you can't make you can't they can't lower my vibration
I'm I'll still be happy, you know, good. That's what I want to hear
Positive negative
Well, yeah, and it's like, I think that it's like, you know, if you're, if you spread positive vibrations, it's like, you can, you can affect the people around you in a positive way, and you'll sometimes you'll notice, like, you know, if you're agitated, people will be agitated, but if you're like, sending out good energy, all of a sudden, like, people kind of transform a little bit.
And so, I don't know, I just don't like when, like, you know, head.
Somebody talked to me today and he's very nice when he talks to me like on panels
But then he goes right to another panel and starts talking shit and it's like and it's like it's really different person
It's like a chameleon and I just get confused by those kind of people, but who are we talking about?
Um, is a certain, certain ginger who had some bintenol?
Oh, well, that's, that's his name.
I mean, look at how, look at how horrific he was when it came
to everything that I went out on my way to do for him.
Like, I mean, let's really keep it real.
And here we are literally four years later and even on his
binges for whatever reason, I enter his mind.
That's called guilt.
Yeah. So, you know, you can't really do anything with a person like that.
You just kind of got to look at it like, well, that's the way that the tennis ball bounces.
That's the way the cookie crumbles.
Like, that's the way the cookie crumbles.
Yeah.
Well, Joe, you're a ginger, Joe.
What do you think?
Hey, watch your mouth.
It's like, well, I see the beautiful ginger hair.
Like, how have you, how have you felt like being a redheaded?
an alien or do you feel like you have a bigger temper?
No, we're not, sorry to be honest,
but I was in my twenties, I got so much fucking pussy.
I'm just like older now and I gave up.
I'm like, I don't even care anymore.
I don't even cry.
But I used to get, I swear to God, I did you.
I don't care what the fuck you think about me.
I did use to get a lot of fucking pussy back with it.
All right, psyche I fixed your picture. I want I want to upload a new edition
Wait, I'm not sure which one I need to upload though. Just give me a second
Yeah, I think you'll like this it's a friendlier looking picture
Oh, here we go.
Oh, I like this one.
Look at this.
Oh, there we go.
There we go.
All of a sudden, I don't like your hand on the left.
I got to fix that.
Okay.
Yeah.
Plus fingernails are too clean.
His fingernails are too clean.
No, that's a joke.
That's an old joke.
I like that better.
I like that a lot better.
I think I love that.
Actually, I'm going to screenshot that right now.
I could make it look more like you, probably.
You know, I was watching, you know, some of the videos you made,
and you just had like such a talent for...
I like making it look like the person.
Yeah, I love that. I love that.
And it's like some, you know, you have a great talent for that.
It really inspired me.
Well, my mom was an artist.
She was an artist and a music major.
I'm not like up to par.
with her when I think about it. I got to work on my skills a bit more. I'm lazy when I think about
it. My parents are both like, you know, my dad was so smart and successful. And my mom was like,
so beautiful. And it's like, that is so cool. Your mom was an artist. That is so cool, though.
Yeah, well she still is like you never stop being and she's still with it. I don't know you're right
I didn't even say like was
That was my bad I can see where you get it from now
Yeah, I always wonder like where the fuck did Alice get this from like you know what don't make sense now
It actually don't make sense
Yeah, I was and also like I was like
Like some of the just like the lyrics and stuff that you you like that you come up with early
So funny, like, I don't know, I think you're funny.
I love the, I love the Psyche's Boys Club commercial that you made, and it's like,
some people said it kind of looked like a cross between me and Blogger a little bit.
You and Blogger have very similar facial structure. I mean, it's, it's interesting
because Blogger is very petite and you're very tall, but, but you're, you're, you're slim also
when I think about it. I am slim, yeah.
but but like heith wise you two are opposites
Facially probably just because you both have like actors like like traditional actor looking faces
That's probably why people because you don't really look alike. It's just like
First glance
Yeah, you both have good teeth you both have long hair, um
Would you ever be open to streaming with him?
I would.
I would love to.
You know.
That would be insane.
Oh my God.
I feel like that should be a donor goal like like blogger, psyche, neat, like what what would y'all do?
I don't know. I mean, I'd be afraid like I'd be like so attracted. I don't know.
Are you afraid I like hit on the person? Would you be attracted to him? Really?
I think he is kind of. You're a little leather.
So here's who I've learned about you, psyche. And don't get mad. I say this publicly. You're in love with yourself.
Well, okay, you like, okay, psyche does tend to gravitate toward people who are like him
in some way, shape or form. Okay. Um, appearance wise, the most similar. And I don't know what
I was saying to you about this other night, because I don't remember because I was yelling
and screaming and I was drunk. Now this was a private phone call, but that's me.
Benny Blanco you and Benny look like you could be related to me. Oh
I always thought he was very younger version of you. Yeah and then yeah, Benny
He looks really good with his haircut and stuff. He's come over a few times on the show recently
Um, he was very I think he gravitates toward you because he's in love with himself too. Yeah. Yeah
I think blogger takes issue with you because in a way you're kind of like
Um, competitor without trying to be because of like your book have like a very sculpted sort of face
um
Yeah, you like me, I'm your personality and a woman's body of color, so that's interesting.
You're in a woman's body.
Yeah.
You don't know about that, Joe.
I'm just keeping you, please.
I just thought you said something.
You know what I mean?
What I was saying, Joe?
Oh, I know what you mean.
I know.
Trust me, I know exactly.
What do I mean?
You mean that's like he's a good guy, but he's in a woman's body. Like he's a great guy
But do you Joe? Do you know that?
Psyche and I have the same birthday
Get the hell out of here
Yeah, but I'm a couple years older than he is, so.
What day is it?
So I can look this shit up.
No, I'm not telling, but we do.
No.
I wouldn't make you really-
Well, let me, can I guess it?
Can you tell me the month and I can guess the day?
Yeah.
Is it June?
No.
It's the first month.
It's January 28th.
No, lower.
Oh, we have another guest coming up.
Have you been on trackable?
Here comes Untrackable to the show.
Welcome.
Oh, I like him.
I actually made some AI of untrackable recently I think I have a handy like let me see what it was like
Yeah, I mean yeah, so it goes through all the phases of them like if you shows me it's like this is a
This is the first phase of the werewolf trans
Transformation was like that. Oh, I saw yeah. Yeah, that was that's him
That's undraggable right there and then there's like a then he goes into like a little bit darker, like
Like if a dog had light hair on his beard that would be him
And then this is the third point of the transformation.
Is J-Ball got sex with Sasquatch?
That's what I think I'm looking at.
Good.
It gets like that?
Whoa, my god.
Is that thing that is?
No, that's...
And the final...
That's the, like, thing that is.
And the final transformation, there we go again.
No, that doesn't look like, well, I mean, if he became a Neanderthal slash werewolf.
Yeah, I think intractable has a nice face.
I'd be curious to see what he looks like without a beard, actually.
One time he shaved off on my show, he was doing donations like $5 and then he was swiped
down like a big piece. He has a nice face. He has kind eyes, a nice face. He looks happy
for the most part, but I feel like something. You saved his beer's life. You never seen
when he saved his beer. He shaved it like a week ago and it grew back in three days.
A week ago. Well, he also likes to run around in his underwear too. Good for him.
We got $3, $3 in this channel.
Yeah.
Are you in Alaska, in fact, or like somewhere cold?
You don't have to say exactly where.
Are you like near Anchorage, perhaps?
It was cold when I did what I did.
Yeah.
Oh, OK.
Are you in Montana, Wyoming?
It was, uh, I think, I think it was, uh, roughly 20 degrees when I ran in my underwear.
Uh-huh.
In it up.
I love it.
There's a door now.
The entire life too.
Where are you at?
I can't tell.
He might be from the Appalachians, actually.
From the Appalachians?
He might be with that.
I wouldn't doubt it.
I would doubt it.
I thought it was Oregon or something.
Oregon or Washington, but I-
I thought it was from an article.
He's-
he's he he has like a mountain i think he's from the appellations but he might want to stay untrackable
so i'm not going to track him yeah he doesn't want to be tracked and so he's not going to ever
tell us but i could track him is he related to the wedgars like is he related to the wedgars
I was right, he's here at the Appalachian, he's an Appalachian man.
Yeah.
I have razor mounds.
I do know the Appalachian.
I was not born here, I was not raised here, but this is where I am.
Okay.
Calm down, calm down sir.
Yeah, yeah, I wonder about your background.
It's easy.
tell me to call them
I wasn't raised here, I wasn't barred here
I was doing whatever I was like saying
untrackable is stuff
untrackable is the kind of person
you will want to track you
let's say you go missing
and you're like
maybe you go on a camping trip or something
and all of a sudden
something happens and you go missing
you want him to find you
because he'll get you back to safety
I'm like, it's so good to see you, I've been starving for three days, thank you.
Pretty much, yeah.
That's what will track you, you can tell.
Kind of a joke at work is like, you know, you see all this every day and they come in and they're like, oh, you're beard, you're beard, you're beard, you're beard.
And then you shave it, and they're like, hey, why'd you shave? I was like, I had to kill somebody.
Oh my god.
Well, maybe he did, you know,
and that way he can't be tracked.
Oh, he might have killed someone with his bare hands.
He looks like he's killed someone with his bare hands.
He looks like that kind of thing.
You don't gotta kill, man, you know.
If you can spill them off, you never know.
Times are tough.
You know, look, Hitman make a really good living.
Well, yeah, I mean
I would never buy one
It's like I think I mean I don't work a regular job to hide the fact that
For hire, you know, I'm saying
You never know, you know, this is the interview of a lifetime
Look at him, he cracks his self up. Look at him. Look at him. He cracks his self up.
Well, he actually lost his temper recently because I never saw him lose his temper like
that. He got mad. I do remember he got mad. What did he do inside me? So what happened?
What happened? Someone was like bothering when he started yelling, God damn it. For who was it?
I tried to hold up his- What? I think it was Sig or something like that. But he was like,
You little punk, I never seem to get mad if I did something wrong
I know, not at all.
No, he didn't know what I was saying about that.
The last guy in the chat is saying...
You did something right, actually.
You did something right.
Like the teas.
So he thinks you might...
He might be Swiss.
You never know.
What?
I think that he's tricking us.
I think that he is in a different country.
I think that English is not his native language.
And the reason I think that is because...
the way he speaks English, it's like he learned English from somebody from an urban area, but
his look doesn't match up to the area. And that is the case sounds like you learned English yesterday.
No, it sounds like he it sounds like he's known it for at least a decade, but he learned it from
someone of ethnic origin from. I got I got you. That's what I think. But I could be wrong. I'm just
watching me the first time music on the background. What's this music come from the ducks? It's
like one of the standard. Oh, really? Streamy art. It's kind of like a little R&B. Yeah.
Better. Am I am I in Chicago or something? A little R&B in the background. It's only
a dog song. Jesus Christ. What are you talking about? Why are you against the duck song because
Well, you know what, there's the guy from Godigator, that's the actor from God.
You are able to like make these, like look at this, you can like put these A.I.
I thought it was also bro.
You can make these, so that we have like, you know, they're, you know, easy and like
Alexander McQueen, we're like, we're like these, this like the quack.
Oh, Doug Tracy, that's how Tracy.
And then there's this one and then there's a we made some more like this was we've a ghost in one of them with
There's a dolphin and there's the doctor's page page. It's a dolphin
No, it's not something that she's the dog. He likes being the dog
Why you are doing that why no that video that you put up that you
Is wrong what you didn't you know it
That was so fun.
It was.
It even made a dover nose.
Yeah.
Well, don't play the original video, but I know it's that video.
Oh my God.
Oh yeah, you're talking about when she was giving these to you guys.
I don't like that you're equating that, because Paige is a very nice young woman.
There's ghosts riding the dolphin with the ducks on, like, little, like, little, like,
Yeah. Now you said that that's Paige. I don't want him to ride Paige.
There you go, there you go.
They're called the Hepper Gang and so there's like the Heppers of the Apocalypse or like
the Gang of Tracks. Those are bulls.
Yeah, they're bulls and then we have, there's another one of ghosts. I think that's ghosts.
What's baby? That's baby oil. It's a baby oil baby.
I was covered in baby oil and then we had like then there's Alex fighting the
ghost and then we had Crystal Marie flying a plane there's like there's um
who is that thing that is and and uh Jamie's Cowboys with me and I think I'm
the skin walker. No you were saying because you made the picture of Gaudi is
that supposed to be Gaudi? That does look like thing that is.
Oh, wait, well, oh my gosh, oh, wait, it's a black girl, it has to be me unless there's another black person who's infiltrated the cult
Someone was sick. I forgot who it guys. Does anyone remember who was with sick? I'm not
Surgery that could be him and there's like better or not be sick toilet, right? There's a spider toilet. Oh
Who are these witches? I think that's the
Gang or something like that. Are you the spider?
Yeah, you're you're holding on to the lid of the toilet. Yeah
I'm not going down without a fight.
You better use some webs at those witches.
Yeah, but I never thought of the broom gang.
I never thought of it like, you know, the actual like wish,
but then it's like, that means sense kind of,
I have a video where like,
Wait, are they the broom gang?
I think so.
I think they might be.
Cause I never like told about it.
Yeah, cause the brooms and they're like boys.
They never go nowhere alone.
They always team up.
They're like witches.
They come into COVID.
Like if you talk to one, you got to talk to all three of the witches.
Well, I don't like witches like that.
I like solo practitioner witches and why do you think I hate Christine groups?
Well, you know, I actually like Christine.
The one I have the issue with is Vita as we all know.
But I think Christine is actually.
I don't think Christine's always gonna be Bita's friend.
I'll be honest with you about it.
I'm always on and off with her like we go to long last week
and now this week she hates me again.
She calls me scumbag and stuff,
but it tells me get the hell I go to this place.
Christine is gonna outgrow Bita.
That's what's gonna happen
because Bita is perpetually about.
late 20s, early 30s.
That's where she's at.
Christine, Christine actually reminds me of,
what's that girl's name?
Barb Sawyer Lifestyles.
Oh, I heard of Barb Sawyer.
And Barb.
departed from, um, you know, I thought you meant Christine, my, you're the mom from Beverly
Hillbillies.
I thought that's yours.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Sorry about that.
Sorry.
Maybe we're talking about Christine from Phantom of the Opera.
I mean, what Christine are we talking about?
That's what it was.
Oh, he's Christine's.
He does have nine grandchildren, so she's a grandmother, so, you know, hey, watch your
mouth.
You're not gonna die any time soon. I might you don't know tomorrow's never promised. That's true
Well, how have you been? I feel like you're being neglected. What's going on with you?
well, I'm not being neglected and I can tell that you're not being neglected because it looks like you have
ball sacks hanging from your neck
I'm sorry
Let me ask you is that a Freudian slip? Have you been secretly watching Monica Foster porn?
I was uh, I was looking at your avatar and I'm like, hey, there was like balls
If that's the case things happen, but how are you doing? I'm just gonna forget that I even heard what you
I'm trying to go. Do you know Alex has born? Did you go watch Alex has porn out there?
You can actually I don't think anyone should watch it because it'll forever
I'm actually gonna watch it later tonight
Actually a mind control mechanism
specifically designed by the Illuminati. I am a plant. And if you watch it, it will forever change you.
You're damn right.
Oh, but for the badger, for the badger, it's up to you.
You know, a certain fentanyl addict went on a rant recently, and I was mentioned, and
I didn't hear the whole thing, but I did hear that for some reason, and he specifically
used my adult industry stage name instead of my name when he said this, he said that
The cat's out of the bag. The dog's off the leash.
I am a real Illuminati plant here to offer some of your minds for the better.
So whatever you can find about me, please do learn it will sucky when I watch Alan's is born
I was like I wish I was the actor in that video. I wish I was that luck
I was surprised to see Lexington steel a lot of that was like my final like big scene
Well, hey, emphasis on the word big, but he's a big by the way guy Lexington steel is the epitome in my opinion of what a black African American man should be who's a professional in the adult entertainment industry, he out.
He out does Mr. Marcus, Jack Napier.
And does he have a big dick?
Yeah, would I be able to normally deal with that non-everyday basis?
Probably not.
He has to be his alter ego.
He has a white equivalent, Eric Everhart, and I did a scene with him too.
Eric ever heart is like he's Eastern European. He's hot man
The guy was dating at the time who was a Canadian white guy
He was jealous of Eric ever hard because of that scene, but Eric ever hard. Yeah, perfect name ever hard
That's what you name yourself if you're a male porn
Well, you know what Eric ever hard eat your ever-loving heart out you piece of shit
Well, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe Joe
Well, if you are, I am too.
But look at me, yeah, I mean, good times is like my age,
and good times looks like 20 years older than me.
And we could call the boy the mommy.
Not when he shaves that beard,
he looks like a different person, he does.
I wanted to shave his beard, yeah, he was-
Have you ever seen him with his beard off?
Not really, I don't think so.
Really?
Pushy, his big long beard.
When he answers, he's actually pretty handsome, he's a good looking guy.
Never seen him with his clothes off. Hello. No, I never know that was done at me is Joe
and I were friends. We never even met. Yeah, and I enjoyed it. I enjoyed it actually. Yeah,
there's a I love that kiss. That was one of my first kisses. That was exciting. That was the
first time I ever kissed the man and I loved it. I liked it. No, it's not your first time.
No, no, no way in hell.
Yeah.
Alex, calm down.
I don't have to calm down.
I'm keeping it real.
Maybe one time I kissed a guy in college, OK?
At a party, everyone was like, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Do it.
Like, kiss that guy.
I think Joe publicly is super duper straight
and always will be.
But I think that if you could look her in him.
Things could happen.
Oh, you know, you give me a lickered up.
You better bend over, pal.
My God.
I think so.
I'm sorry about scary things like that.
Yeah, no.
I don't know about you.
Well, Psyche is a top.
He's not a bottom.
Yeah.
Well, you know what?
I'm a top two, so now we're going to have to wrestle.
Does he have fucks the other way around?
That's how I know you're open to being a bottom, Joe,
because you put out the offer of wrestling.
I know. You kind of put out bottom eyes. You could put out bottom eyes to Alex.
Like you're a mom. I'm a woman. I'm I'm supposed to be a bottom by default.
Yeah, but you love anal. Like Alex, you know, I don't actually in this weird that
people do you understand? I've never done an anal adult.
I've never done anal either. I just heard you say anal. I'm not deaf.
You know, there's this argument about tops and bottoms.
I turn each and every one of you upside down and turn you inside out, you know what I'm saying?
Wow. Do I need to make it?
No, actually, I don't know what you're saying.
I don't know what you're saying.
I'm smiling face right now.
All right.
Yeah, we've been fucking smiling about beer.
I screamed after you on Shrackable.
I'm gonna get AI of what you just said.
No, I think we fell fast one.
She's literally right next to me, you hairy fuck.
He found Bigfoot and he's on my show.
I don't think he's going to get that.
Yeah, we found him and he's wearing a Nike face.
I'd like a trackable space.
He does.
He has a kind of face.
And eyes, he has that next warm smile, he's like, I like this, I just lose it was behind the
mountain and like he comes to rescue me. It's like a very movie. That is big, big muscle. Yeah,
pulling you up. Yeah, you can help me. You'll be like, Oh, hope you and I'll be like, Yes, thank you.
He's like that. He's like that for a month. And that's no way you're rent, but then I'll be on my way.
Well, I must admit, she just wants to use your body and be on her way.
She just wants to use your body.
I'm a bit of a pirate, so.
You're a bit of a what?
You ever been on the news?
I'm a bit of a pirate, so I will gain.
There is nothing I will do where I won't gain.
You understand?
Yeah
Where's the parrot because if you're a pirate you need an eyepatch and a parrot on your shoulder
I just need I just need what you have that's what pirates do
Well, how do you know I'm not a pirate's pirate? Maybe I'm a apex super predator and I'm out to get all the other predators
I'll set myself up as a bait and then I'll figure out what kind of pirate you are and
then I'll loot all your plunder, but then I'll leave you a little bit so that you can
survive.
I think I'm hot.
Is that what it is?
Is the Psyche's Boys Club just going to be your, your, your like lunch?
Yes.
Ha ha ha.
Why do you think he's not supportive of it?
I would say good luck to the other pirates out there.
Yeah, I'll get a cute vlogger.
He's leading me to the slaughter and I know it, but it's okay.
It's alright.
Well, maybe I should make his picture more handsome.
Maybe he'll grant me mercy or something.
Oh, my God, what do I do?
Well, I made this one a thing that is kissing ghosts here.
This is a thing that is kissing ghosts right there.
I don't know, that didn't really...
That was it.
Alex is gonna make a video of this guy
like being a grizzly bear, like kissing her,
like as a bear in the woods.
So like, oh, over you can start forest fire.
Oh, speaking of parrot, look at this.
This is like, this is a goddess with a parrot.
She has a, she's always has a parrot.
Oh, what the hell is that?
Yeah, she is she's like an Indian goddess rap leader. She's flocked. No, it's not but she's always flocked by parents and
She plays the Vena right there. Let me take a look. Okay. You know
My mom loves like like she my mom is a Christian, but she's always loved like the Indian art and whatnot and
Like my mom's face strangely like I've been looking at some of that art even posting
I always wonder like and I asked her I'm like is there like East Indian and she's like people always have asked me
But her face looks like that a little bit
But she's not
But she likes Indian art
So she probably previous life maybe was Indian or something
Forget the face
But I don't think I had this life. I felt sometimes Ellis that your beauty was out of this world
Like your beauty was on well, that's because I actually am an extraterrestrial. So you're on point about that
Thank you
Well, you are yeah, you you are gorgeous and
I'm an alien and nobody wants to acknowledge it, but I'm just you know
I thought 3i Atlas was gonna pick me up and that didn't happen. I'm pissed about that
So I'm stuck here on this godforsaken planet reading the Bible on my other channel and I come to talk to Psyche and
Every once in a while Joe comes up and I flirt with undressable and that's my life
It's a good one though, Alex. Thank you
Well, I'm going to travel some this year and I'm going to harass more streamers
But when I harass them, I'm going to give them cash prizes
I've decided that. Have you ever seen this picture, Alex?
I
Remember that from the San Fernando Valley when I was spending my time in the adult industry
I always knew that I recognized from somewhere and
This other one. I'm not sure who he is. He's interchangeable
That's Aldi from another dimension
I think, but, um, yeah, yeah, look, I'll tell you something, Chris K.
I think it's many things. I think he verifiably might be an adult performer. I think he verifiably might be
Verifiably he might also be psychic. So I don't know what to I'm not scared of him. I went on his show
And I didn't do anything to me, but I'm a, I'm a woman.
If I was a man, well, like imagine if I was a man instead of a woman.
What do you think would have happened to me?
Well, I mean, I know someone named Squidward, like, uh, and that's like,
he like lived with Chris Kay for a little while and, um,
and I think that's well and Chris K also said he wants to come like he wanted to move in with me
and he said do chatter bait or something like that I'm like I don't okay then he's like whoa
and he was talking about being the bottom too I was like whoa okay well I wasn't even thinking that
far ahead though wow um I don't know why I don't know I have had some guys in this in this panel
kind of why
I had someone named Lou sassel like the guy whose name is Lou sassel and he wanted me to go to San Francisco and
Meet him, and I don't know. I just met him the other night Lou sassel
I take you
Would be a guy named loose asshole, but you don't want to meet up with a guy. It sounds like a great guy
Lou sassel SSOL Lou
Sassel
Joke your mind out of the cutter
Was his other name blogger?
No, his other name was Eric Shun, Erech Shun, Eric Shun.
Oh, Eric.
That's what his name was.
But he sounded pretty nice.
He sounded pretty nice.
But yeah, I don't know.
I didn't see him.
Probably is.
He sounded pretty nice.
Like, I'll bet you, like, if you decide to call yourself that, that's probably the biggest
leap into depravity that you've ever taken because you can remain anonymous doing it.
Like, really think about what true depravity is, okay?
It's when you make that conscious decision, I'm gonna be bad.
You know do something that might buddy out, but doesn't gross me out like like a lot
label myself as being like a
Depraved person because of what other people do does gross me out. I don't like anything
That has to do with anything
slimy, or gross, well, like that.
Okay.
I want to be.
But I do have a depraved mind in other ways.
So I can't really say I'm depraved because I'm not sexually depraved, I'm depraved in
other ways.
But the reason I'm not sexually depraved is probably because I worked in civil industry.
That's probably what happened.
like I used to do that, like you know, I'm more of like a twisted, depraved person that does not
have to do with anything gross. Yeah. Yeah, I don't like anything with bodily fluids. No.
But you, but you mentioned and you say it this way, the adult industry.
Yes.
Watch it.
I take issue with that.
No, I know he does it's okay
Just let it out, and I will not be overly upset you can share your thoughts
Cuz I know
It's okay
No, tell your thoughts because it's not a conventional way of being that I to be honest with you untrackable the kind of woman that I am and I know it actually doesn't have anything to do with my ethnicity is just my personality.
If I were to ever come into your lands where you likely live in your everyday life.
of the
I can't I can assess what he's saying before he says it. Yeah, so
Corporate well the reason that that term sounds
I I apologize for raising the question about terminology
No, no, I just want to say that adult industry
Is
Exactly what we are once we make our decisions and we go full-heartedly towards them
because we
Whether you kill somebody or you fuck somebody you are an adult
So
The military adult industry is basically porn for you know
chillers
You know hey
Do you know that sex workers make the best spies, which is the adult industry, often at least to assassinate them?
Yes, I do know that.
If you know Mata Hari, have you heard of Mata Hari?
She was a spy.
That boils down.
You got to work it down because just saying adult, it's not enough because...
Well, look, the thing about me in trackball is that I come from a certain arena in life
to where at one point in time.
I did have to use very quote-unquote sophisticated language, language that was deemed as socially acceptable for some very off-color or off-the-normal Rails thought.
But when I hear you speak and that's why I am a fan of yours and trackable and I'm not just being flattering. I'm being genuine.
I do know where you come from for the most part and I will not say, but I do understand
why you feel as you do and I understand why a woman such as myself would be very disturbing
to you and just keep in mind that I will never negatively impact your area of the world.
Don't consider yourself disturbing
Can I say one thing, Sluggy, one time a trackable beat, it took off her underwear on accident
and your beard looked like her asshole, like her ass cheeks.
Thank you.
Yeah, that's Tux right there.
In front of the TV.
Yeah, in front of the TV.
All right.
Hey there.
It was so hairy.
It was so hairy I couldn't even like, nose.
His little white spot on, I'm sorry you can't see that.
I see him.
Yeah.
Oh!
Hi, Lenore's looking at him.
Hi, babe, that's Trix's brother.
He was in the same litter.
So they all ended up with a bit of white on their chest,
but I'll tell you, Trix is the looker.
That's why he got abducted.
That's what I think happened to Trix, I'm sorry.
I think that there's very happy human woman
in your neighborhood.
Honestly, like, I'll tell you, psyche, if you really wanted to find tricks, you could.
Here's what you would do.
You would just assess who in your neighborhood is a single woman between the ages of 35 and
50.
And whoever that is, one of those women is probably only about less than 20 women.
One of those women is not that easy to Alex to find it.
Yes, because all my cats live next door.
Tricks was very attractive.
Tricks was a very pretty gray cat with the green eyes
and then the little white underbelly with the chest.
And it made it look like he was wearing like a little gray suit,
like an outfit.
Because I named I he had a brother magic and magic had just like white paws
So clearly they're white gloves, but tricks was like had like the kind of long gloves
And so magic and tricks went together then I had pie and there's a woman in your neighborhood who taught who brought it one day
Tricks will come and visit you if he feels like it
But he's probably being spoiled to death by whoever that woman is probably getting fancy fees
probably he's in fancy feasts he's listening to some lo-fi music that's what single women
lions do taking cat and he gets he probably always wanted to be a single cat and he gets
to be away from his mom and i know that that's hurtful to psyche and lola
Um, what's the other one's name?
Um, there's Rudy.
Rudy didn't care. Rudy looks like an uncle of mine who passed away recently. Rudy's just like,
fuck you. Leave me alone. There's my hub around. Oh, there's Lola over there. Lola's looking over.
She can see what she's looking over. Lola is depressed. I've noticed that. That's why she's
been so- Oh, I see Lola like stared at us. Yeah, she's getting a touch right now.
it was to be a single cat and one day he won't get along with the ladies who brought him in
and he'll find his way because cats don't forget that they just don't just like dogs
he's i'm telling you tricks is probably only about three houses away from where psych
Actually, I've had someone do a pendulum reading on that.
And they said the same thing.
They said he's like nearby, like right.
It's one of the neighbors knows where he is
and has him inside and stuff.
I think whoever that lady is,
I think that she saw him before.
She probably even knew that it was the cat.
But every one of your neighborhood
would see that you're the cat man.
Yeah.
You're basically the humane society
of your area of where you live.
Yeah, you're the cat man, I'm cat daddy, cat daddy, we'll look like we're all in our
basically just pigging right off the street and brought over here, you know, I think untrackable
probably adopts animals too as I look at him, I'm reading your answer, do you like animals and trackable?
I'll adopt you you animal and it's that no I think he likes well
Do you like animals or do you not like animals untrackable?
Yeah, we we took a Jack Russell
Would you adopt Sam man? Can you let untrackable talk? I mean you guys were getting on me about
Interrupting untrackable and now you're
trackable
Speak sorry
Your animal adventures
Yeah about um ten years ago
It was freezing cold in December and this Jack Russell jumped in my wife's car when she was coming home from work and
She's been with us ever since
It isn't a thing for us to
Like just
seek
But what comes to you comes to you?
And the animal chose you
Yeah, she she's a pain in the ass
She's chewed shoes and bitten feet
At the toe of the bed
but now
Her you know, we called her we called her Lucy because she looked like a single cigarette
She's all white with a brown on her nose
And she's she's starting to lose her brown
She's that's because you're so Caucasian
she's
you took the ethnicity out
she fell lies every five minutes if she did game or salmon
she fell lies every five minutes
and when Bakelip says you're insanely hot by the way intractable I think Bakelip's mad
ow!
I thought Bakelip said something to me
he's hot it but he has a wife
he has a wife
what about me Bakelip
that's cute, the Jack Russell Terry
I don't have a wife, I'm single
he has a wedding going on
I bet untrackable you know what I used to know this guy who um it's it's a crazy I'm not gonna tell
y'all the whole story but he was someone that I know tell the whole story Alan tell the whole
story sweetheart okay I will tell the whole story he's somebody that I met in the adult industry
but not in the area of the adult industry that I was in but it was still all the legal adult
He based he was like a fish out of water
He was like the little mermaid, but a man but for real and he was a redhead
So you all know how I love the redhead
This particular young man for whatever reason he was like the little dog following me I couldn't get rid of
So I took him in he was my roommate for a while when I was living in Hollywood, California
But he always told me
that he was from and I'm not going to tell y'all because he would be able to identify him so but
he was from a different area of the US from the California area and he always told me he was like
the only reason I'm out here doing what I'm doing is because I'm making money to be able to take care
of my family and expand my family
And I get back home and that way we can buy off the debt from something was going on with some land that he owned
And he had to pay off some debt
But he wanted to be free of it and I and I always thought was he telling me the truth or not?
Well, guess what it turned out he was 100%
principle
somehow who found me years later and sent me all these pictures because I did help him a little bit
but he sent me the pictures of his family and everything he's like don't show this to anybody but
this is the reality I'm never going to be that person again that you met but thank you for
You know, sheltering me and taking me because I did.
I took him in for a long time.
Did you ever feel bad that you doubted him?
I didn't totally believe him, but I kind of,
but it turned out that everything he told me was beyond the truth.
He actually doubted him and you doubted him.
Well, I did because I'd never heard a story like that before.
But it turned out that he was of like a fundamentalist
Tight background they never knew and I would never say that's why I will never tell the story really the way I could
But he really did and you know what the last daughter that he had
He named her Alexandra
You swear
I swear, I swear to God, God could strike me down right now.
Yeah, but I didn't know because when he told me everything, I was like, well, you probably
shouldn't be going as far as you're going.
So I reeled him in a bit and I helped him like, like, you know, not do.
what he was doing before. And I'll, if you ever want to know about this psyche privately,
I will tell you, but I'm not telling anybody else, but I did help him and I helped him in some other
ways too. But everything he told me was real and the truth and I couldn't believe it. And I was
like, wow, it's a good thing I did help him because if I didn't help him, what would have happened?
that's what Alexander means
And maybe I won't like who's going to defend me nobody will you know sometimes people did you fit me I shouldn't be I always had your back
No, you don't oh Joe you at one point you said you're gonna kill me for beta
Well, that's an accident
That was an accident. I think that is had my control and we ever had an accident. I'm trackable
The last thing that is having in mind control. Look at the cats are kissing. That's Lola and her son
Look at the cat's French kiss scene
Son joke. No, the mom is
There's something to be said in the name and
Are they on each other? Oh, come on. I received I received a name from like
And my daughter's name is my name, so sharing names is very, it's very important.
Your daughter's name is untrackable.
And well, he doesn't want to tell us the name for obvious reasons. He doesn't want to be trackable
At the meaning of his name is the same as I would assume the female version of his name that his daughter has
Imagine a boy named Sue who has a dog and gives his daughter the name Sue
Well, guys and wake up boy was named Sue. I don't
It's a famous song
So you want to know what my daughter will have much
I have a I do have a I do have a piggy pillow
What the fuck is that?
It's my piggy pillow
I'm a
It's my pillow
Aww
It's a piggy pillow
I think I'll be on a session scared the fuck out of me when I say the reverse
Yeah, I love it.
I'm happy to catch back tonight.
So, he's over there just sitting chilling.
Yeah, last time he came in, but I like stood up
and then he like ran right out.
But tonight he came in.
Well, Prop's untrackable.
He's a nice husband.
He sounds like a nice father of a daughter.
And I hope that, like.
everything works out for you, untrackable.
Because-
Well, what about me and Psyche?
Can we get a little process?
Well, Joe, you don't have a wife.
You should.
That woman that we always see at your house,
you should marry her.
If I did have a wife, Alex, it would be a lot easier.
I wish it was you, Alex, my wife was.
Well, I would not be your wife.
You're racist.
Well, I will make you be my wife.
You don't have a choice.
You're going to make me well even more so why I would not be your wife.
I just like Alex, don't pull that duct tape off your lips.
You're my wife now.
Oh, come on, Joe.
I'll kill you.
That's what I was about to say.
No, no.
I'll kill you first, watch out.
Do we want to get violent?
We can handle that.
Yeah, we are.
We are.
Well, you know what?
That's why.
Well, look, I'm going to say some psyche, don't get mad.
Sometimes, do you ever think to yourself that you might be a descendant of Abraham Lincoln?
Um, yeah, I mean, when I had my beard was just like, I've noticed that about you recently,
and I'm thinking to myself, is that why he's in these communities that Abraham Lincoln
Okay, I noticed every time I brought up John Wilkes booth. He got like a little scared like something's going on here
Because that's probably
Alex do me a favor zip it. Oh Harriet Tubman kiss my ass
No, you're way sexier. No, I am Harriet Tubman
I have a gun under my
You're sexy
No, I will get you. Don't worry
Good coming in it, baby. I will
Underground
I'm fucking waiting. I waited for you. Oh, yeah, you you are you better wait
Yep
I'm announced to you
Yo, y'all are just being facetious about sex.
Yeah.
Well, we're not.
Are we talking about sex?
Because we're talking about the underground railroads.
What?
Oh, how did that happen?
You know, she's almost on the $20 bill.
They're saying that they're going to design the $20 bill.
Do you hear what intractable?
Like, how do we talk about sex?
Because I'm talking about the underground railroad?
You train going into the tunnel, right?
Oh, we have a guest coming on.
Hold on.
Oh, they better be Harriet Tubman.
Vanguard is back.
You get tight with Joe.
You're fixing to get fucked.
You know that.
Well, don't fret me.
We're a good time on track.
Well, thank you.
Well, hey, talk talk to me the way you were talking to her and you fixing to get fucked. You understand
What the fuck would you do about it?
You're retarded
I'll take it for you
Daughter again keep bringing up your retarded daughter. You fucking animal. I will
I got to go to bed anyway, psyche.
I want to be kicked off.
Kick me off, psyche.
Kick me.
I don't have my mouse, so I can't kick anybody off right now.
Well, do it.
Do what you're mind.
Do it with your mind.
I lost my mouse.
Cause I ain't gonna sit here and let some hairy bitch name on trackable dog shit.
I'll sack the fuck out of this nigga.
Get me on, bitch.
You're not gonna do it.
Can I just repeat?
He can't do anything right now, but he can let me up.
He didn't let me up. Who let me up?
I did. I found my mouse at the last second.
Hey, there's um, hey, hey, what was up? I'm completely numb. How are you nifty nifty nickel the Hebrew hammers here? Hello, Hebrew hammer
So untrackable, can he ask you three questions, please? Oh my gosh
You asked me what you need to do
met
What are the original stripes and how many stars?
We also have another guest.
Let me just put up a banner real quick
because I'm not sure I met this person in one second.
Hello.
Brandy?
Are you there, Brandy?
It's probably a fake person.
Yeah, I think that's...
Okay, I'm going to kick them down.
So, untrackable is not allowed to answer my question.
Is this the tactic?
It was 13 stripes for the colonies, right?
Go get the trackable.
Did I do something wrong?
You weren't allowed to answer the question you weren't even allowed to fucking listen to the question
Okay, well, yeah, what's your second question on track?
Right the second question do you think that?
Warp speed is possible
What speed is possible W. A. R. P. Warp Warp speed, you know, like Star Trek Warp, you know, like faster than light speed
You know speed is an equation
So it's
Relative, you know what I mean, but anyway, what's relative if you can see that if you can conceive it
Easily warp speed possible it's like the speed of light
Hey, I don't I don't think anything is impossible
But it is an equation and it is distance and time that is the equation for speed
Yeah, he was MC squared. Is that it or distance exactly? It's not exactly
Energy Mars work fuck off. Will you psyche you try to be
That is exactly the equation for speed is distance in time, you know miles per hour kilometers per hour
The
Time where you know, you could put a billion in there and
Handle it in a second. It's like do math. It's like how far
It's a it's a it is an equation distance and time is speed
That is the real question.
For this way, there's more things in Heaven and Earth, the ratio,
that we will ever understand, the ratio.
Well, yeah, I mean, it's like even like the human brain is like the most complicated thing that we know of in the whole universe, right?
I think that's us. We're the most complicated thing.
Well, that's why Un-Trakable said it was so profound because he's like, okay, let's look at mathematically.
Distance via time is
need, right? So what happens when the mind can no longer conceive the amount of time or
the distance?
Then that's when the travel becomes
instantaneous because you realize none of that matters. All that matters is the thought.
Wait, are you saying that time
time
I am the vanguard
are you trying to see
are you trying to see that you're
superstitioning
your quantum reality
you
what's up on draggable how are you buddy
nice to see you man
just imagine
You are this spaceman
You are
Hey, please
Yeah, I found Psyche, bro. What's up Psyche? Hi
Who are you? Who are you?
Who am I?
Is Mayel Martinez?
I am the Vanguard
Who are you?
Just imagine
You have left
You have left where you are
there there is no in does it matter how fast you go does it matter how far you
go you are have been sent that that's when it doesn't matter anymore we had
another guest Alexander
That's right
It's one way
I don't want to hear it, I don't want to hear it, I don't want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I want to hear it, I
You understand what we are now, you know what you are you never die you never grow old, but you must feed
I
Watch and wait for story hotelers. He wants to ask me why my name is Alexander McQueen. I already know why
You tell me baby
I have learned the history of the fashion mogul, Alexander McQueen, I've learned about
his proclivities toward the darkness known as Lilith, I'm really embracing him, I'm
also learning about the beauty of the world, I'm also learning about the beauty of the
world, I'm also learning about the beauty of the world, I'm also learning about the
about the beauty of the world, I'm also learning about the beauty of the world,
I'm also learning about the beauty of the world, I'm also learning about the beauty of
the world, I'm also learning about the beauty of the world, I'm also learning about the
beauty of the world, I'm also learning about the beauty of the world, I'm also learning
about the beauty of the world, I'm also learning about the beauty of the world, I'm
in regards to what psyche likes to bring forth, which is in parallel with Alexander McQueen.
So I think I do understand you, but I don't ever have to interview you if you're not comfortable,
but I'm not. I'm comfy, baby. Oh, I'm comfy. If it's just you and me in a room, by the way,
you know, in a virtual room.
You know what's going to happen at the end of the interview, right?
Part of the video in the middle of the interview, the sacrifice.
very and supposedly he was a pedophile. Let's dive into
Alexander McQueen. Oh, he wasn't. He was running a bigger ring
than have seen you dumb bitch. This is why you need to interview
me because you have no blue. I must.
Oh, he made Epstein look like fucking Mary Poppins.
I don't think he was a pedo.
What's he really, where is he?
Yes, he, oh yeah, he ran the biggest pedo ring that ever existed, baby.
Let's go get up right now on your little computers, Alexander, I know you got 10 fucking computers.
Oh, that's the Queen Prandtl ring. Look at him.
This is what scared me about Alexander. He looks smart, but yet so dumb at the same time.
No, no, no, no. He was used as a trial.
Epstein period of time.
yo vanguard just put spice on on on the top he's the cherry on top i'm still gonna
fuck out xander take it doesn't matter you're in bed with us we are snorting
oh he did a show he did a whole show revolving around the trauma of rape but he was gonna hit
I mean, I get it here
Wait, what are you saying?
What are you saying?
Successful one of the highest
Look at Lola.
Is this your beautiful?
Look at her little fuss.
Oh, Lola.
Lola.
It's okay.
Trixie is living his little
Trixie life, Lola.
Oh, you T.R.
Hi, Lola.
Hey, Lola.
You know, but it's a mom.
A mom who is going to worry
about their young.
Too high, Lola.
You know what you gotta get?
Lola, like a spa day to make
her forget tricks.
Like, take her to the spa.
Give her a little...
Sunday all yeah, well her other son is home right now, so she's like a little bit happier
But yeah, she always has a little bit of a fussy face. Come on. I'll be your mayor's you're the one that met this guy
Is he crazy or not?
He's not he's out of his mind. So that's not what I said. Okay. No, I just won't be doing
it. Thank you. Thank God, so wait, you met psyche. You actually met him. How tall is
He looks like he's a fucking old tree from hell. I told him this guy
You looking up at him your neck was sore the next day, right?
I'm on the taller end. I was surprised that he's as tall as he is
Yeah, I am okay. I'm up here my sister the one that twins are back, baby
He says he's a 6-3 too.
Alexander, I've got to earn your respect.
I figured that out because you don't trust me.
You don't know me.
You don't respect me, nothing, but I'm on a mission.
Alexander McQueen.
You're almost there, baby.
Don't quit.
Damn.
I have a long way to go.
You can?
No, it's after battle.
Don't give up
I have a long way to go, I'm just letting you know I am aware
I can only take you to the door of McQueen, you have to walk through it yourself
Well, I want to walk through McQueen because whatever's through that McQueen door is something that I need to learn about
Oh wow, look at that
Alex, tell us about your brother that lives in Texas
He needs to know
he's extremely rich owns of blocks of you know he's the real estate king he owns a
mountain of gayness why are you making me repeat this psyche
it's like a drag queen i'm a resort right
hey there's easy so let me ask my third question please go ahead
My brother's extremely rich
He's gay. He sucks cock. He's married to a man. He owns a lot of properties
Let you know come
Texas and many until gay resort. That's how rich they are. They bought a mountain
I don't know how the gays are so rich. I mean
It's my little brother. It's my little brother. I used to smack him around
This guy's buying mountains across the USA
Never settle and
Protective gay males are the same thing. It's gay stuff. I mean besides psyche and my brother
I'm not a fan of gay
All I can I mean gays are cool
I don't stop cock. This is my point on this very good. I don't stop cock. Okay. That's a no-no for me.
My boy, Psyche, sucks cock and I'm cool with him. You know, it's a metaphor and I'm like yo, but I like the guy.
He sucks steak. I hate it. That sucks. But he's cool. So I try to erase the cock-sucking point out of the equation.
You know
Me or like, you know, that's not gonna happen
I'm in a moral room. He's we'll keep it
I'm gonna bother him for what he does
You got gag reflex or what?
Fuck it Alexander you suck cock before
I got questions. Have you ever seen a cock with the girl only can put the head in her mouth
Like how big is the cock you can't even put it in your mouth like they can only suck the tip
like there's some giant cocks out there right?
what are you drinking?
there's some gigantic cocks flying around out there
like I think my cock is huge but
I mean they can suck my whole dick
I go up and down but I see some cock
you know you ever seen a porno and the guy
the bitch put only something on the tip
it's like a tree trunk like what
have you ever had that kind of cock?
let me answer the question
go go for it
All right. First off, if it's to the point of what you're referencing to where it's so big that you can't suck it
The my question would be is this interspecies? No, no, no, he's
That would be the first thing that goes on in my no, no, no, he's
I honestly because only what I'm saying is like a horse she's with a cock bigger than my arm and that's the black
I would not ever be with something that's not compatible to my size
Can I ask you a question honestly? Can you for us man? It hurts if it's too big, right?
Seriously, I'm not being funny. I don't I don't do anything with anything that hurts
Oh
Big man, you're killing the girl
she said she never dilated
That's like you're gonna take
tact, you know, feet and take
that two away. That's like
showing up, taking a hot dog
and just sliding it down the
hallway. What am I gonna do
with that? No, you're not
gonna. But six to eight inches
is ideal. I would think for
exactly. But what about when
20 inches comes along and says
hello?
It says hello to an ancient baby. It's out there. Martinez own life. You know, it's true.
No, you like it though. I guess it's every woman's vagina different size,
like someone like a public feel, someone like a little garage.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, I don't
what's called the razor blade, what's called the razor blade?
It's like the thin, like, line, you know,
and then the fat cat is like the fat cat,
and then there's the Arby sandwich.
I can show Saiki's head into a pussy and something goes online.
These curtains, man.
You can shove a pinky in some pussies and they'll be like,
oh, it hurts.
Yeah, Peter.
That's what I'm trying to get to.
Hey, what's going on down there?
Is it a cavern?
or is it like a little time, you know, a best of you or it just depends on if you go, right?
It varies from girl or woman.
That's true. Not all women got grenade nibbles.
Oh my gosh.
Different women and I think that men need to be sensitive to the differences between
women just like women are sensitive to the differences between men cause there's a lot
of differences.
You know I saw SIG, SIG has what looks like he said it, what do you say he said it was
like a micro phallus or something like that or some kind of like he has some kind of like
I don't believe any I've never seen this picture. You think about those micro thing
He's a psyche. Well, what's your what's your opinion on micro joints? I don't like the micro
But you know what like some women do like they do like the like there's a certain like women that
Yeah, they like to they like to scissor bang men
Well, pretty much some women don't want
to survive penetration
Women don't
Do I even want to know what's this?
Hetero women, but we're having a man conversation here extreme penetration
And I think that those women are perfect for the men
who are who are smaller in that department. And what's more to you? What's more to you? Five and
under six and under? I mean, the woman that has dealt with heavy artillery, nuclear weapon
come up like 40 times. What's more to you? I wish I could just like shut you up and
you can't can you see that that's how you're gonna know the kind of woman I am. Okay. The kind
a physical woman. I was, oh, she's dominant. She's dominant.
No, I'm not don't become a hacker though don't get all controlling
Men who are truly dominant men, but unfortunately they're
in our society
But I'm one of them baby
Woman who does not like certain things who is going to assert herself in certain ways
Who has been an?
independent and the legal
my car got off
entertainment industry
all right
who isn't independent
What I'm looking for is a man would not with no criminal record. What what do you tell me because I'm your man
Listen to everything I had to say and maybe you need to rewind the VOD
But what I was saying and what I am saying is that I want somebody who's as interesting of a human being as I am
That's good. Oh, yeah, there you go
And so that would be it.
Oh yeah.
Someone translate what she says.
Is there a translator in the building?
Thank you, what the fuck?
Let me see if I can do it.
You're not letting me talk.
I'm basically a fucking unicorn.
I shouldn't exist.
Unicorn!
Translator, hook me up, bro.
What the fuck am I?
Let's be up on it.
You're transgender.
That's terrible. Are you a transgender?
Why? No, I'm completely biologically female.
Oh, okay. Just making sure because you said you were a unicorn.
Wait, wait a minute. Wait.
Alexander, you're not a floaty diamond.
Don't tell me there's a story down there.
I would love to be a man.
If I was a man, I would just...
What?
So that means you pegged before. Are you a pegger?
You know, it's gonna stay on her mailbox if she gets married, he'll lose the money.
That's okay, Peggy, that's okay, Peggy, that's okay, Peggy, that's okay, Peggy.
and I'm one the headline. Yeah Peggy Bundy come on there Peggy. Hold on. Why did I get muted? Why the
fuck did I get muted? I haven't said a word. Oh my god. I know. I know. Okay. Geez. Alex,
he just said he has a video. I said I admitted it at least. Yeah. I went here about this white
slavery. I never should have admitted it because I'm listening to you. White slavery? Yeah. I'm
Nothing. Nothing. Nothing. I didn't say anything. I like that a male
Of the Caucasian variety known as less more in that particular adult fictitious
Video
I'm an actress less more. That's a good name
that was his stage name
I wouldn't jump straight to actress baby porn store
shut up to you
I am DB I'm a real actress asshole I've done mainstream
a real actress he said that's funny
yeah I've done mainstream also
hello
hold on so um
alright okay real actress
you mean like um you know Demi Moore
Kind of mainstream Hollywood regular movies. That's why I'm on IMDb
There's really good. I think it's not digregory, but it's like a guy that's very similar to digregory
He's a kind of comic and he says he's
People would be like
Flavor he did yeah, well, that's the name of the movie Halle Berry and monster ball and I'm not ashamed of that
There is a
Someone who reminds me of less more in my life that makes me upset
All I have to do is watch that scene and I feel better and that might prevent murders. You never know
What you getting fucked it's gonna prevent murders. Am I missing something?
Fucking somebody else
Y'all are rockin' her, y'all.
I love her. I love her.
Have you ever seen a bro? She gets into it, man.
The pussy shakes, he moves.
She as soon as laid there.
Like a lazy fuck, you know, you're a fucking girl. It's like fucking a mannequin
Some bitches like monkeys. They can fly around the room. He's one of the room flyers
You're a failed corn star
I wasn't failed because I did win awards, strangely.
But I was there and I helped to push some legislation
when it came to adult entertainer rights.
And I left and I never let myself be pimped
or go into the illegal market.
And I'm not ashamed of any of that time in my life.
It was illegal market.
It was illegal market and maybe.
prostitute, selling myself to guys like I'm back page or Craigslist and I never did that.
Yo, Alex, I heard you finger pop Alex.
Fucking easy, bro. That's not me. I'm just reading the chat. I'm reading the chat. That's what I'm doing.
Don't know Alex. Are they talking about McQueen?
I'm just reading the child
Okay, there's any way fuck them out Sandra. You're the best
So your friends are onies. Are you gonna break it's hard again? I'm an entertaining guest on
Don't break his heart again. Okay. Okay. He's a good guy. We're building something here. We're
But you miss writing the first time around
We're creating new
horizons
new
Beyond the ice wall. I don't know where we are
Yeah, I just I feel like if I know it's less it's more. Yeah. Well, I'm just gonna hold on to Alexander McQueen's life jacket
In the in the frozen ocean and I'm gonna say near far
Wherever you
I think we can get it going again. I'm gonna have to swim underwater to somehow like
I don't know, I have to get the engine going, but I think I can do it.
Yeah, I'll be right back. I'm gonna go check out white slavery.
We're going.
Okay.
And eventually we're gonna launch from the ocean into outer space.
Oh, wow.
Oh, check it out. See what's up with white slavery.
Okay, can you make a video of psyche one over here you me and Alexandra shooting from under the water
What did they call it again?
What a space
Well, it's white slavery, let me tell you what studio made it
Me, Ronys and Alexandra
I did go kickass, kickass studios
I'm on pornhub right now
Everyone's on pornhub
Oh my god, come on
Well, sometimes it's pornhub
Kickass studios
To gas studios man. Oh, yeah psyche bring put it up man. Pull it up man. What the fuck?
Don't don't pull it up psyche. Do not pull it out
Angel whatever she says you do
It will be a to s violation
Right white slavery don't listen to them
All I see is the last year snow white
in the seven doors video looking for it can find it it's what but don't put it on the screen white slavery
yeah that that I don't even know why you're saying that but that's a little way I was wearing what was
I wearing that day he's coming in it's coming in tree I was wearing like a denim outfit white
You want the link?
He's here.
I know the Monica Foster.
It's the link.
Yo, uniform.
Shout out to you, Miss Alexa.
Yeah, it's okay.
I'm not offended.
Miss Alexa.
Here's what you got to understand.
You know how many guys clap to you?
Well, that to me was lifetimes ago.
I mean, I've done so much more in my life.
I've owned, closed, reopened businesses that have nothing to do with adult entertainment.
to me, that was like nothing.
Yeah, but you don't have to throw that.
You met Roni, you had dinner with Roni,
you had tacos, and then you still have a green board.
You should have agreed to me.
No, what my favorite part about having been in the adult
entertainment?
You work together, smoke the joint,
and then you disappear in the two months.
And you put a 30-day ban.
That's what made me happy.
i got to date really attractive like physically attractive but successful men that is what
me losers and every once in a while i still carry overs into my present day and i'm happy about it
but that's what i kind of want to stop that's what's up
Cut out to you.
He's a hot, attractive, successful man.
He's got the top of the line, and I was like,
ah, I achieved my goal there.
Nice laugh.
Which is the opposite of ugly broke men. That makes sense
Correct
And when it happens
It does happen
But it does correct it so thank you. I heard you do corn also
i don't but i did like i mean i did like i think i did like a cup of tea
i know you did i already know you did oh my god well i know you did
it didn't pay well enough for me to be doing that okay you got used and abused i understand
guys aren't that popular but i was actually like it was actually like women that said they were watching
and then there were the guys that they were like oh used and abused uh sweet dreams by urythmics my first
Some people are meant to be abused, do you believe them?
That's a hot song.
Can we play that?
No, we can't play that
You know my times why not you can't play one song
Okay, okay, it's weird
That's like a Groucho Marks game show last night like to tell the truth or something and then I
You know got taken down for a little bit damn girl
Yeah
That wasn't even her nose that was the gate
The other way, who's the nose of the ass cheeks same thing?
For now that was that was the gate breathing breathing in taking an errand
So who are you I'm less. Oh my god. This is less less is more this is less is more on this on the stage
Yo, let him let him hit the link man. Let him hit the link. It's real. It's right next to you. Yeah, shout out to the prolapser
Oh, that's not okay, well, I don't know if you've ever vloggered my...
També, yeah, look at her laughing.
I don't know if I've ever vloggered my asshole, I mean, I think I've seen a picture of that, yeah.
Yeah, remember?
You know what's crazy? I've seen this, yo, yo, we were celebrating,
we were celebrating my friend's bachelor, right, bachelor party,
and everybody's like fucking chilling and making love, like all sweet to this girl, like this dancer.
Oh, she fucking gave me a dance and I realized she had fucking these holes on her back
This bitch fucking hooks on shit and fucking dangles. Oh, you know from ceiling and shit like that
When it was my
Yeah, but when it was my turn, when it was my turn, I was brutal.
I was brutal and everybody was like, why are you?
So hold on, you, you, what'd you do?
You, you were a party.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
A woman hanging from the ceiling with hooks from her back.
And then what'd you do?
No, she wasn't hanging.
She, look, look, look, look, we, they ordered her for, for the bachelor party.
So she came through and started dancing
You know, you know after the dances and all that shit you pay a little extra, you know, I mean for other shows
So when I look everybody was being sweet with her
Everybody was being sweet with her and shit like that. But when it was my turn
It realized that she had those things on her back, the fucking hooks, the holes for the hooks.
What gave it away when she, oh, bro, bro, she was, she was giving me a lap dance and I really, I
seen it and I felt it. I seen it and I felt it. So when it was, when it was my turn to have fun with her.
What's doing shit that niggas didn't even they couldn't even understand the evil one look at that
I just
Had to do what I had to do that song
Yeah, when I seen that I said, well, man, everybody's fucking being sweet to this woman
I'm just making panels of you. You're gonna have to do it in a week about this
You gotta fucking punch this bitch in the thwot
This is why I've been introduced to Lilith because now I understand the real function of Lilith
Come on, bro. The show. It's a show. It's a show. You came for a show
Trish police um Lilith doesn't like psyche that much I'll tell you I'll tell you oh well
Some of her avatars do some of them don't like I have like no because she no there's there's uh
There's a fast set
What about next what about his daughter
Stand does he go with child support?
No, so let's say some
But what's going on?
It's another reason but that's not though. No, she would like psyche more
than most men
More gay, but the but because of certain
affiliations
That's anyway, man. It was cool hanging out with you guys. I can see you guys
A lot about Lilith and that's how it has helped me understand psyche more and actually looking at this
They're cooking them in a dumpster full of fire.
A foresight that I didn't even know I embodied when it comes to-
Kentucky Fried Psyche.
They're cooking them.
No.
What do you have to say about this?
Fan man?
No, he did not.
He's burning.
No, he did not burn.
He doesn't have abs like that, by the way
No, let me see the abs you don't have abs not like in the picture
Nope
no
he's actually kind of
you need to take a ballet
dancing class
honestly if this thing went to
Calvin Klein
nowadays they like skeletons
they need models
all they want is this
like thin skeletons
I don't know why
but that's what the model industry is
psyche's body is model
city
Don't you this guy could be in magazines 50 grand the picture
I'm never gonna not say that he's not in shape, but I think well for my taste. He's a little skinny
I think I would like to put a total of 60 pounds
Well distributed on his body
Perfect, I mean, I wouldn't this should be the 60 pounds like six goes to the legs
You can't do that
It all goes to his ass, by the way, if you notice, have you seen him bend over in the
speedo, the American, it's all in his ass, he's got wrinkles, his ass starts to fall.
Go ahead, go ahead.
She doesn't see me in the speedo, I don't think, I think I've met her up.
I have seen you in the speedo, all the McDonald's is going to his ass, Alexander.
I'm trying to get him to be introduced to better food, but it's not like I'm like
Able to like like I'm not like what am I gonna do like force feet? No
And you guys stop eating too messy. You know too chubby. You're pulling a sober on me
I am getting to the ponds of yeah, stop it. I get on the treadmill. You know
20 pounds, you know, you know, if you're gonna be Amanda Erickson back on the treadmill, baby
I agree. It's not over yet. Well please fat shame me. The more you can fast shame me. I'm just
telling you you're letting yourself go with me. I have already lost the weight. I know that one
angle that I did the stream it was it was it was horrific. I saw the roles. I know it was
I think I am working on it. Yeah, but you don't know the angles men have to endure.
For example, if we fuck and I was on the couch and you were riding me, right?
And you got up to go to the bathroom from that view. I'm going to see all the
all the cottage cheese from how I'm going to see it.
this summer I will be better okay give me a chance I think you look great in
that the media loves the BBC video no but I need to look better and I need to
be bikini ready for the summer guys we're already not eating just leave me
alone okay I am getting there
But I understand what McQueen is saying and I do agree. I was too fat and it's fine
I'd rather hear but you're not past the limit of no return if you jog for a month your supermodel
But baby, you know
That's why I'm working on it and I would rather you tell me the truth
Yes, you're hot, but I see little puns and love handles coming out because you don't see it talking about all these losers
Get back out there. Okay. I am. I am. You've been out for a month. I haven't been out, but I am working on it and I will be the Devil Wears Prada by the end of this year, preferably before. Okay. I'll be fine.
Okay, good. Good. I'm gonna check in in a month pop quiz
Because your opinion does matter to me because I like your opinion. I don't like everybody's opinion
But I do want the opinion of the person who knows fashion because I don't want to be I would rather be dead
Then be a fat ass
Exactly die bad boy and bad girl like ill. Why is the enemy? No, I just the enemy
It should not be anywhere around
And I'm not as thin as I should be and you know because I am a little yes
then you would think I have a loose skin that makes me look fatter, but don't worry because I'm
getting my plastic surgery too when I you're too hard to let it go now you understand come back to
hotness I'm getting a look like you know what I am 40 when I am 40 late 48 maybe early 49 I'm getting
all my plastic surgery I already have the doctor picked out everything
No, you don't need plastic surgery.
Yes, I don't want that 20 grain of the surgery on lettuce and tomatoes.
Okay, not enough for me to be natural enough for the Parmesan cheese and
Parm pizza and lettuce and tomatoes.
And most psyche has met me in person.
He knows exactly what I look like.
But I can be
Imagine I'll squish you your everything just to squish you one, too. No, I don't like don't get
Because I've got the money, okay
and I'm going to just live that life and I'm going to have to allow myself to get accolades but I'm not just going to have, I'm not going to be by myself, I've got to have hot people around me, oh my god, if you want some plastic surgery what you want to facelift let's go, I've got a nose job, a facelift 10 grain for like one cheek, I've got a nose job, see that was my nose job, so you'll get more, so we're going to be good, look at that B, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good,
I am going to visit and also I can go for free. I thought for free. Baby. I would be offended. I would be like, why visit. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended. I would be offended.
that's so fun
that's right
no you're right
why can't he jump on a plane and visit
what the fuck he doesn't have a day off
maybe he doesn't have to jump on a plane
how do you know I'm not going to have my property in Mexico
you don't know what the fuck I'm doing
I can go to Mexico
Tijuana
I'm everywhere.
People can't find me.
People have been saying, oh, Alex is going to be sued.
How many years has it been that I'm going to be sued 10 years, 20 years, and yet somehow
nobody can find me really, really, I mean, you're hiding out in Mexico makes sense to
you.
You're hiding her in Tijuana, that's so funny.
Yeah, that's where I am.
I'm in Tijuana.
Welcome.
I own Tijuana.
It's called Mayor's Wana.
Mayor's Wana. I love it. Mayor's Wana. I like this Mayor's Wana sometimes.
Yeah. Well, no, that's not the game. All I'm saying is that all that stuff, it's all a lie.
But am I going to live south of the border? Probably. Yeah, why not?
All I got to do is have hot friends around me.
And be happy have my little parties run my little business if you lose 20 pounds
I'll think about it. We can
I'll lose 30 pounds
I'll gain 30. You lose 30. How about that? I'll become the muscle man for you when you become the little Barbie doll.
I'm not going to be judgmental like you.
All right. I'll meet you in the middle. We'll just be two fat blobs.
I'll meet you in the middle.
I do. I look great. I don't give a shit.
You do look great.
I'm great no matter what I do because that is who I am
No one can ever take that from me. I love you, and I don't care that you you know had sex with
I've had sex for the minute
I've actually had more sex with girls than you had in your porno industry
I
Fucked over literally a hundred girls in my life, and that's like low-balling you
I believe you have like 10 guys in your porno life
so I'm the bigger pig in reality, I'm the real porno star
but isn't that funny how that works?
I always tell people, like anyone who thinks
that I'm like this porno star, I'm not.
I never have been, I was brought into a situation
to where i really honestly did not know the point of the story is that i'm the best that's that
it's only you well it worked out for me it just did so i'm not upset about it like hey why is
But yeah, it's a psyche I'm telling you like no one's ever gonna ever believe us on this
But if like psych like it has to do with the birthday thing we basically have the same
framework, but different external bodies. And psyche can get away with
some of your black keys. Why you got kids? He doesn't. I don't think I've got
that in different external body with me. He might think that I get away with more,
but it's only the fun stuff I get away with, not the stuff that really matters.
So does it take you know my question is are you like do you have to work to make you come for an hour or do you come quick some girls you just touch the clip and they're like I just came ten times some girls you gotta fuck them for ten hours like I'm almost coming
Well I was waiting for you to finish your quest because you're very long winded as I am here's my answer for you I only
fuck lies, who from visual contact turned me on.
The reason for that is because I am a very, um...
sensitive person and I just know if a guy turns me on or not I've always been
that kind of woman I was a very easy adult performer to cast because no like
you're like dick and you know his income and you're like yeah that's not the
question let me talk I'm not done answering your initial
The thing about me is that I am very particular and very aware of exactly
What works for me versus what does not the studio owners and the directors who paid attention
Got the best fucking scenes from me and that's why I get residuals most porn stars
Don't get residuals. I'm one of the few who do because of a few
Particular scenes now my other scenes crap
because I wasn't really that into the guy.
It was the director into the aesthetic look
of what I looked like with the other guy,
but not what I felt.
And that's what makes me a very good porn director,
especially for women,
because I do get hired on a contractual sense
because I know what other women are into.
So I'm done go ahead, and I'm sorry to have
Encroached upon your speech
Mr. McQueen
He muted himself
You may respond
Okay, well, he's that was great. That was great. So basically you come fast. I got you
To the man, right? Yeah, of course what she will be attracted to me
I get it so the guy's ugly. I'm gonna take an hour to come if he's hot
I'm gonna come right away. Well, I don't think she'd even mess with the guy that
Know
My real power is psyche, and I'm only telling it to you and it is an illusion
The guys who do not pay attention to a word I say,
but who think that they could potentially be what I'm attracted to,
that's who I have the most power over,
and I will not ever be upset about that until the day I die.
It's funny.
Well, that's that's that.
Those are the three amigos.
Yeah
We can take over the world. Are you ready Alexander?
I was born ready, baby. You know that dumb line
As long as you keep me in the background. I think that we're safe. We're okay
We're going to put Psyche out front.
We're going to bleach his hair a little bit more.
You got to be a little blonder, at least in Greeks.
I like it all the time.
No, because we got to look.
I'm going to tell you something funny.
Aaron Carter, his mom, has an infamous interview
about her children getting them into the pop industry.
She always said, the one out front is the blonde one.
It's the truth.
Beyonce's mother, a black woman, or at least a partially black woman, realized that.
Why do you think Beyonce over the years has kept her hair so light?
That's not natural.
Right.
Your mom has very light skin and blonde as well, I think.
She's from the Louisiana area.
My god, I almost just had an heart attack.
Yeah, oh, that's what we're gonna do. Okay, psyche. We're gonna make you platinum blonde. We're gonna put you out front
Alexander you're gonna be I guess the
Kevin from the backstreet boys
We'll put you in the back and then I'll be way in the back because I'm gonna be we got to have another
Howard Stern and I'll be Robin, but I'm controlling your Robin. That's the funny shit
You're very handsome and I will make it publicly known that if you still have swimmers
in the next two years I am going to extract your sperm medically for my own uses because
I'm going to clone myself but you're going to know no no you got to sign the contract
you can't just say it I said to be the tonight on bronzes I said beat up if these losers don't
But I would be happy to have Psyche to be the male contributor to my female child
And I would have a gorgeous daughter. Imagine my daughter, please
Well, how do I come in? I might be the godfather. I'm glad you're having fun with Psyche daughter
Well, what do I still mean baby?
Where am I in the picture?
You're the godfather.
Yeah, you can be the godfather.
There you go.
I'm a godfather.
Wow.
And I've seen people look like, allegedly, and if you do look like that, then maybe
you're attracted to my daughter.
Maybe you want to have a child, and that's a good start for another lineage.
I'm not against that.
You're you're not blood related to me. Maybe you're maybe you're suave. Maybe you're a Casanova McQueen
So you want to fuck is that what you're saying? You want to have sex with me? Not me. It's my daughter
Yeah, oh
What do you mean? I'm not fucking your daughter. What are you talking about? Yeah, the only one we're getting fucked is you a psyche
Psyche's daughter, but you better be respectable because I will be watching from the other side
Hello, and I'll get you I'll kill you. Oh my god
and when or will help me and you're crazy if anyone's having a daughter is you and me
He's going to be the girl I'm having a daughter with psyche and me
It's your and then like you try to do something evil psyche only jab this cock and pussy once
He doesn't even know how to come in a door with nothing
I can fuck you and give you you know, I can come galore like a fountain a special case
Yeah, there's always exceptions. There's always exceptions, right? Yeah. Wow
Well, that'd be interesting because
You know, I do I do think my I do think our lineage deserves to go on and I think it would be an amazing
Well, I need the gay lineage
Your family
Let's think about this. My father actually
Was not just gay. He was super gay. He ran for Houston City Council under the body
So we're here folks. I was he like a
that he would fuck any gay man.
Yeah, so
Oh my god
In in in a minute way
Yeah, I get it. Some games are gay, man. Like old games. Like they don't pay us. No, this is a couch.
I'll suck it. I'll fuck it.
Maybe you're not... Are you not bisexual?
Well, I mean, it's like, I mean, I guess I could be the right person.
I mean, it's like...
He's 100% bisexual. He wants you, Beto, everybody.
Like, like, straight porn, kind of.
He chokes off to Christine, I think. This guy's creep.
Well, he didn't like...
elements of my porn but if I was just kidding I was well my porn is what
element what element did he not like hold on I'll analyze it
psyche, what element of performance did you not like? It was all gold.
I didn't want to be there. No, he picked up. I mean, it's the original. They sucked the
cock, they sucked the pussy to get on top of it, cowboy, then the, you know, doggie style
and then they get on top and it came over. It's up on the fact that I did not necessarily
want to completely be there and he got it. Good.
hey more points in my book
man you could have fooled me baby you're pretty happy
i don't want to be here that's bullshit
i'm getting both and i'm getting a 10 grand check
i'm not buying that bullshit
you don't want to be there
you are so misogynistic it's like ridiculous
I know isn't it, but oh my gosh, he is and it's like sometimes I'm like Alex
What it really comes down to with Psyche is that he's a solid gentleman of the most righteous of right
And you don't have that so much nowadays and that's why he is a very rare
Jim or I don't even like the word Jim. He's what word do I want to use from my mouth?
he's a well i don't even like that he's a rare i'm just jealous because i can't i don't get
the fuck and get sangria and tags honestly i'm here for a rare observation because i'll
fuck all day well that's the dream job you don't make a fucking pussy and get paid for it doesn't
say anything like that i like it to be observation
because that attributes it to a person.
And not everybody would take the time to look at psyche,
but I have, and I'm happy about it.
And I'm not going to be upset about it.
Thank you, you're very flattered.
And yeah, I mean, it's like,
yeah, I really, I think I've had sex
for like over three years.
I mean, it's like, really, I'm like,
It's crazy.
You're not having a lot of sex.
I'm saving myself for Q maybe.
I don't know.
No, I'm just, Q's always like,
I'm just gonna punch you in the face.
And I'm like, I like it, bro.
I guess, I don't know, I'm just kidding.
What I would say about Psyche is that
he's actually very normal when it comes to his,
sexual, conquest, proclivity, because I mean, for the most part, men in their
lifetime don't have that many opportunities. God doesn't make it that way for you.
Unless someone's having sex all the time, right?
The only time that you have, like, is the longer the better.
Okay.
,
Is that going to the gym your dick is a muscle you got to work it out pal, you know, but the hard everything
It's a muscle
Is the gym?
Yeah
For the cock. It's coming. You gotta go to the gym, bro. We haven't gotten to the gym in two years
It's a miracle you never caught like, you know, you gotta work that shit out
Right. Well, I don't know. I'm about to explode. Do you ever see the South Park where he like doesn't work out for a while?
Cuz the internet's down and then he like finds like an internet room and then he like starts working off and then like they open the door
He's just everything's just covered by two water two girls right now. It's just because I need some gym time
You know, I haven't been to the gym in two months. I
Remember bring the gym to me. This is the funny thing the world we live in I can bring the gym to me
Money talks and bullshit walks. Haha. I can have pussy delivered to me right now in 40 minutes
How insane is that easier than cocaine? Wild war
Yeah, bro, they're fucking harder than any girl you'll ever have so do not get to you try it my boy
Well, I mean, I, my brother's got fans or my, oh my, I'll miss it when I went to Mexico.
I can order three Alexandria mayors in a half hour here.
Literally.
Okay, I'm back.
I'm back.
And that's a fact.
Can you hear me?
Alex, tell, tell psyche how I can make, pick up the phone and have three of you clones,
black girls, Spanish, whatever I want, Russian, Czechoslovakian, Brazilian, I, there's a menu.
I will have three bitches on the knees talking my dad will blow
It came to me while I was just taking a piss in the in the toilet
But I I have something that I think will blow your fucking mind if you shut the fuck up for at least
10 minutes to let me tell you
Make it count, baby. Make it count. All right. I'll make it. Can you be quiet for 10 minutes?
Is it possible?
I don't believe it is.
Yeah, it sounds like beat and I just sound like beat.
It's a possible.
I don't want to tell him.
He annoys the fuck out of me.
Great.
So here we go.
All right.
Psyche, the LD situation.
I want to explain something to you about that.
OK.
When I met him because I saw that he was on your show recently and that you asked him about me, and I'm very
Very appreciative actually that you did
When I met him, I was surprised that he came down to Fremont Street within the literal 10 minutes that I would have still remained there, that I was there.
Okay, it was actually somebody who's a very prejudiced person, known as NorCal, who kind of made that happen. Yeah.
Because NorCal is obsessed with me, he loves black women, he hates black men.
And that's what I encounter a lot in my life.
That's why racialism and racism and colorism
is very interesting to me.
I didn't realize that I was sending the cement to psyche,
Well, you need to stop right now, you said 10 minutes.
Come on now.
But what's interesting to me about anything
having to do with superficialities
is that I strangely,
and I've talked to my sister about this,
my mother, my father, when he was alive,
about before I was born,
because they say that you don't remember
before you were born, I think I do.
And my sister asked me, she was like,
what did you look like?
And I was like, great question.
I think I looked like an energetic butterfly of some sort
when I, like before I had like a body.
And that's why having the body I have surprised me as much as I do, but I'm going to like
redo some things.
But anyway, when it came to this particular form, meeting LD, or LD15, or Bobby's brother,
like, who is he known as?
LD.
He is actually really nice.
I can't say anything bad about him.
He has a certain quality about him that is even seductive.
Was I personally seduced by him?
You're so lucky I'm more cooking to listen to this shit.
The reason I was seduced by him,
I think was because I was so familiar
with his sister's energy and I know that's what he wanted to ask me about or even confront me about
and I've never had like an enemy like
Anger like she thinks that I hate her or something. I don't I just would like for her to be honest
She's threatened my life several occasions unwarranted. There is no reason
She said that I've stalked her never did her mom asked me to draw her out of the adult entertainment industry
Which I did and like why won't her mom just say to her daughter?
leave Alex alone, she did what I asked her to do.
What pisses me off really about that situation
is that her mom doesn't do that.
That's it.
Outside, I don't have any anger with Bobby.
I feel like I did the skis line X, but she is a liar.
I don't have anything to say about her mom, her brother, whoever her dad is supposed to
be, whatever.
When it comes to...
Um, chicken cakes, yeah, game mask, Andy, I was mad at him forever.
He openly, publicly, and I have it clipped, apologize, saying that I have AIDS or HIV
or whatever.
He did that.
So, um.
Who's in the back?
Hold on.
Who the fuck is me hold on
Okay, you know, Katie. Okay. Hey, it's okay. Well, come on
I've never talked to you before I love you kisses
Sanchez saying something a story. Yes. I
Wasn't trying to interrupt her at all. I know
Security measures, it's okay
Well, I was gonna let Alexandra finish before I do anything
Yeah, but another funny voice you guys are so funny
That song's the best in the back by the way
Hey, I've done Katie actually since I started doing my show actually like you know over over almost
about a year and a half and so
It's Katie, okay, it's Katie cool with Alex though. Yeah, I think so
I've never had a problem with her
Yeah, all right, so welcome welcome
You know if you know about Jamie like Jamie is Katie's friend like my mom my mom Jamie's
Jamie's Cowboys
Are we doing okay, I'm glad how are you good?
Thanks for coming on the panel
so
Alexander are you there yeah I was just letting y'all talk Alex Alex do you know
Katie do you have a problem with Katie
I don't know Katie. Um, I've seen Katie's avatar before. I don't know Katie
But I was just like taking a backseat because I thought that
What the hell is Katie anyway? It's like you can introduce us cuz I don't know what either
I'm chilling. Wait, you coming from Kate's like beat us. What is Katie?
I'm trying to make a pretty different sector Alex if you want to be completely honest
Okay, wait, are you talking to me or Alex dinner McQueen?
McQueen right now
You got a number so Katie when you're up here Alex one acts to so we know because we don't know who you're talking to
Well, do you have a question?
Well, I will address you as McQuinn and Herzalic.
OK, perfect.
There you go.
Think that is gay, your fucking ass up here, bro.
That is.
And I want to hear about the president.
That's OK, very well.
I met K through Jamie's Cowboys and so yeah and so I've known them both for like maybe
since I started the show like before the start of the show um it's been what about two years?
Yeah about two years
Yeah queen. I do have a couple of questions for you and I didn't want to come off rude
We're getting a rock, but you said something about a woman and caught a sheep
So my question is what about if they lose that weight and they have stretch marks there
Then you get um, I don't know butter oil or something cocoa butter and put with that
You can't out of era, but that's okay. Just looks are hot
You know, okay, it's almost like a war scars war wounds
Well, I just didn't want to come on like it is all it is
Scars are hot man stress marks are hot depends on
It does depends how fat you are
And all I feel like a normal girl with some stress marks that your tits got big during pregnancy
And got back to normal and you got a stress mark. That's hot
You know
When they have love handles and lose that
Mm-hmm
The stress marks and like that area if you take like somebody that was a big bone person
And they've lost a lot of weight to work on themselves
Alexandra you you want to take this one you should know
Constant personal improvement like
Like right now, I'm actually excited about getting on the other side of my personal feminine time of the time of the month.
Like y'all know what that is, right?
But whenever like you as a woman, especially if you're exercising and working out,
once you reach your other time of the month, you do see nominal.
physical improvements. So like I've been doing like a lot of core work and what
not over the past month or so. So I have my time of the month and that's when
you're almost like a star in the sky. Like you go through your supernova point.
And then like, as your time of the month comes to a conclusion, you become a white dwarf.
Basically, well, I know it sounds silly, but that's how I see it.
And it's like, you can see the after effects and you're like, whoa, I really improved.
So that's what I care about because I'm a little self-centered because, well, I'm child-free
by choice.
So I can be, but it's just what it is.
And I, you know what, I do believe that I am going to be like the next Oprah Winfrey
Phil
Who's that guy on a you?
But
Dr. Phil
Because you have helped me and I think I have the power, like innately, like I feel like the energy of Whoopi Goldberg in a weird way, like I feel like, I feel like all the adversity that I went through with my sexiness having to do.
with the porn because that was really just me in my own awkward psycho kind of way being sexy
and hey if you bought it fuck you i don't care not really um but if it worked i think it worked okay
and i think that we can pull this shit off so we're doing it
we're doing it and I'm happy about it and I'm going to get my and I'm going to create my external
contributor child because look I'll tell you something crazy and I don't care if anyone believes
me or not officially I do have two genetic contributors unofficially I have seven oh wow
And I talked about it once on the live stream that I think was for the most part deleted,
but maybe I didn't want all of it to be, but that is the truth.
I was a part, or my parents, I won't say me, but it was me because I exist, but I was a
part of an experimental thing.
where I have more contributors genetically than,
but not legally, there's a difference.
Right.
So what I will say is that all the people who were
not legally a part of me are all still in my life,
be they alive or dead, they all care about me,
they all grew up with me.
or were with me as I grew up.
Well, they make you a part of who you are today.
They're all people who are a part of me.
And that is why I will never,
and I will confidently,
I didn't used to confidently be able to say this
because I guess I didn't want to acknowledge certain things,
but I will confidently say today.
that nothing bad will ever happen to me.
That I will never be left dead or anything.
Come on, let me see your stretch marks, Ronys.
I love your stretch marks.
He does.
Look at that swing yo shake that
Mr. McQueen would you ever let me like
Well, I like put you up in my place for like 30 days. Just so you know my god
She wants to birth my babies, basically
I am Colombian and I eat beans anything I touch gets pregnant. So just say it as come
Too late
We've been working something out. Trust me. I don't want to die alone either, baby. We can work something out
Already worked out
psyche
You're in the back. I never heard you laugh that hard ever. That was great. You're you're I think you're funny as hell
Really? Yeah, and I owe you one by the way you saved me pulling a stretch mark talk with Katie. I was like what the fuck
If my plan works out then I'm in good shape if it doesn't work out, it's okay. I'll still be in good shape
But you know a girl's gotta do what a girl's gotta do
Oh, Katie at the end of the day.
Trust marks are hot.
Guys love it.
It's more.
It's like guys love natural shit.
It's like, I don't know.
The beast in us, the animal, like the human, like
trash makes it harder.
Like, wow, it's like real.
It's real.
It's weird.
Michael J.
Fox was like horse crush.
yeah because it means like the real there's a real person they were fat there was gainy
they have a stretch mark it's like reality it was just a boy next well you know my my my first crash
was a boy down the street from me david cambell i do
And he was a really nice, well, he was a little bit older than me, and he, he kept up with me for a long, I've had these guys over the years, keep up with me, but you know what, they've always been the hottest, cutest ones, so I'm not unhappy about that.
It's great. Like at least at least what do you mean kept up with you though like sexually or like just kept up with you with your
Lifestyle, what do you mean kept up with you?
stalking stalking stalking stalking. Yeah, oh kept up with you stalking. Okay
Yeah, because you're so hot they'll fall in love with you and then you're like fuck off and they're like no I can't let go
That's what it is
Oh
Like I don't know if you read my comment, but I said thank you for showing me really earlier. Oh, yeah
There's really right there. There's really there. He's watching. Oh, look at that cat. Look at that. Look at him. Oh
Yeah, he's meowing
Hi, taxi, that's we're talking about where we're talking about man
Because getting kind of
Yeah, oh my gosh
Sends your energy level going up. They sense the energy
Yeah
The normal time they're in heat now. They're like, yeah, I want to take we're all horny at the moment
Actually, this is all the shit. We're talking my stress marks babies
these four curtains are like
cock
we need to fix your apartment
will you let us, we'll see
I can imagine
Alexandra there on a ladder painting
that would be so funny
because psyche met me in person so it's different
but if Alexander McQueen and I
were to
revamp your apartment will you let us sure yeah we might have to put you up
in a hotel for at least two days to get your phone that could be a hardwood
floor in carpet I know that carpet this carpet is done I think the carpet has
to go only in the bedroom new paint new time
to do it
It is a beautiful apartment. It's just like, you know, it's just I've just lived in it for so long
But we could if you gave us a blueprint of your apartment
We could make your apartment shake your law for real
Well, there's a there's an a there's a VR program that like will map out your whole apartment
if you give me look if because
Like, I will not donate forever, but I'll donate for that.
That'd be awesome. That'd be awesome.
Like, if you give me a blueprint, like a real blueprint of your apartment.
and then don't know what you buy I thought I was the most in the future but I'll deny you for that
Thank you. Well, yeah, I mean that would be that
Plenty because I'm gonna be here forever and then you do the maintenance Alex. No, I want to see Alexander
They're carrying tools and a little overalls
No, I'm not doing
Like Alexander McQueen I will admit something to you
I am not of hard labor at all.
Really? Wow.
No, that's not...
You're a little princess. You're a princess, I know.
Well, I have a hard labor.
Well, I don't think I'm a princess. I just...
No, you are, though. I know. There's some girls that are princesses.
There's some girls, you know, can hammer. You can't hammer nothing.
The point is, you turn me on to have women in workout pits like that,
Well, I will do hard work if I have to but Katie what you say to me
That I should not do certain things. So I don't but alright
Can you at least be there in overalls and nothing else? Well, I will be on
If I pay for it, that's pretty good in my opinion if it's coming from my own hard earnings
That's this is good. Yeah, that's this is good. This is money bags. That's it. What are the labor?
You know
In my own way
You ever seen that it didn't make it housekeepers that like they don't really like clean that well, but they come
Topless housekeepers. Yeah, they don't really they just come in dusting stuff and everything
I like the Mexican laborers, you know
Yeah
You know, yeah, they're, um, well, I do, like, I always, I have a hot cable guy, I always have like a hot, like, uh, you know,
I was always hot on installers, I was hit on them.
nothing ever happens. Does she give you three cable? No it's not like the cable
guy but you know it's like a cable guy. When I think of cable guy I think of Larry the cable guy
sorry psych. Larry the cable guy oh he might be a redneck if you know that one
that's true. Now you're talking about the cable guy with Matthew Broderick.
You carry on.
He's talking about illegal cable
Faces Jamie's cowboy making
I don't know
Come on Jamie
Or noble do you want to come up? No, that's his noble Castro right noble noble splatter. He's uh, he's Hispanic
I don't think I don't I think I think I might have hit him up once and scared him away, but um
69th Sage, I don't know who you're talking to, but yes, if you're talking to me, I support
self-improvement for even people I don't care for.
Is 69th Sage the real Sage, or hold on, 69th Sage, yeah, is that the Sage that like hates
me now, or like, is it, there's a Sage that's like...
I have no idea.
Yeah.
I have like a lot of the Sage's banned, you know, I almost banned the word Sage, but I
can't do it.
I'm a terror reader.
Actually, I have a charcoal right here.
I can burn some incense tonight.
Have you seen these?
These are called charcoal master
and you just light these little things.
They're like self-lighting.
And then I have some like resin,
some frankincense incense.
Oh, look at how bright it is.
Oh yeah, there it is.
See?
Oh shit.
Let me put it down there.
And then you get some frankincense.
This is a real frankincense, premium frankincense.
Put it on there, it'll smoke up.
The brumel smell is fucking really good too.
I love it. The music is good. I have never tried frankincense tea. That's really good for you.
He says tea? No, I haven't. I was burning the frankincense. I'm here. Frankincense is like
it's one of the things that the wise men brought Jesus. Like frankincense, myrrh and gold and
stuff like that. You mean like frankenstein? Frankincense? Frankincense. Yeah, it's like uh.
It breaks the blood frame barrier and it's known to help with
cancer patients and things like that this is prefer for protection purification spiritual awareness a
meditation and to ease sadness and
Just an herbal plant is it like safe with that?
It's a resin
it's like a little like what do you get it melts i got i got it i got an etsy i got a bunch of these
resins and then it's like you can see it that's burning in there i just put in a pipeline in
utah charcoal it's like a charcoal that's self burning charcoal and then it melts so cool so you
guys teach me shit and i never heard of this in my life yeah well frankincense and myrrh is what
they brought like the wise men brought jesus like frankincense and myrrh and so it's like it's like a
um like uh incense it's very big well you said purification it doesn't just purify the outside
it also does inside but you have to get uh food grade for that to happen and that's why i got
three young living there you go oh there now it's burning up there you know well i'll tell you
There is a perfume called Star by, um, oh, I can't remember who does it, M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M-M
It's smells like frankincense like frankincense the smell is
What Mughlifer?
Parfait, I think that's what they call themselves. I don't know
but
You if you want to smell like something divine
That's what you want to smell like.
The other thing I know about mixing fragrances and more together,
it really helps for like, I would spray this paint.
Oh, well that makes sense.
It's a star ingredient and luxury perfumes. It says yes. Yes. Yes
It smells so good. Oh my god. I mean
There's this guy that I was in a relationship with for a while
We weren't married or engaged or anything. Thank God because it would have caused a lot of problems for me
But his name was Francesco Barberino.
He was such an elegant man.
He was Sicilian.
He was just like beautiful.
He was so, and he thought that I was like,
literally the personification of Aphrodite.
Like that was his whole thing with me.
I felt like it objectified me to an extent,
but like looking back now,
oh, such an extreme compliment, seriously.
And that's why I like that one young man's song,
Aphrodite was that guy's name, Reform Stoic.
I think to myself, like, is there a linkage between the two?
I don't really know.
But anyway, I want to find that perfume
to tell you what the name of it is, because it smells so great.
Um, there's something called Star. Let me see. Oh, I mean, um, Angel Nova. Let me see.
Yes. Yes. Angel. It has some something to do with Angel.
Mugler, Angel, alien pulp, alien pulp.
Yes, yes, that's what it is.
Uh-huh, a Mugler, M-U-G-L-E-R, Mugler.
Yeah, whoever it is that makes that, it's so great.
It's just like the best.
Scent look at if you look at I'll show you look at look at this. This is like their their page on Amazon
This is the thing. It's an interesting model. I'll show you look at this. It's quick. Okay moogler
Let me see where is this right here. Yeah, look at this. This is on the Amazon site, and it looks pretty interesting
See oh
Really? Yeah
You hear me? What's wrong?
Moogler
Look at the bottles, the bottles are really cool.
Well, I mean, the scent of it.
If I could have that scent around me all the time, I would.
Maybe I should.
You know what, I'm gonna order it right now.
I think I need to have that scent around me all the time.
Here's the angel bottles that are in those star bottles.
Yes, those are stars.
Oh my gosh, look at them.
I know, is it Luciferian?
I mean, what's going on?
They have the alien, they have the angel,
they have the amen, here's the, oh look at the amen.
They have one for men called Alman and it has a star too.
But is it Alman or is it Alman for women?
I mean, what's happening here?
What's going on?
You told me it was Alman.
Is it perfume?
They have the best sellers.
Let's see the best sellers they have.
Yeah, let's see this.
I'm going to order it right now.
I have to order all of it.
That looks good.
Oh, look at it.
Yeah.
Pretty cool.
You know, a stent is the strongest sense in humanity out of sight, hearing, smell, tricks
the brain, you understand?
yeah it brings you back to like childhood like sense look it up it's the strongest sense
the lotion yeah they might have it says bath and body so they do have lotions okay this is like oh
yeah so this is the lotion that's when you can get blindfolded and eat a banana and smell an apple
and you think you're eating an apple it's so good that runs the show that's really cool
It's amazing.
Also, they have refills, men, okay.
So, tell you how it's a beautiful smell.
Oh, beautiful gift sets, too.
Yeah.
lotions body lotions body wash I used to I used to get like my mom would give me
these like Calvin Klein with it I come with a lotion and it come with like the
Calvin Klein CK1 I used to love CK1. Oh, it's a gift? Yeah. Amber but woody sort of scent it's a
wonderful scent
There's a devil eyes is in the chat. Yeah. Oh my there. Oh my hey, what's important? There's Brandon. What's up, Brandon?
There's noble. What's up guys 69 stage. Wow. We have a nice chat
Yeezys here. Wow me queen. Yeah
Who is Jamie fighting with Jamie's flirting with somebody. No fighting. Jamie's fighting
You can't tell someone to shut up.
He's devilized.
He's saying Jamie and she's like, shut up.
Oh my god.
Yeah, I don't know why.
The thing that is here still, the thing that is,
I haven't seen him for a little bit.
Where is it?
Yeah, there is.
Wow, kind of a really cool chat should Joe is here. Oh my gosh
Hey Rudy
Rudy's like he's like set he's like 18 years old, but he's like so soft. He's very soft. He is really cute
He wants to come up that doesn't want me to like, you know be here
You should leave in but then win if you want to stay stay well, but
You fuck them. You're not going nowhere. You're better than all of them
I rather be up here with you than any of those
You're not leaving
Is afraid to come up because I'm up here. He's work now. He's working today
He's I know he doesn't work
He, well, he does like, I think he does like coding. He does. He's like, well, he did something, but he, he's at home. Yeah. Yeah.
He works at home. Yes. Yeah. He's at home. Yeah. He's, well, he's, okay.
We didn't know about you saying that is, we're, we're, we're just magic. We're doing is a warlock stuff.
Canadian warlock. Well, just so you know thing that is, as sexy girls, we are tracking you.
And you might think that you can evade us for your woman who never will be because she doesn't actually exist, be this kiddies.
There's some of us out there who are real women who are tracking you, watching you.
Oh come on, I haven't talked in forever, get up here.
Yeah.
I mean, Katie over here, she's...
letting you know I think that is that there's an opportunity there
But it's all about what you want thing that is but we're just keeping track
Because eventually thing that is there will be another thing that is
Who's braver and more courageous than you are who will be ready for these wondrous
amazing seductive
sensual women of men of the man who are like Katie and who aren't gonna want to
deal with you anymore original thing that is so when that happens just
remember that you will not be privy to the scraps of the thing that is 2.0
3.0 4.0 whatever it happens and you know he was to come up
but you know you gotta live in the moment and just do it go for it because god forbid you die tomorrow
or you're laying in your hospital bed you're gonna regret it like it should have went up
Right now I'm dying. I should have went up and talked to Alex and Katie and Alex and psyche and now right don't be scared
Just do it literally
You never know when it's gonna be over
Just now look that was his training around he would have come in his pants if he had come up
At this moment. Okay. He already had to I always think about that when I'm like scared of some shit like that like no
I'm like bro, just do it
I'm sorry, Alexander McQueen, the voice
then there's me adding a little bit of a base undertone
and then there's the overtly sakes sexiness
that is this young woman below me
who I don't really know about yet
but she's there
so, you know, it was too much for him
Yeah
And the cherry on top is the music in the background.
He's not used to the music in the back.
This is new.
Yeah, it was too much.
It was too much for him.
He had to run away and hide.
But that's OK.
Orchestra?
It's like an orchestra.
We're like a quartet.
Yeah.
Me, me, me, me, me.
We're like a barbershop quartet.
It was too much.
I mean, I'm over here looking at Amazon.com, shopping, buying more God t-shirts because
I like to remind people about God's goodness when I'm out and about. And it's a little discerning
to people. Let me tell you something that happened recently. I went to get my oil changed.
at the um local you know um mechanics place whatever you call it right and the guy was a
little bit an asshole to the young woman in front of me and she was substantially younger than me.
But he didn't know how old I was, but I was wearing the God t-shirt, right?
Plus the necklace plus I have crucifix rings and stuff
Yeah, I mean, you know psyche thinks that he's down with his school. Who's the fix rings?
Because I'm the same way
Yes
Yes, yes.
Well, that's because you were like a Bible going, right?
You said your parents like ring the church keep certain people back.
So I was wearing my rings and whatnot, and I have my outfit on or my shirt my t-shirt that said God is good
So he looks at me and you can tell if he was a little bit of an asshole
This particular guy, but I mean what are you gonna do was the end of his work day?
I just came in there to pick up my car or whatever and he was just like
Okay. And I was like, oh, this young lady is trying to educate you about the Lord. Look at that.
God is good on the t-shirt with the big boobs in there.
I'm uncomfortable considering what I could tell about him.
It was free reign and he knew it and there was no escape so it's just you know sometimes
life is like that.
You gotta wait until you get older in order to see it.
Yeah.
That's all.
I like getting older because it's like and I still, I mean, I feel like, I mean, I can't perform age.
Nobody likes getting older, don't lie to us, actually.
We can't perform age in reverse, so we're like better and better as we age.
I like getting older.
I like it because it's like, I mean...
You do?
I like it, yeah.
You do too?
I like it.
I don't like that I'm getting old feeling.
Okay, why are you like like getting older it means closer? I don't know what I don't know what to do with that
I like getting older my like is that we see we okay
Here's where both of us have a certain advantage and I know it
For whatever reason, we've both been able to hold on to our youth to an extent, but we're
able to maintain the wealth of knowledge that we remember as the key word, remember from
this current life experience, and we're both being assholes.
Now the birthday is a certain way to triangulate certain things.
come to a place where we can both be like ha ha super twins let's go but you know at some
get sick of it no i don't like getting older i know you mean i like it because
life is awesome right who doesn't like like progressing but none of us like getting closer to
You know, I know it's coming baby, but I don't like it and tell me you do
It's my point
We're holding on to our youth about their well speaking of which how old do you really think I am looking at my picture?
Oh, do you think Alex you're uh, are you a picture? Let me think
In that picture you're in your dirties no
There okay the picture says like late 30s, maybe early 40s the way you sound. I don't know a little
Older you asked me about the picture not the voice
No, I'm asking you how old do you think I am in that picture because that picture is just a couple months old
Okay, what?
Yes, I mean this shit again. No way. Oh no
Couple months old
the
I just like you know
well yeah I mean it's like it means sometimes some some of it's not great my grandmother hated
I mean you're like she's really like Johnny she's just terrible it's just terrible and you know
but she lived to 93 years old um if she was still alive today I think she would be 105 years old
so um it's pretty crazy you know how old do you think you're more than brownies
To what he looked at 30 years old originally like you know, I thought I would look to 30 and so I'm already living
I'm now in 44. Yeah, and you're some way and you're thin
You don't have fat so you know that your heart doesn't have to work overtime to carry fat around
You're gonna lift to like 110 you one of those skinny people. Have you ever seen an old fat person? No
Roni's and Scott and he's gonna be 120 years old
Both my grandfather's died in the 90s man, and my grandma's
90s Lee 90s
Well, it's like my my aunt was like, you know, she just passed away recently, but she never got over like she was always like
Oh mom and dad are gone and my my sister my mom would be like well, Terry
They'd be well into their hundreds right now. Like she's you know, everyone has to get everyone has to go sometime and I guess
Yeah
If you if you tell your
relatives who are related to the ones that just passed on that so-and-so passed
on at a similar time they will die at that same time if you tell them that
right don't tell them yeah okay I like what about genetics no I agree so if I
Um, don't tell them that
someone has done play a part
into it. But, um, I think the
mind plays the most part and
the body, the way you, the way
you treat your body through
life is the whole game plus
your mind. That's it. Eventually
your body is going to give out.
Doesn't matter who the fuck
you are. Okay. That's the point
Yeah, but the way you eye your body during life will make it extend longer before it gives out
That's why they promote healthy living
exercise healthy foods
Okay, a hundred is that smoke is that smoke cigarettes and you're right?
I saw a hundred three old lady, you know what she told me I eat four things every day
I don't go fuck eggs potatoes steak and
I forgot the fourth thing, bro.
Eggs, potatoes, bacon, right?
Some shit.
Four things every day, 103 years old.
Still has a marble.
Well, I'm in the process right now of going one week with no cigarettes.
I tend to do this from time to time.
Oh, please.
You smoke?
Oh, you've got to.
Yeah.
I didn't know you smoke.
That's how I make it to where I can quit.
I want to.
But I'll give myself.
Well, you know, some time I recently, you know, when my dad passed, I didn't smoke cigarettes for a while.
I've had an uncle pass recently and I'm doing the same thing.
It's just kind of like a moratorium or like a...
What's in the back?
What's going on?
Martinez is back. Martinez is back.
I always am obligated.
Where is Psyche? Where is Psyche?
Here he is. Where are you?
Here he is.
I always return to smoking but I mean like at this moment I don't even have any cigarettes
in my in my immediate possession at this moment. Do you smoke weed?
Yeah, I would rather do the edibles opposed to I
Seen your show already. Your show is amazing
I want a signature now
She's amazing. She's a superstar, bro.
Alexander Meadows is literally a huge...
You should do a meet and greet, Alexandra.
Alexandra.
Well, I would do it with Psyche.
Like, he can be the main attraction.
Again, so you can just fit him out onto the dirt like last time.
And you can like sign the fucking anal beach.
The next time you go out with Psyche,
I'm gonna be there to quarterback this shit.
You should.
You're not gonna...
I want you to be there
So you can sign you know movie tapes, you know DVDs
Blu-ray like
Like the music video
Yeah, bro. I want a fucking bub plug where you're fucking signature on it. No, I don't want I don't want to make a
Oh my god, go with this here. Hold on
Who is this guy?
Is that Dumb Dumb?
Yeah, you know what I heard about Dumb Dumb?
I heard that he got turned off on only fans.
He asked somebody for their only fans, and they said no.
Who the fuck liked Ghost in here though?
The only fan.
Yo, that's so fucked up, bro.
Ghost, I don't believe this shit, bro.
Yo, you be nice to Mayer's Ghost.
I didn't like the way he got to her last time.
No, no one's gonna mean to me. I just don't want it.
I just want anyone to know any product that I ever put in.
Well, just joking off to white man you tonight, all night, Alex.
You let me know.
You're ghost.
I'm a white night ghost.
This lady here has all only fans, I think.
Well, in some way, and are twisted and nice.
It won't be, like, gross or anything.
But that's, that's all I have to say.
Oh my gosh.
Well, okay, well, go say hello.
I'm gonna smile along.
How are you guys?
Bro, I'm trying to promote the lady.
I'm sorry.
You watched the white slavery movie?
Yeah, I saw it.
How was it?
Fucking amazing, bro.
I love it.
You guys got pegged in that?
Come on, bro.
Is that what you really want to know?
You know the fucking movie.
Jesus Christ.
What the heck bro, you see you want to fucking silence me and and always put me on mute
But that you want to talk about but that now now that you want to talk about
You see how you are psyche
That's not fair, buddy
Here's what's gonna be fucked up. That's not fucking fair, bro because of these stupid streams
You know what I'm saying you want to hate on me and then now you want a tongue swap. You know, I'm saying that's not good
I'm gonna be like why is this movie so popular?
I'm trying to promote her and shit like that
Silence me
And then you want to fucking saliva swap
No, nobody do anything
Adult nobody
Now you want to have a deep conversation about what's going on and fucking in the video, right?
I'll go I don't mind. I don't mind talking about it
It's amazing, we don't need to talk about it. It's amazing. No, I'm not gonna talk about it
You're gonna have to fucking pay for it. You better subscribe to fucking go out there and look for it
Good stuff. Let's let's talk about
Let's let's talk about our favorite flavors of oatmeal. I like strawberry
Anyways, I came back to say shout out to you because I saw it amazing much love. All right. Well, I'm
Blueberry is good, you know what else is good banana and orange
Like like like with like with mandarin
Orange, are you guys singing? No, what happened?
oatmeal with fruit
Okay, the cream of wheat is really good whatever Martinez everything would go Martinez
On that well, I mean it's like if it has like a lot of milk in it and I
Hey, Brandon quick like Brandon says multi meal. Oh, I don't I don't know about multi meal. What's that?
Is that like a I think it's a is it like a medicine? I think that's the brand out now
Oh, well, I don't like Quaker.
Oh, yeah.
I like that man who's on the thing.
You know, I trust him.
He's got his wig on.
He's like, hey, it's, it's Quaker time.
And I'm like, I don't even know what a Quaker does, but.
Yeah.
Do you know the judges in England wear those wigs?
No, I'm sure, right?
Everyone needs to wear the wigs sometimes.
Yeah.
I have ancestors that um well they were she was burned like I think she was like you know hung for being a witch but they were actually
I'm looking at you tonight psyche
Is your ancestor?
For real
The witches of Salem
Abraham Lincoln
I think
I think that are you related to?
There's me.
Bates?
Is Bates?
I'm going to look it up on the internet.
Yeah.
Well, I'm really the captain, Bates.
I stole his pillow full of blood.
I bet the Bates are really so lucky.
I might be.
Actually, I think on Ancestry it says I'm really the 11th president, I think, of the
United States.
I bet you are.
Abraham Lincoln is my brother by the way. I saw I saw the Betty died on I sat in the chair
Where he got shot in a sixth grade school trip to Washington DC to Booth Theater. I
Was in your six like 30 years ago. That was my graduation trip
Washington DC and they took us to the theater and they sat in the chair when he got shot by William
Booth or whoever whatever theater and then they took us down the block and showed us where he bled out and
The pillow was in a glass case
Yeah
To your answer mr. McQueen
According to the AI
Okay, the Bates are not a blood of relative of Abraham Lincoln, but they are a close political
ally.
Okay.
Wait, tell me the Bates, no, but the Bates are aristocrats, according to the Bates,
they owned, no, no, they're aristocrats.
Not forever.
I got it.
There he is.
I'll talk on my own platform. That way I get my own information out because he's not gonna let me talk
No, you can talk I don't know don't mute them
I'm ready you talk talk
No, you talk first because eventually you'll get tired
I'm already tired just talk. No. No, I will let you talk first
Debate to aristocrats. That's all I said your turn. No you stop energy left
I'm not a blogger. What are you going with this? You are finish your story. No, I'm gonna wait until you're done
I'm done
there you go well I'm actually um all right well when it comes to um no because the base are
strangely a big deal I didn't even know about this um a prominent Missorian base was part of
Yeah, so you y'all were up to stuff. The Bates the Bates. Okay, like I have looked a little tiny bit. So I do know how treacherous the Bates can be. But it doesn't bother me. Like it's not affecting me. But I do know about how the Bates have been a part of a lot of political parties throughout the early
I, what, what, what, what, what, what would you call it? The, uh, civil, the, the early
colonialism or
there's, there's a look about John Wilkes Booth by his lawyer.
I know.
I almost want to make AI about it when I think about it, but do I have someone?
I've had, I think, you know.
I grew my beard when my beard was really like that Lincoln beard.
You look like a colonialist, man.
You do, you look like Abraham Lincoln.
Yeah, I am.
I think you are!
And, uh, I'm related to Kathy Bates.
She's my, like, sixth cousin.
I've actually traced it back.
But actually, I do have a family called the Zinnongs,
and they founded Harlem.
They were like they were like Nancy Kerrigan you know I was drinking the other night talking to you and I got like
Did I get it? Did I yell at you like in a mean way? I'm sorry. Not at all. Not at all.
Oh yeah, it's Opelmop on. I think I can't you scream at you calling calling you Nancy Kerrigan for some reason.
And I'm getting a little crazy right now. Well wait, who's that? This is Ilya Opelmop. I think he's in like Russia or something.
Oh, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here we go, here
The only thing that you said is by you is your love, in God.
Nope, I don't want to hear it, pal.
I don't want to hear it.
I'm saying you.
I like it.
I like what we say.
That is what you say.
Thank you.
And that's how it is for me.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
That's what you get from me.
What's with Jason?
Look at that lady.
Look at that hat.
I don't fucking know that I haven't played that.
what are they doing well everyone's wearing a nice outfit where the hell are the f16 dropping bombs i
don't get it it looks like a normal world isn't there a war going on gorgeous it's gorgeous no
because yeah it's all lies bro look at this shit they're too comfortable anything could happen anything
could happen wow don't bullshit the line to us okay
whatever they tell you it's the
opposite I mean I like this scene
but anything could happen because
they're too relaxed
yeah
yeah 2020
watch out for the Jones incoming
bullshit look at this
it might be me coming
oh my god
don't say that to me
I don't know
Look at these Russians enjoying their life like like it's it's Ukraine. It's Ukraine
I mean, I might go crazy one day. I might get mad
See I knew obloom off will come around
I'm thinking about trying out some peptides to keep it going.
Was that really about the brown sugar?
It's not the black women that you have to wear.
You know what's throwing me off the orange, though?
That's a lot of orange.
Is it orange or something?
What's up with all the orange?
Who's the enemy of white culture,
if you really want to think about it?
Like in a really, like, um...
methodical kind of way, uh-huh the real enemy of white culture would
essentially be
The classified black male who's brother psyche. You got a full screen. This is Russia. I
Think that's funny
Tell you
Because he stopped me and he's probably right to stop me
Yeah, oh my gosh
Well, I think it's in the Netherlands, but they're why they're wearing the bright bright bright orange everyone's wearing that
To be able to see them better. Yeah. Yeah
Like like an alert. No, I'm glad that you stopped me from saying that I what I was gonna say because
Should there be a real warning as you coming maybe?
Maybe not
But is there a reason for the warning that I wonder about that
Maybe there's no reason
I think everyone should be over the map. What's up with the orange shit though, man?
Sometimes there's people that you need to be alerted of right
No, there's too much orange going on. There's something up with that. It's like already
Looked out for yeah someone said it's the pros or the kings bar to be seen
they're happy like they're not like like oh no i have to wear orange they're happy to wear orange
no it's like same patty's day like imagine you know i went on a realm some patty's day everything's
green like that's not normal what's today obama of orange day like well no vodka day look at that one
he's happy he's happy to wear orange
Look at these Russian bastards
Other one is vodka, bro, they don't give a fuck about nothing
Are you like orange wearing orange because bright is really orange is actually my like the best color to wear
I've been told like like a lot like as far as like looking nice. I shouldn't wear orange, but I like red
I like pink
like
Like a
I like all the colors.
And you for your service.
You also.
Hey, hello to North Korea.
North Korea number one.
In your good number one.
Yeah.
America number seven.
It's a Dutch flag.
They're in the Netherlands.
Give a big doobie.
Are we going to take it over by Korea?
Are you Kim Jong-il or Eun?
Wow, this is crazy.
Really, thank you for taking us through Amsterdam. North Korea's number one. Oh my gosh, I think that is.
Where's Dennis Rodman? Is Dennis Rodman around?
What do you think? Do you think Dennis Rotman is attractive? Do you remember when he married himself?
I think Dennis Rotman and I would be really good friends. I've never met him.
And I think that, you know, I'm just working on making sure that I don't have my citizenship.
With my future child, that you will be the sperm, um, donator too.
So, I'm just, I'm just becoming familiar with the land as I watch your streams.
I'm gonna change my, the color of my banner to orange. Let me see how I look at that.
Yeah, orange.
Is it?
There we go. We're all set. We're orange blossom.
There, um.
Yeah.
There we go.
Beautiful.
Well, let's make it more of a red or orange.
Okay.
Red, a red orange here.
Yeah, like, yeah, that's better.
That's perfect.
Yeah, that way.
this one, this later one.
That's more like a blood orange.
Well, that's me.
I'm all about blood orange.
Oh, I love blood orange.
Well, that's my favorite.
Yeah, we have to make sure because I'm going to,
I'm going to have Psyche's future child.
It's probably going to be a girl.
And you know, things have to be okay.
And she will be like amazing.
So I think she'll rule the world.
Yeah, she'll be president of the Galactic Empire of this area of the United Planets of Ever since.
Federation, the Galactic Federation, Happy Kings Day, North Korea.
He must go to the Wonder Park, they said. Red Light District. Are we in the Red Light District? Let's go.
Look at the windows.
Yeah, let's go.
I actually went one time to the red light district
and I was like, when I was been over there
and I like, I just went in because I was with some guys
and I was just like, there were two shy to go in one.
So I went first and I didn't really do them very much
except for like, it was the main one, my treat.
and that's it well it counted so that's something so you're in there I went I did I
went in whatever counts you're in there okay so whatever
closest I ever got to there you go there's a lot of choblamon I haven't seen
obama since he had to skirt on and show his cock I know
That's the last time I saw him.
He's in the bucket and he's in the bucket on my show.
Yeah, that's the last time I saw him, bro.
And now he comes back.
So we're moving along.
We're moving along.
Here we go.
Everybody's free today.
It's holiday.
I'm on my couch in New York.
Look at these people walking around.
And this is live right now.
Like all these people are out there right now.
Like doing that.
the world is awesome
10am over there, it's like 10.30 in the morning, 10am I think, because it's about 8 hours ahead
yeah, it's a beautiful afternoon, we're here
hey, are you telling me the sun is not a light bulb?
like, we have a light bulb, right? it comes up in the morning, comes none at night, like, shut the light off
someone made that shit, god, it's not playing at all
and the moon is the nightlight
Great Balls of Fire, I heard of Great Balls of Fire, that's what it's called.
That's what it's called, right?
We have more holidays in Americans, wow.
Nick of Time and Europeans.
So even Amsterdam, that's not Russia, that's Amsterdam?
Yeah, we sell the Dutch flag.
It might be North Korea, I'm not sure.
Wow.
There's something over the orange though, I don't want to hear the orange shit, that's...
You're gonna look up King's Day.
Oh, look at Alex, just leave her up.
Look at Alex, pink scarf.
I will change my scarf soon, Mr. Yo.
I don't know what I'll change it to, but,
what would you like, Mr. McQueen?
Like, what would satisfy you?
for my Neal avatar look.
Color scarf at Alexander.
Or maybe no scarf.
Maybe I should.
No, I don't want to say it.
I was thinking of no color,
but no scarf would be nice.
A tank top, a nice little tank top, the hair.
Should I just be like no scarf, no turtleneck, maybe,
Yes, it's not like you're in the fucking Alaskan and Eskimo
Lighten up a little, you know take the jacket off
I'm not wearing a jacket. I'm wearing a I'm wearing a just like a
Sweater in that picture. It looks like you're fucking protecting yourself from vampires. They get away from me now
Uh, I mean, it's possible.
Interesting, I have actually, like, I remember like...
I mean, vampires do come at me routinely, believe it or not.
Did you really date that guy Tommy James or Eddie Datum?
What the fuck? Come on out, come on out.
No, it's not real. It's all a giant.
Like freaking
Save me, please
Dave, you, we've taken, you're gonna save it for me?
Yeah, I'm gonna, I'm gonna show you this real quick,
cause this is like, um, I always wanna show you this.
This is like, if you ever thought,
are we just like, maybe like,
soul twins in a maybe way?
Cause look at this, what I have right here.
Here we go.
Well, I don't see anything.
I'm gonna put it up right now, here we go, here we go.
There it goes.
Okay, and where's the TikTok?
Okay, um, right here?
Yeah.
It's a scarf, that's funny.
That was August 4th, 2025.
So I think that was like right around the time we met.
Mine was before your scarf.
I'm sorry.
No, no, you're wearing it, but I think we met when we met.
Yeah.
I'm so I was going to put me in a blue scar. Maybe I'll let them baby blue color. I would
like to change the pink. It's time to change the pink. I've been looking at shit for a
long time now. You picked your time in a pink top with the blue scar. I can't do it. You
can. I can imagine it. He can do it. I'm like he do it. So wait, wait, pink top with a blue
a light pink V-neck cleavage showing top yes cleavage showing that's the magic
word right there thank you I don't want to say cuz I don't know how sensitive you
know we're up here tonight but exactly let's get some cleavage going summer it's
springtime get that scarf off let's get some cleavage out there
I'm skinned the elbow, you know such as women's shoulders are I love when they wear like a shirt and then put the little shoulder hanging off like one
That's too hot. That's summer
You do it all the time
I see you you put the little and then they show the bro. That's even worse
You know what a psychological mind pop that is when the shirt is hanging off the shoulder and the
Boy showing like why do you girls do that to us? Why?
said I can't say cleavage but it says it can generate a new outfit okay okay so we've got a pink style
no I rather cleavage cleavage is nothing but that hanging the bra showing it's like it's such a
mindfuck like coming at it baby come and get it I tried this I'm speaking to the space
more than the cleavage the cleavage is saying just come in my face but the shoulder thing is a mindfuck
okay I'm gonna try this one
it was like, okay, I got it, I think I got it, I'm gonna try this one.
Cleavage.
Let's see if it does.
How can you expect to talk to a man, right, face to face with Cleavage showing?
You know he's gonna look down, see the boobs, see the Cleavage, think of his stick in between them.
Like, nothing's gonna get accomplished at that meeting.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no.
Well, it's making you look different hole. I mean I need to use a different
So now you have to change what you can change my face. I mean that's easy
Well, I mean it made you a different race and so I'm trying to keep it kind of
Well, I'm I'm multiracial in a lot of ways. It's gonna be hard trying
I'll use grok because meta AI was being difficult
They might make me, I don't know, at the end of it,
that they'll make me Italian, probably.
Oh, yeah.
Mafia.
Oh, you know, I think there's an Italian...
I think I mean the word mafia or something has to do with beautiful women or something like that
Well the Italian guys they they do like the black girls, so I'm not worried about that. That's not in
Now I got it
Here we go
Okay
Let me see if I get...
Oh my God, that was trying to get me to upgrade, okay.
Okay, let me see.
End image.
Okay, is it working?
Oh my gosh, it's trying to get me to...
Oh my God.
I think he's taking me to the order page.
I don't know.
It's okay.
I believe you did a good job.
Don't worry.
I'm trying.
I can actually.
I don't have to see it.
I already know you did a great job.
Well, this is one of the ones I'm I'll show you one of the ones the other the other side made but it doesn't look okay
I'm already laying down. I'm asleep here. Look at this one. Okay. Okay free fall asleep here
Image, okay, so this is what it came up with and here you go
Me too Alex. I'm laying down too, baby. We're sleeping together on the panel
Well, no, I'll screen count. Who the fuck is that?
No, that was me that's no I didn't
Yeah
It's like if I if I had a lighter complexion
was like 20 years younger that's me yeah I think I got it more more but look at
me that's me okay it made your scarf the same they put you in a blue top blue
by the way but no she's pretty she is pretty
she's looked is that a real girl is that an AI picture it's an
Eurasian a little bit of africa she's pretty in an understated way
how smart she's a smart girl look at her eyes look at the lips the nose the
cheese the face is pretty the hair is high if she had longer hair she'd be
hotter but she doesn't look fat she could kill me I would kill to fuck this
thing okay she's so smart she can use
telepathy to kill you yes man would kill to fuck that
trust me whatever you say I'm not yeah I can actually animate it too okay I'm
gonna animate it okay well here you go it's coming it's just gonna it's coming
up right now and I'll it's almost there it's just coming I'm a man trust me
Come on
It's animating something here it is it's got it's got it. Oh my gosh. Oh wow hurry up. You're gonna love this you're gonna love this
Okay, hurry up. Yeah, I'm gonna love until I see it bro. Let me see I'll be the judge of what I'm gonna love
Is it
Okay, yeah, here it is. Okay, I got it. Oh people tell me that shit sometimes like you're gonna love this and I watch him
Oh, I don't love it
Oh no. Yes. That's not look like me. Wow. Look at that hot mama. I don't think that looks like me. No. She's so hot. Okay. I'm sorry. That's exactly you. What are you talking about? That's you. It's close but not exactly. Close.
Yeah. Well here's the picture of it. The picture's a little bit better.
Ronis, can you take a close-up, though?
Can you get there and I'm working?
I do like it. I'm not against it.
Here, there you go. I got it.
There.
I don't think it looks like me.
Can you join the panel?
Of course, Ilya, come on up. The link is pinned.
It looks like you because it is you. Okay, okay
Seiki all right, so everybody heard it tonight. Me and I said you have a contract
Even three years. We still haven't found love. We're gonna get married. Okay
so
I'm blocking you. You're not blocking you. Two or three
I didn't block Ilya. I didn't block anybody. I'll give you a two and a half year buffer.
Okay, I'll give you a two and a half years.
Crystal Marie's blog. Yeah, I mean do your thing for the next two years. If love doesn't come across
then, you know, it's you and me baby. Times are taken, the clock's taken, okay?
That's what I know.
I'm not worried.
You'll back out before me.
No, I won't.
Actually, if that's the case, I'll be waiting.
All right, for the two and a half years.
Because I know...
Wait.
McQueen, you said three years.
Now, two and a half?
Yes.
Black North has faked, and 2020 keeps asking to see boobs.
Well, we can't see boobs on the panel.
One time, you know, it's funky.
We should all make those kind of agreements up here.
Like, psyche, you should call Peter tomorrow and say,
listen, baby, I know we have our differences,
but if you don't find love in five years,
you should get married, because the clock's ticking,
and none of us, you know?
You're going to need somebody to gain your coffee and your little slippers for you.
I'm scared to ask McQueen, but who do you think I should marry?
Me, baby.
I'll sign the contract with you or whatever.
Three years.
Challenge.
Hahaha.
I'm not into bigamy like that, man.
No, you ain't.
All right.
So who do you want to marry?
Who?
Then?
Same man?
Absolutely.
I just threw up through my mouth.
I actually have a picture.
Like, I made this picture of, like, you know, I got a, I got like a leaked image of him.
Honestly, you being funny with that shit, bud.
I had a girl tell me that once back in the day when like a young as a joke
She was like you I swear to God
She was like you want to make a pact if we don't like are not married by like 45 or something like we'll get married
That's this is who I'm getting this from I didn't make this shit up
Some girl told me that one and I was like alright deal and it makes sense like you love doesn't come cuz
Don't I'm just remembering her name is more real a real
45 we're getting married, okay
Actually have a picture of Sam and and here here he is. Here's a real picture of him. I just altered it slightly
You make them look good, Psych.
Psych, if you're not married by 50, buddy, I don't know.
You're a gay man.
I think you're a meat pal.
I think you're open to the sunset.
Oh, if you get...
McQueen, you cannot marry everyone on the panel.
You just cannot.
Yes, I can if we go right ran I can have 12 wives. Don't tell me what I can do. I got the whole shit planned out
Okay, but I'm not going
We'll all get married
Put you in a burka if I but I'll go to Iran. I'll have a type of sex change though burka
You me everybody what will be in there all the hapers
12 wives in a rain. That's my end game by the way
I'll go to an array and just have 12 wives. 12! You can marry. I think that's the law at 12.
Okay, well, you can not put me in the same house.
You can't do my homework, baby!
I know, you'll see.
Oh my gosh.
12 wives. Jesus. Picture that breakfast table, huh?
Who wants pancakes? Me, me, me, me, me, me.
Who wants to see my, does everyone want to see my Charles Manson?
Yeah, let me see if I can remember and bring that up.
That was pretty fun.
Um, let me see.
Yeah, there's like a, a trip kick made this great video.
I'm sure you've probably seen it, but um, it's a short.
The trip kick makes some great videos.
And uh, yeah, you're, you're in a few of them.
I was on there that are on rumble, um, of these, uh, the trip kick videos, but,
You know, me, well, he didn't even, he did me as Michael Jackson too. I don't know if you ever saw that, but um, this is the, this is a classic one. Have you seen this one? Here we go.
Oh, hold up, hold up, really quick. Okay, there we go. Um, guys enjoy. This is, uh, my trip. Kick. Um, investigate. Oh, okay, okay, okay.
And, okay, perfect. Okay.
And...
Have you seen this one?
The random.
Tied up the family at gunpoint.
Then ordered his followers to go inside and commit ritual slaughter.
Random.
Right.
I'm telling you.
You're doing exactly what I said.
of members of a so-called religious cult with a leader they called Jesus as had
three of its followers arrested called themselves the family they came and went
and the number varied from 20 to 30 police said they were a pseudo-religious
cult. What do you want to call me a burglar for? I've never killed anyone. I don't need to kill anyone.
I have it here.
That Persian spell put on me.
Great Morse for what?
You people have done everything in the world to me.
Doesn't that give me equal rights?
I can do anything I want to you people at any time I want to,
because that's what you've done to me.
You know, if I wanted to kill somebody,
I'd take this book and beat you to death with it,
and I wouldn't feel a thing.
It'd be just like walking to the drugstore.
Do you feel a brain?
Are you mad?
Do you feel like Mojka Bob's reference?
Got friends?
Mojka, Mojka, Mojka, Mojka, Mojka, Mojka, Mojka, Mojka,
Mojka, Mojka, Mojka, Mojka, Mojka, Mojka, Mojka,
I can have a crystal ball, like every good wizard.
Here we go.
He is great, huh?
All right, psyche is everyone.
Okay, yeah.
Well, of this cult, call me whatever you'd like.
Hey, what's up, Brandon?
So Brandon Mitchell.
Why no Brandon Mitchell? That's up in the living room.
So I can muted.
Okay, hold on.
Have you muted? I'm not muted.
Do you hear me? Lou?
I can't hear you.
Okay, hold on. I need this one on.
McQueen's muted too.
Oh McQueen. Oh yeah, he's muted.
How are we doing guys? Brandon Mitchell, do I know Brandon Mitchell?
Is that thread? I know, let me see.
Psyche just showed us the future, yes.
I actually have one that's kind of light too that I can throw around like the David Bowie one.
Sarah, this is not an ordinary gift for an ordinary girl.
And then he has this crystal ball that turns into snakes and stuff.
Yep, I just showed you the future.
I'm gonna go, oh thank you guys.
I think Alex fell asleep. Did you fall asleep, Alex Andrew?
You should go to sleep.
Good night, sweetheart.
Love you.
Psyche making new religion?
Yes.
It is the cult of Psyche.
Well, Psyche is actually a goddess.
And she's a butterfly goddess, actually, so.
You saw a Jesus-like character the other day.
He was wearing a pyramid on his head,
and his chat swore he'd levitate.
Well, yeah.
There's a guy in the, I guess, the McMartin,
one of the guys the rest of the day,
and he had a pyramid hat he would wear.
Yeah.
I can throw away in the future, in the future like this.
Yeah, so I have like, a lot of cool things.
I'm gonna do a job off of here.
Okay, sweetheart, thank you so much.
I think Alex fell asleep.
Love you, Alex.
Sweet dreams.
Love you, sweetheart.
I'll let her go.
Okay, see you soon, me, Alex.
Do you want me, McQueen?
The panel fell asleep.
Hey, so, Brandon, do I know you?
Do I know you?
Let's see. I'm their Jesus. Yep. I'm the goat. Maybe I
I'd probably say I'm I'm found the clown mask on the curb. Yep.
Anybody else want to come up before I go? I might I'll
actually I'll show you the I'll play the video I made today.
I think that Alex McQueen falls asleep too. I think he did.
Okay. Here's the video I made today. Um enjoy and then I'll
probably wrap it up. Let me see. It's yeah. It's right here.
They smile in your face
While planning your fall
But the joke's on them now
I already read it all
it's run by those who see the design they lie they manipulate they play but i learned the game
yesterday never fight with your innocent
Hi, sweetie. I couldn't hear you.
Hey!
I'm sorry.
No, I rejoined because I thought it was over.
Yeah, I mean, I thought it was like, I thought I couldn't hear anybody.
I thought everyone fell asleep.
Well, I did. Well, I didn't fall asleep, but I did other stuff around here.
Okay.
you see the Charlie I'm intoxicated you know post my little links and
everything but I don't think anyone saw them so I will post that oh well I was
trying to like show that there's like power to being a woman of color when it
came to certain things that were being said but I was wasted and I'm wasted
No, I'm having fun, but I'm posting your links right now. I'm posting. I don't have any links for your channel
IRL news time ip2 wiki.com
Those are stupid links. Oh, okay. What links did you want to post? I don't know. I don't have any new links, okay?
Okay, I don't want to be a linkless. Okay, linkless
Well, oh my, what's this picture?
Okay, well, you know, I do love the commercial you made
for me, the Psyche's Boys Club.
And-
Well, I feel like people think like I'm like trying
to like get you or like insult you with it and I'm not.
No, I don't feel like you are at all.
I don't feel like you are at all.
It is parody, it is meant to be like funny.
Oh, it was, no, I loved it.
I love it. I could be darker.
I could be darker with the humor, but I didn't think I thought it was like
in a weird way, you actually are creating like a bad boys club.
I know. And I actually I love this.
I think that the guys like it really.
I I'm ready for this club.
I'm ready for this club.
I mean, I'll gather it up like and then they.
There we go. This is great, guys. I don't know if you've seen this. This is so great.
All right. Everybody watch it and tell us what you think about it.
I'm not looking at the chat, but you tell me what the chat says.
Okay.
Are you Latino living in California?
Have a criminal history under the age of 30,
familiar with Santa Muerte, into live streaming?
Enjoy distributing illegal substances.
Do you know it's how the guy on the left looks like Rick?
And so, you might be part of the Psyche's Boys Club.
Glasses.
Yeah.
They're cute.
Okay, so we have, let's welcome Alexander Sussman.
That's awesome.
I mean, what do people think?
I mean, I...
Everyone's laughing hysterically at that.
I think people, they want to come up in arms.
Come against me, not psyche, okay?
Because if you come up in arms against me,
that gives me an excuse to defend myself finally,
by anything is necessary.
And I have been waiting for that day my entire life.
If you need some backup, I'll have your back.
No, I don't need backup.
The day that I defend myself by any means necessary,
I'm going to have the best time doing it,
and I'm going to hit every single one of my targets.
So if you plan to come against me on my day,
I'm defending myself by any means necessary is not the best thing well
I will not I will not I will let you I will let you do your thing because you are a powerful
Fabulous woman and I know you can it's gonna be the black woman
Day of the world that I defend myself by enemies necessary
Every single person who has ever filed a false police report against me
That is going to be the day. I'm not gonna stay like in one location
That is gonna be the day that I just find wherever you are and I feel like one to fitting myself by enemies
by any means
Very anyway, so let me go after everybody else. I want to go after who's been
Fraudulently filing things against me and I'm gonna go from the Northeast
to the Southwest in one day
Yeah, all in one day
And I'm just gonna defend myself by any means necessary against everyone who's ever filed
a false police report against me and it's just gonna be like your last day on earth.
This woman Claire do something because she's like talking to you.
I don't know.
I don't know who Claire is.
There's CFC.
I've never heard of her so he's not in my list.
Okay.
There's some other people.
Mm-hmm.
I know who your list on your list.
So I mean, I'm just saying that's going to be my day of defending myself by any means necessary against whoever I feel necessary to defend myself against.
Well, I would never file a police report because I'm too, I can't wait at the police.
They've been waiting too long in that lobby, so I'm going to try to do one for that cement for that guy.
Yeah, but that's also your white God only only two women who
classify themselves as white who I'm going to
eliminate and
They should probably
Call for extra patrol
Will that help no
It's coming. I mean, I'm just letting you know
Okay, it might be the year 2027 might be 2028. I don't know, but it's coming. Okay
Those two white women better watch the watch out. I mean they could be anywhere
It could be it could be. Yeah
But uh and god watch watch out
Claire Claire's being very weird. Just watch out. Yes
Alright, so are there any more mass-terroristic things I need to put out for the night?
Probably not.
I love you Alex.
It's all in theatrical comedic form.
Yes.
It was not real.
If you thought it was real, you must be on crack.
Someone says peps and amber, or maybe Jen.
No, I don't even know who those people are.
I'm just thinking about crackheads.
I mean, who's the latest crackhead we've known about?
Oh, I forgot.
Junkie James.
Yeah.
This is not even rude, this is bad.
He's very, very, very rude.
Like, he's a horrible person.
And then like, he's on, he's literally on crack.
I know, Method Fentanyl the other night,
Method Fentanyl hits for $10 each.
Yeah.
Of course they think about me and it's like,
I'm like, we're like, oh my God,
Psyche's charging $5 for songs.
This guy is doing Method Fentanyl hits
and everyone's just like, oh my God, he's so funny.
And then he's like rolling around in his underwear.
No, I think it's time for the state of Washington
to be aware that it's possible his poor elderly parents
fall prey to him. I mean
We don't know who's gonna take care of those poor elderly people, but it shouldn't be a it shouldn't be a
meth or fat head. I mean our crack head or whatever you want to call it
You're pretty good at taking care of things. It's like can you imagine? Oh my gosh, that's crazy
I mean, I don't really want to intervene, but should I?
I don't know.
Well, I'd be a divine intervention.
Yeah, let's see.
Yeah, we've got, yeah.
Well, do you like my shirt tonight?
I love this shirt.
This is one of my favorites.
Yeah.
It's because if you look at it, it's kind of like black
and white a little bit.
Oh, OK.
Yeah, I see a little, like the little design.
Yeah, I got my, this is like, this one is, this is, yeah,
this is like, it's called Solomon's, oh, sorry, my nail's terrible, I'm so sorry, let me see.
Okay, yeah.
Well, I don't really look at your nails.
That's whoever the other person is, or there.
Can you see it?
Yeah.
That's the first, it's called the first symbol of the sun.
It's what's used?
It was, I think it's, they say metatron.
That's somebody.
Yeah, it's like an earth angel and he has horns.
You see, he has little horns on his head.
Oh, okay.
It's of the sun.
and then it's on the back of it.
It's got that, there you go.
Well, Metatron, is that what Metatron?
I don't even know what Metatron looks like.
And what are all these markings on the back?
I mean, is that a language?
It's Hebrew letters of the angels.
I think there's 72 angels names in Hebrew.
Like the three.
Okay, well, I guess that's all I need to know,
whatever that is.
And I have another one too.
This one is actually, am I wearing my other one?
This is like it's got kind of interesting symbol on it like that one oh that's nice and then the back of it
It's got that it's got a cross. Okay, so we got that going on. Yeah, and these are I
Don't know. I just don't I just feel I just find them good luck
Well, I mean, maybe maybe they mean stuff. I mean, I'm gonna run all of them through the AI. Yeah
Well, it's like that. Not this moment because I'm sleepy
It's called the first symbol of the Sun because they have all these planetary symbols of song
Are the Sun psyche?
Yes, you are
You're you're you know, you actually like Mark Schenkenberg. I feel like you're like this
Walk through of my life of good-looking attractive men who have helped me
along the way
Figure out like who am I?
Alexandra, what do I not need to worry about? What do I need to worry about?
What means something what does it?
What do you want? What do you desire? What doesn't matter? All these things.
Right.
You are a beautiful person and I know I picked on you and bullied you and I wasn't as bad as some people.
Oh, no, well, basically, it was like, yeah, I mean, it's like you really helped me, like,
you know, like, and, and we're whatever I did, that was horrible.
I hope that you beat me up in that capacity.
Well, I didn't want to.
I didn't want to.
It was all about.
But at some point, you need to just for the karmic alone.
I probably, you know what, I probably deserved everything.
I probably deserved all of it, but here, look at this.
This minnetron looks a little bit like me.
I think it looks a little bit like me.
All right, let me see.
Okay, I'm gonna, did I get the right one?
Okay, I have to.
You've been looking really nice lately.
Like, I don't know what you've been changing,
but you look like healthier.
Thank you. Yeah. I mean, I've been putting on like a little
Why is the whole what maybe you've been eating a little? Have you
been eating more food? Yes, I have been. Oh my gosh. Okay, good.
Good. The difference is like, I'm really eating food. I ate
some chicken wings today.
Did you put the sauce on it?
Mmm, I had the chili sauce on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the, on the,
danger. If you avoid danger, like serious people that might be out to get you, you'll
be okay. But you have to conscientiously avoid danger. That's what I think about you.
I will. This is my, remember I said that I'm related to the first clown? This was him right there.
Yeah, I don't buy that so much anymore. I don't think you're a clown.
No, I don't think you're a clown. I think you're better than a clown. I'm not against clowns.
Well, there's a family called the Merovingians and they're supposedly of both the bloodline of Jesus and Lucifer.
you know and I don't believe it I think they made it up you think they made it up well it might be
but they're called the long-haired kings of France and stuff like that I don't care I think that I
don't want you to be a clown because I love you and I love you too I love you too but I just think
that you're more of like a teacher so that's what you have to be
Thank you. Yeah, I love it. I love teaching and it's like
In a clown if you do you want to be a clown is I mean, I think it's an interesting like
Grimaldi is actually the rule Monaco now. So it's like, you know, he became
I know, but it's too good. I don't think you should be a clown, right? Well, you know, I mean
Yeah, clowns are you know because I think about that evil Joker
And I'm scared of the Joker's
So, you know, it's a selfish reason I don't want you to be a clown because I'm scared of clown.
So, and Nora Grace is like, has my opinion changed since Alexander Mears told me about the guy?
Well, yeah, I definitely listened to her.
You know, who's saying crime more? Oh my god. Well, I just don't I I don't think that I think that you should be a
Wizard hmm
Well, like like a super magician, but what like a real
wizard like
with like super
like medicinal wizardry.
Yeah.
If that's...
I think I do have a healing energy.
I mean, it's like, I hope I have like...
Yeah, I think you should heal stuff with your wizard.
I mean, that to me is you.
Like if I had to like put a label on you,
you're a super healing, good, medicinal,
a wizard who creates like the most amazing new stuff
that nobody has ever thought about before.
Love to, and look, I have my crystal ball right here.
Yes.
Oh my God, you have a real crystal ball.
Ah, do you have some wizard stuff?
I do have some.
You are a wizard for real.
I think you are.
Thank you. Well yeah, I do know some I have sitting magic under several traditions and so you know
Well, no matter no matter what you have the magic from within you. Yes. And so do you. I know
Yours is I don't think yours is totally awake yet, but I'm excited. I think it's maybe
I don't think this year. I think next year
I'm going to come into my power.
Am I going to come in finally?
Not this year.
I think this year you're like figuring stuff out.
Yeah.
And you already did figure stuff out.
Don't get me wrong.
I could be totally off because I'm off sometimes.
But I think that you are going to totally be full force
next year.
That's what I think.
It's 2027 is going to be my year.
I like that.
I like that number.
27. Well, I'm all about seven, that's why. Yeah, we're both born as seven. Yeah, and I feel like
kind of sheltering you a little bit because I do care about you, so I don't want you to
I'm gonna go to bed.
I love you, sweetie.
Thank you so much for coming.
It was a blast.
I like this little musical track here on the background.
It added to it.
It made it better.
It did, it was awesome.
I love you.
Thank you.
All right, sleep well, have good dreams.
And I'm sending you positive energy, light, love,
all that stuff,
but especially good dreams to inspire you
because
Thank you. You just need extra right now
Thank you so much. All right. I'll talk to you later. Bye. Bye
Hey Nora, so it says don't block me. I'm just wondering. Okay, so Nora
What are you talking about something like someone was talking about that? I mean, it's like that he said he has in the past
I don't know who's delusional cookie cookie. I'm gonna kick that person out cookie cookie
There okay, here's my new song guys. This is called the game
I'm gonna restart it and
We'll see it. Maybe I'll be back. It was a song. Maybe I won't see see what happens. Here we go
They smile in your face
While planning your fault
But the jokes on them now
I already read it all
The world is not run by the kind
It's run by those who see the design
They lie, they manipulate
They play, but I learned the game yesterday
Never fight with your innocence
i see the game, i see the game, and every player, every name, they move like pawns, i move like light, i see the game and i'm out of sight, they can't touch what they can't predict, they can't control what they can't inflict, i see the game, i see the game
Watching for cracks in the armor that faxed
said something that change everything the wise man except once what the fool
does finally transition I'm already finished while you're still starting
this isn't a battle it's a foregone conclusion you can throw stones but I'm
a still lake every ripple you make just shows where you break and comprehend
what you can see can't begin what I've already penned see
Isn't defeating your enemies
Seekers and survive
Tonight specimen and they're smiling
No, no pitch for no open hate just five
Questions and a coupon for betrayal
That didn't not that didn't not that didn't not that didn't not
you're slid and soft with the halo tilt just checking on you for the loaded blue
you said i care you said i see you brought fake loyalty wholesale tax free you'll learn my
words you'll learn my math you're not real hard then set the trap we'd call it concern not call it
You leave with screenshots tucked in your chest
You want the T, the keys, the codes
The private bank, the hidden roads
Not here to heal, not here to build
Just here to see where the armor is
Too many questions, not enough so
Too much sugar in the casserole
Too much I'm neutral, too much I'm good
false little friend you won't get far
but then I'll spin that crow
everybody watch the bloody troll
who died, who died
false little friend you won't get far
but then I'll spin that crow
first they fly
then they pride
who said what
with the saintly eye
not to stir things that'll routine
meanwhile
they mop the floor with kerosene
they whisper here
Person A gets a spice double quote. Person B gets a softer note. Person C gets a hate all drama.
First from the department, a manufactured karma. Now the room feels weird, the wires are crossed.
Trust gets taxed and the vibe gets lost. That's not magic, they're the sleight of hand.
A sewer wizard with a needy brand. Can't build a stage, can't hold a room so they brand free space.
Another folks' doom. Always nearby when the mess appears. Always so shocked with crocodile tears.
is concerned funny how bridges behind them burn but the troll but the troll this is
the goal in the friendship roll oh oh oh oh smile in the front little knife in the
shore acts so worried while they gossip to
Back is truth and sell the stain
Danger two, they split the crew
Make folks doubt what they already knew
Danger three, they bait reaction, them point and scream
Look bad attraction, oh sweetheart, you built amaze
Now you're acting scared of the fire you raise
Danger four, they drain your heart
Diplofocus part by part, not always
Trano in the war, sometimes they just want a rectal floor
What's the cure?
Slow that truss, what's the tip?
Patterns first, what's the rule?
Lock that gate, what if they pound?
Too damn late, guard your grief
Don't overshare, watch boundary
It won't play translate a priest and spy won't hug you close while sharpening lies
A real friend comes a fake one stirs a real friend ass a fake one
There's a real friend keeps the chambersill
A fake one wants your wounds revealed
So if they rush like this and he's cloned with hungry eyes and a borrowed tone
Don't hand them candles, keys or gold, some demons freeze when the door gets closed
Fuck Detroit, but Detroit, cheap little ghoul in a satin robe
walk slip through the loophole till the lights come up and we name it all buddy troll buddy troll
fall familiar with the hungry soul you wanted the temple the map the scroll now dance back out
through the banishment hole
That didn't fit, nah, that didn't fit, nah, no more entry, not at all
That didn't fit, nah, that didn't fit, nah, true hit, hotter than the mirror ball
True to yard, out to road, exit left, little buddy trolls
My law, you won't, we know the road case closed on a buddy troll
C'est qu'il y a...
If it's you or something else, wearing pieces of yourself, faces hanging in the air.
Try them on if you still care. Every mask of life you wore, every life still wanting more.
You said, something's always watching. I said, yeah.
is all too long I'm running from the thing I was the mirror shows a stranger the ground
keeps giving way beneath the weight there's a hand even in the nightmare I'm not alone
even when the darkness swallows whole there are helpers here
That fear can make, they can wake me when I'm trapped
They can sh-
Hello?
Hello, what's up?
Hey, what's up dude?
It's been a while.
Yeah, what's that music?
That's music I make.
Pardon?
No, no, right.
Right now, do you hear like a loud ass background music?
It's called The Ducks in the Pond or something.
I'm gonna turn it off.
Oh, please, please.
It's super loud.
Okay.
I got it.
Yeah, yeah.
It's been a while, how have you been?
Good, I miss you.
Let me look at you closer, hold on.
Wow, I see you now.
Oh my God, you look like a celebrity.
You look like you look like Michael you look like Michael Jackson's little brother or something Michael Jackson the fuck oh
Yeah, I already played
packs
But it's oh, yeah, we already played the buddy troll song. Yeah, I'm here with I'm here with a rogue. No, man
Rogue no man is the gym right there. Yeah
Yeah, you're Paige Alex Alex Alex just woke up your page
Are you uh am I
Yeah, you were never banned to begin with Ilya about the night. You're not banned. Why would you think you get back?
Kick you off you even Ilya you're not banned at all
So you get a you get in addition to your tattoo
How do you like it? You like it? You wanna see it? I think that this is so crazy that I
Like it's crazy that this is real life that you actually went through with this. Yeah
That's some cartoon as shit, dude
Backwards to look backwards to you. Oh my god. I'm a little bit it looks like like some sort of if let's say you don't know anything
You see that it looks like some sort of actual gang
mean
It's the fuck BKG. I got it here. I'm gonna switch it around. It's a video. Oh, hi Lenore. Okay video a camera
Hi, okay perfect now what you come out, right?
There you go. Can you read it?
Yeah, yeah, that's so funny. That's crazy. You like that and you put it right on your heart Lake. Yeah
damn
But it will in the linoar is on my heart, but then the wording is
They didn't have to modify it at all. I just had to
Fast forward like in a year, imagine that you go back to being okay with beat and then what you're gonna never mind
No, don't fuck BKG
Yeah, well y'all all cross our crossing it out. It's gonna have like a it's gonna have a whole bunch of
It's gonna turn into a whole chess piece by the time that you're late fucking 70
Welcome another guest
Oh my god. Not this guy. Yeah, what's up? Oh my god. You look terrible. What happened? Good morning
That's because I'm kind of drunk. You're drunk. I know I'm just having one beard in there
Oh, you look pretty good. You look kind of cute. I could barely open my eyes. No. Oh my people's podcast
The right hole psyche. What about your hole?
This is a thing about a hole
You okay
Clearly not look at the guy is barely with us ban you from stream yard. That's I didn't that's I didn't bring you from
Stream art. Oh, yeah, there's nobody banned from my stream. I swear. No one person the guests. There's not one person banned
Oh, I need to cancel my fucking stream yard before oh, that's why maybe
Before it charges you how much is gonna charge your psyche like 80 dog $80 or something for like a week
Oh, you are thank you so much. I'll really help me out. $80. Okay. Thank you. I appreciate that
Counts
Okay, so Rob no matter where we've been
Uh, dealing with a very, very stressful 2026, um, I'm a virgin.
You are?
From that.
I don't believe you.
Cancel?
Okay.
My ass is a virgin, but my dicks are slut.
Oh my god.
Okay, well, that's crazy. Okay cancel got it. I got it. I canceled on time. Oh, yeah McQueen back
Yo, psyche. Do you have girl? Do you have like girlfriends like girls that are friends that I like is your
Fat boy, shut the fuck up my man. If you show a gun or poor mom this channel again
Don't do it. Don't do it. They're gonna go don't get any ideas
But you're saying if I found there yeah when this guy's drunk just get ready for it, bro
I'm just telling you man
Damn oh and Ziggy the little all right here we go Wesley. He's all scared. What are you scared about bro?
I don't know
Fake plastic gun that I bought the mighty nice sun store. Mm-hmm. So I'll show it to me. I don't want to see it though
I banned you in your game. So these losers they get all drunk and come up here and show a fake gun in their little peepees
What's up with that? What's up with you?
I remember your girl punch you on my panel. You guys are freaks shut the fuck up
Yeah, I remember when you got shot in the knee.
I remember when you throw your shit and you throw guns.
Taking guns. That's all you do.
Let's see what happens tonight, my boy.
Let's see what you do tonight.
I'm gonna, I'm just gonna wait for it.
You fat losers.
Let's see what your fat losers do tonight.
It's like Tweet'l Dee and Tweet'l Dum.
I wasn't gonna miss this party, man.
It's like dumb and dumber
They look like two eggs they do look like dumb and twiddle did you look like a fucking retarded
Yo, I never seen such a fat fuck then glow. You know the day he was naked
He had a shirt off that motherfuckers body his stomach drags to the floor. He's like 300 pounds
Bro, 300 pounds is not here.
This guy sits in his bucket.
That's how I know you're a little kid.
You need a lot on the whole day.
300 pounds is a lot.
Oh, come on, come on, come on.
That feels like 400 pounds, bro.
You're tripping.
Oh, I see.
Look at his fat on the edge.
No, stand up, stand up, blow.
Show us how the stomach hangs like a pig.
Stand up you fat pig. Look at that disgusting animal
Look at that disgusting
Bro, is your look at that man Titty fucking pig. He looks like a fucking pig that I would go
I will go to him in Columbia. That's better Neil bow all day every day
But need
Yeah, 99 cents store t-shirt
Yeah, gang sons. Yeah, okay. Hi, you bum
Yeah, you bum you're getting cancer from that shirt that die is soaking into your back motherfucker. I
like your nipples
My god, what's that? It's crazy work, bro. Talk. You're wrong. No, man. What the fuck are you doing up here, bro?
Hey, what's up? How you doing Alex?
We got a lot of I am good. What are you doing, bro? Like Mexican night? I feel like I'm in Mexico
I know they were just providing this guy with a bunch of
Time he showed you your stupid core that drove itself and get crashed
I think that more of moron that was so
What a loser this is like loser city
Yeah
Yeah, thank you. I don't mean to if you offend me, but you're asking questions and it's like this channel you're yours charisma
Don't act like Christine. Oh my god. Who is this? Who's no great? Yo, what's the ground say?
Yeah
Why do you think you still have it like you're snow like you guys are wild bees
Okay, you have a neck beard. You're trying to look ugly. You're actually
How are you? Oh, 300 glow got snuffed by his girl. That was cold cock them in the spring. At least
I'm not a real terrorist like you're
That little pussy glow star showing that's why he has to show guns because he gets punched by his wife
Alex chill out. He has a wife
Yeah, show that talk psyche there you go pull those pants down. That's show the man when you're made of my boy
kill you in a new york nobody's shit
Well, you guys are Mexican losers alcoholic losers. I got a peepee and a gun. Hey, you guys are so
Me and retarded scary, bro
I can't go back to Long Island
Because I'm over talking you for fuck
I'm over talking you motherfucker. I'm over talking you
You can win this
W W
W
Here to Mexican losers alcoholic bomb losers
20s they're already
Alcoholics bro getting put by the girl showing the little wiggly dicks. We're talking about bombs beyond bums pictures
These motherfuckers in 20 years brother
Pictures taking glow store in 20 years. They're not gonna make it another five years, bro
These guys are gonna die from liver cancer or be arrested for showing fake guns
These guys are the bummed the bottom of the barrel broke bottom of the barrel
Bold yo sick you got a fucking rooftop my boy. Look at that. He's got a sunroof sick is losing his hair
Beat us making sick
Oh my god, it's got a full head. Look at him. He's got a fucking he's losing his hair. Look at that hair
Look at that. That's bye-bye hair by the way. Look how it's gray hair
This guy it's all gray and tanning. It's a round black. Wow
Look at all the gray look at the gray. Oh, look at the thin hair
Well, and then the fat fuck goes to has to die is there and pray his wife gives him plot and also does some punch him in the face
This is the kind of pussies we're dealing with
I would smack you why are you crying so yeah, whatever. I don't know. I can't hear you. Would you say you're crying so much?
I can't hear you. Did you say something? Anyway, Psyche, bro, what's up, bro? Who's Eric Sean?
Okay, so now it's anyway. Who's Eric Sean? Anyway, Psyche, who's Eric Sean? Yo, let's welcome
Eric Sean to the building. Eric Sean is in the house. Come on. Eric Sean in the house. My boy,
Eric Sean. Where you been, my boy? That's my boy. He's gonna be, we're gonna have sex with a woman.
Yeah, and also miss that motherfucker with the eggs on the
Origin we're not an orgy. How is that? What that? Okay? That's my boy Alex
Yeah
Sex my boy
Signed my boy
And then Alexander's gonna sit in the corner like a bitch. Okay, bitch. Oh my god
What am I gonna be doing?
What am I gonna be? Fuck this guy gonna have a heart attack in two years. He's so much ham. Look how fatty is bro
This guy's dying in front of us just eating old fat E and J fat much
Bro, your heart can't keep up all that fatness my man
You're gonna die in the next three years
That's all right
Yeah, I'll see you in hell my boy. That's a promise
,
I think it's I think she I think she's talking about some of the else classy
well
this nigga is gonna die because he was a little bitch what you're gonna die from yeah what he's
gonna stop his what oh too hard and he's gonna lie for a minute he's drinking loser you pep
fox because he's a little big you're a glow star when you came the other day with your shirt off
that was the most disgusting fatness i've ever seen
That's not normal, bro. That's 300 pound kind of shit your stomach. You look like Jabba the heart
Literally, you're the form
You're the form bro. That is fat like fat fat
That's not like a chubby that my man glow store is the form the brother
He's dead in two years. That's a fact and
Wesley Brown is right behind them
And that's a fact brother
Really? And he knows it too. They're so in pain that they don't care. They're like, I am fat and I am gonna die in a year
I don't even care, bro. That's how much
They can't wait to die you guys want to die don't you fat fuck
Haha
Yo, I got salami you want salami and ham and platanos and my doodles you want to come
Your arteries are so clogged right now
Look at your face, bro. You're always so clogged your heart. It's not gonna make it another year, bro
Later
What I didn't even do anything. I didn't mean to interrupt
With the gun, I'm gone. That's it. I'm not here hanging out with psyche and Sean
Those fuck fuck no, I didn't trust them, bro
And psyche retarded they do to me all the time and they fuck up good panels
Alexander mayors was up here for 10 hours tonight. There's no way these
And show the little dick and ruin it you understand
and that's why I came up Alexander mayors
Yeah, no, they did it. They came up after
Fuck it up. Those like you have to raise the panel
I'm not Alexander mayors does not happen, bro. You do not erase an Alexander
That's 300 pounds. I mean three hundred
Excuse me
I said
Fuck you so awesome. You be sucking on the bong and they'll show a gun a cock and boom dad
That was an attack man. It was an attack coordinated at home
Coordinate exactly coordinated. I think they keep the turtles trying to pay them to
Sabotage. Oh my god. He's showing his backstage
Who I got it so small or it looks like a vagina actually. Oh my god. He's showing it
Yeah
How's Nika time
but Eric you can't say that kind of shit you have to type
just become kidding and end it now
I know hold on oh we've grown on that's back I have to I promise I won't get I won't pull my shirt okay
hello well thankfully the attack was mitigated by Alex thank you thank you look at you welcome
well now I'm gonna go back and leave you guys alone bro that's the only reason I came up okay love you
That's a fucking that's a loyal
Isn't he?
Warrior at your service. Yes. I love him. He's mad. He's make my my sheriff
I have like a real
Real cop. I love you finally gave him a little out look to be a cop somewhere. I
Know yeah, finally. He's like actually a real cop. I made it as a cop. Yeah
So, do you know Alexandra? Did you watch any of the earlier stream? It was pretty good, I think.
No, I was sleeping.
Oh, you were.
What happened?
Well, do you know who she is?
Oh, yeah.
Have you ever seen the movie White Slaves?
No. No, I didn't even... I've never heard of that.
That there's such a thing that movie called white slaves. She pegs somebody in it. She said, oh
White sleep. Oh, well that actually gives a lot of context as far as they her very skewed views on
Human interaction
She's like bare human interaction
Oh my god, let's take it back. No, but I've mentioned she's really cool. She's really cool. So yeah, so how are we doing in the chat?
Okay, it's what time is it 350? We have 37 people. Wow. We've kind of built a back up
Okay, so let me talk you in the back with you. Is he gonna say shit? Oh, I'm gonna see Leslie
I won't say bad things. I friends with gay guys. Let me on boyfriend. Okay. I'll give you one more chance
Correction
Don't badmouth my my
My future baby mama. I'm cool. I'm cool. I just maybe I get a little melty sometimes. Okay, but Alex. She um, I
Think she does like mean only things sometimes
Well, it's like we don't have to agree with everything someone says but she's an awesome person
All right, I would speak on her
Damn
This is like gangster work internet gangster work there. Yeah, we don't say that name here. Yeah
Unless you're complimenting I don't want to hear you Wow
Alright, I won't say anything bad about Alex. What happened with me and Kate. Well Kate is just
Kate got mad because I had this guy
Brandon Q up and then she said oh, I'm a predator protector because I just let him in the chat and then like but now he's a mob
Brandon Q and Tommy were going going at it for like a fucking hour this morning. Oh, they were oh, yeah
Yeah, they were kind of cool, but yeah, they were really going at it. Yeah, I mean, I don't know
I don't I don't know who to believe I don't I don't
Believable and I bought because I wouldn't watch the videos that he said I would I should watch and I watched them and it seemed like
Half of them were like a bad kind of jokes and bad tastes the other half were like, you know
Nothing like where you hurt anybody or like didn't I mean it's like not like the the best
They're not the best footage, but it wasn't like anything that hurt anybody or gonna ask you a question. Sure. Are you lonely?
I mean, I talked to a lot of people, so I was like, no, particularly, I mean, it's like, I'm, I'm, I'm always, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm,
Whatever they call it. What do they call it when you're one verse one? Oh
I want to wrestle with some other for that for lack of words. Oh, yeah
I want to be one like a white do you think like let me ask you another question. Do you have?
any set of standards as far as the people you surround yourself with that if they don't meet them you immediately
expel them from your life
Yeah, I mean, it's like I mean, I don't really want like people that are rapists and murderers, but
And that's it
Well as long as they as long as they're not abusive to me and like they're cool to me so
Right, what about like just the core values of a human being that say somebody's kind of a liar of discipline
That's the thing human beings are imperfect and it's like the people can people improve can they can I be a good influence on them?
Can they or do they have good qualities?
Are they like totally just like throw away and and not throw away the key and stuff like that?
I mean you have to do something pretty bad for that. I mean, it's like I'm pretty loving of human beings
But I know human beings are imperfect
Have you heard of the concept of the misled optimist?
No, what are you trying to lecture me on something? What's up?
No, well, sometimes when people have a very strong leader throughout their life,
they can be a little bit too optimistic. Um, based on their misguidance.
And I think that you're trying to say, what's your point?
I think that you
Come off very lonely, which sets you on a path to accept any companionship whatsoever
No, I just lonely sounds the path of aggressive. I just I kicked off who me
No
The guy that said you sound lonely. Oh, yeah, no direct aggressive aggressive aggressive
I am being proactively aggressive not pass away that I don't need to be happy aggressive
Who cares? Okay
Direction you sound lonely. Yeah, it sounds you know, I know it's like well
I'm not gonna go cry because I'm so lonely because you keep saying it over and over Jesus Christ
Everybody fucking is lonely to some degree. Come on, right and everybody's nobody's perfect and it's like what it's like
What do I have any standards? Yeah, I mean, it's like what I mean, it's like but this person like, you know, so horrible
I mean, I don't I don't think so. I mean, I actually like them so
Not because I'm lonely. It's just because I just find them attractive and nice
I mean, it's like, wow, he hasn't done anything.
He doesn't have a criminal record or anything.
I mean, it's like, I mean, all these people,
like a lot of people that go against him,
he like will talk about their criminal record
and that's why they keep trying to silence him and stuff.
Rogue Noir might come back.
Rogue Noir, I can go into the chat.
You can go into the chat.
What are you talking about?
The guy that was just here.
Oh, what do you mean the other guy I'm talking about?
You said nobody has,
he has an criminal record and this and that.
Oh, Branding Hue, yeah.
Uh-oh.
Yeah, nobody's produced a video of him yet. I mean, I've seen some videos
Convincing to me there. I mean, it's like, I don't know. He's just talking shit. I think he's just joking
Yeah, yeah, I can you wrote trying what you guys are sending people up here to fucking harass me shit
I mean, it's like how about W me for getting these people out of the chat?
Bye
Yeah, unless until somebody permits
Promotes
What's the goddamn word whatever this somebody gives a video of
Brandon Q actually doing some illegal shit and
Right just that was the case then there'd be like, you know a court case or like there'd be like some kind of police report
But it's like no because I mean it's like didn't do anything. I was even illegal. So
Yeah, I don't know everyone's everyone's gonna try to harp on it and shit like that
Oh my god
I think Kate's sending people and she must be because it's like it seems like I'm kind of I don't know
I wrote no man would do that
Yeah, I mean I do when I mean it's like I
Don't know it's like
Fucking I
Don't I just like people I like people even like put up a 300 glow. I mean
I try like people even though I like
If you like if you do something me some of the people that are going against me
I don't like that are bullying me and they're around constantly keep bullying me pull and they and saying horrible things about me
Does I have a problem with but not necessarily this person that had nothing they did nothing to me ever and was just always been nice to me
So I don't understand, but I my standards are too low when it comes to some of those other people
I shouldn't like fucking try to even please them. It's like
I should just be with people I want to be with
Don't know. I'm also not not for like really like outcasting people because I've been outcast so much in my life
I kind of have a maybe you thought you and Kate were cool last time you checked and she posts about me every day
I know she's putting out. She's posting horrible things. I'm I even say anything about anything
I mean, it's like she's just like she's saying she's gonna destroy me. She's I think she thinks she's like, you know
She took her life mission to like how about like get a life that other than like trying to destroy somebody else's
I mean, it's like really the kind of like sad, you know
I'm not sure what happened either. She just kind of turned on me. I don't know if it was like like
Just a time bomb we need to happen or whatever, but I was always nice to her
And then she just like started calling me names and stuff and
Making demands. I guess the guy mentioned something about I don't know
Was there talk about well, he said something about like yeah, he said something about
Passing remark and I was like don't talk about kids. That's all it was right. Oh my god, RG is here
I he's blocked it. I'm gonna see but I'm gonna just kick this person off. Hey, man. Okay, perfect
Talk I will wait. I better shut it down. So it's not me saying it was somebody somebody else. Oh, so
No, okay. Oh my gosh the predator. Well, don't call him that so okay. Bye
Chibi-chibi bye. It's like you're really down to a
Down to meet up in San Francisco. Is it like a pipe dream? I'd love to are you down?
Yeah, I'm down dude. I live I live like an hour north of San Francisco. So it's not an easy
I mean, it's not a hard not a hard drive for me
Okay, you want to hang out dude? Seriously, I'm just down. I'm not gay
But we'll we will hang out absolutely in the Castro and we'll get you fucking late and try to get me late and
Just do it fucking gang bang. I don't know. Okay. That sounds perfect. I'm seriously down
Fuck yeah, I would love to yep
I'll send a picture maybe I'll put a picture on my profile instead of a fucking egg face
Okay, that'd be great. I'd love to see that because yeah, you look like a fried egg right now, but I mean is that
That's not really your picture. No, that's an old that's an old-ass like meme super old
Okay, old meme. Okay, you're not blocked obama. I swear. There's nobody blocked here
But I'm I will be blocking anybody that fucking comes harping at me and saying okay wins
You know all this bullshit people been trying to bother me and shit like that doesn't really just like
Just be banned it, but you're not ban. Oh, yeah, so but you just say you're not actually you're not gay
Not, you know, I am friends with gays and cool gays. I don't give a fuck
You never experienced besides you woke up that and that guy was yeah, there's some guy was trying to suck my dick and I
Yeah, I was about it. Yeah
Well, I wouldn't do that to you. I mean unless you like ask me. Yeah, thank you. Thank you. I appreciate that
Very like even if it was a girl and like I'm attracted to girls even if it was a girl
Just you feel violated, right? Oh, yeah, exactly. Yeah. Well, I'll do I'll make sure it's everything's content
Consensual you're not blocked on stream yard. Yeah. I told you like a million times
I mean, I don't know what to say. It's like you're not you're messy blocked yourself
I didn't kick you off. You could you took yourself up
Just try another account or something. I don't know. I don't know. There's no one blocked
So I think you would look best with uh
If you tied your hair back like in a ponytail or whatever. Yeah, I mean
I would have
You think you want to yeah, keep the long hair, but just like tie it back. Yeah
Yeah, tell me and tell me how you want it baby. I guess I looked it. I got you. You like it
Yeah
There we go. Yeah, yeah
That's a look
There you go. I mean you either do other gay guys or women or gay or
Non-heter non homosexual men agree. I think the pony tells the look dude
Well, yeah, I mean it's like
Someone said I was like a nine today, you know like
Another guy was like I'm in yeah a couple guys that I was a nine
Pretty cool. I actually like a lot of guys have said this year. Hey, if you can find like a woman
They're like joining in like I'll have sex with you
Yeah, I don't know if I'll be able to find a woman. I don't know I don't but uh, I'm like if they if the woman
Wants to be with them and stuff. I'm gonna say I'm just like
Or if it's just if I don't even get laid it out if it's just you like
How long has it been? I mean, I don't want to ask how long it's been. You want to fuck a guy?
I haven't had sex in like three years, but it's like, I'm down to be like a wingman for a gay guy.
I'm cool with gay guys, dude. I don't give a fuck.
Yeah, but then I would get like, then I was like, but then I would just be weird, like it just winked. Okay, okay.
No, I mean, I can find like a gay, I mean, it's not really hard for me to find a gay guy. It's like, I really want a straight guy.
I know. I know. I know. I know.
It's like I can find a gig. I
can go on. I can go on. I can
go on right now and find a guy.
I gotta do that. Yeah. Psyche
is a lot of you. What 911.
A lot of gay or straight guys
who are. Maybe. Into a whatever.
I mean, I mean, I can just, I mean, I'm a good massage, massage person.
I can give a massage and then it's like, you know, give a really good massage.
Special massage.
But yeah, I mean, I was like, I, I, I, I, I, I used to put the woman before.
So that's like, that was me coming out of my comfort zone.
Sometimes other guys do so it's full of gays the whole street. I know but it's like that's too many gays
And I'm not really into like gay guys per se. I mean, it's like they have to do I don't I don't
Gays
and
Mm-hmm. Yeah, that's what I like make this and you got like San Jose the whole Bay Area is full of retainers, but uh
Especially my mission mission district. There's serenios down here
Well, and it's like but it's hard for me to go anywhere
So it's like I guess people have to come to me, but even like 300 glow like you know, he
He won't even come to me. He loves like 20 minutes away, probably
No
He's like, oh, I was like come over today
and I'm just like, you know, that's fucked up.
Come on, three-header.
Yes, it's very sad.
I mean, that would get my, at least I need my confidence.
I need like a little, well, actually,
I do have some confidence now, though, you know.
I've gotten enough like good feedback
to have some confidence.
If anyone wants to come up, I have the link up.
If anyone wants to come talk to erection or loose asshole.
I'm afraid, but I'm afraid like, yeah,
I need to see your photo.
Use it sometime. Yeah, I'll uh, you want me to change my profile picture. I'll change it to a really old picture
36 people in chat 300 was scared of the glow-up. Yeah, 300 glow would love it. I give the best massage
They almost was a massage therapist, you know, I know how to do
But what are you making that face for a thing that is your eyes are open and you're you're not smiling
Okay, perhaps this horror lemonade I have like two I've like three coffees left or two coffee
Okay, I can't wait to see this guy what's happening right now. I'm gonna be looking at erection. I'm gonna look at erection
I'm gonna look at a loose asshole
I
Know the person that's not that's not not actual
Please don't just put a picture of a loose asshole
Actually can't find my picture fucking. Oh shit. You'd all saw soon
Oh and the other cat ran out shit
Hmm, I lost my fucking lighter I do that
I've found it whoo what's happening right now this is Matt called magic. Oh, I change
Whoo, I wonder I think I like
I think I'm already broke ship. Let me check my bank statement.
Do-do-do. Come up, come up somebody. Especially if you want to hit on Psyche in there.
No, it's okay. You really don't have to. Okay.
I just oh, it's 4 a.m. Already. That's pretty time is going fast. I think people in the chat
41 oh my god, it's a lot
Well, not really. Okay
Guys check out the cold codex. Me. It's almost ready. It looks so good now. I'm so proud of it
I need to smoke, I need to smoke, I'm out of my bomb, I think I lost loose asshole, well
I'm here, I was like trying to, I was gonna upload a picture but it's taking me like forever to find it
Okay, no problem, I'm very patient, I'll be very patient
You probably won't change. I got probably got like probably got a disconnect or streamlapse
I have to do it for a second and come back on I can let you write back up
Yep
Let's see
Okay, so oh my gosh, oh my gosh
So last night I got a warning and then I appealed it
and it says after taking another look,
we can confirm that your content
does not violate our community guidelines.
Thank you for your patience.
Oh, yay.
So read and say to your content,
if you appeal as a warning,
you'll be allowed another warning in the future.
Okay, yay, that's good news, good news.
Very happy usually they just have AI like I did this other like appeal by video and they didn't watch the fucking video
And they so that was kind of just lucky
but um
Do you leave okay, I'm gonna go back and get my name on my end. Oh, I gotta do oh my god. This is the fucking neighbor
I'm sorry. You can actually do it. If you click on the little three dots. It should say change photo or something like that
I don't know if you're putting the fucking loose asshole profile though. Okay?
It's okay, it doesn't work, it's okay.
Someone blocked me, I wouldn't block you, the thing that is, is our community, it's
our community, yeah, that's really good news, okay, so I'm going to look at my YouTube
channel now.
I think that should be gone and, or that strike should be gone and that's good news.
Let's see, oh there's Lola, I miss Lola, oh God body rains.
I
You know the guy that but um the guy that uh tried to shoot, you know who?
He was born in from the city. I was born
You where was he born in the Torrance, California, which is where I was born. Oh, no way
Yeah, he didn't get anywhere near Trump though. Did he he was like in the water?
I don't think so. I don't think so, but yeah, I tried I guess but
Yeah, but it's kind of crazy a small world FBI was in in that city
Doing stuff yesterday, I guess over the weekend
Okay, let's see going to my studio a studio studio
Actually, I made some cool works. Okay, perfect. Okay, appeal granted. I got the appeal. That was so cool
Yeah, I played this like Groucho Marks thing, but I I said fair use on it and
They agreed thank God that's really good news, okay
Usually it's like 50 50% chance I'll give my stuff
Appeals granted. Okay
Okay, kid it. Oh, yeah, so you didn't want it. You can look at the kitty here. Here's the kitty
Just lola. Hi lola
Oh
She's very sweet
Yeah, I guess as long as you like comment on like
things then it's like not really like copyright because it's like
It goes along with the
Topic it's educational you can show stuff. So let me see
All right, I think I changed the profile picture. I need to join and reload. Okay. Yeah
Just come down. I'll let you right back out
Yes, I see what this guy looks like then I'll be like oh
My little kitty. Ooh, I know. The thing is, isn't it exciting?
What are you doing, little, like, grooming yourself? Hi.
Aw, you mean little kisses? You mean kisses?
Okay, well, let me see. I was, I made this another website for...
The goddess I'll show you if I can bring it up. Let me see. It's under
This software
Lowly you're purring. Oh here he is
See let's see guys, I can't wait
There you go, okay. Oh, it wasn't right
Yeah, you have to change it.
Hello, Flipflat, how are you?
Good morning to you, good to see you.
Okay, so I'm gonna try to find,
oh, it's not working yet.
Okay, didn't work.
Oh, well, didn't work.
You can't, if you go down
and then you go change profile photo, we'll say.
I think you put it on some other profile or something,
but it's okay.
Some others, time.
Maybe we can talk in private, okay, so let me see, okay, there, okay, hi
How do I bring this up?
This is it
I'm so sorry, I don't know. I feel kind of stoned right now because I'm only so slow
I don't know what to say.
Okay.
I made this website.
I'm really, I'm getting pretty good at creating these.
Made a dream website, actually.
So what else is new?
All right.
it's just chilling me I don't know I guess the Trump attempted assassination is pretty new I don't know
yeah I mean that's kind of crazy that that happened I mean but it's like you know I'm sure it's pretty
common for people to attempt things and uh you know I don't think we've lost a president since
you know JFK okay oh hi love seriously yeah JFK was the last one we got
I remember that. Yeah, pretty
crazy. And, uh, I actually did
this one. I don't know if
someone tried to do Nixon or
something. I'm not sure about
Nixon. Um, I don't remember
about Nixon. Well, oh, Nixon
had the Watergate. Um, the
Watergate. Yeah. He also went
to Bohemian Grove. Have you
been, have you driven through
Bohemian Grove ever? Have you
Mm-hmm. I've nothing to know if I might have driven past it, but I know I've been up in that redwoods area before definitely
Yeah, but uh, yeah, I've never seen like the it the Bohemian Grove
I know Nixon called it the faggiest thing he's ever seen
I'm not I don't doubt it. It's like a lot of it's like a lot of oh here we have another guest come in
It's like a lot of
A lot of guys running around naked. I think
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, so you're not blocked, but you're not your camera is out or something because it's like you need to have
your camera or your voice
so
Yeah, but he did say that and the faggiest thing he's ever seen. Yeah, that's funny dude
I think he said the faggiest goddamn thing he's ever seen
He's like, oh, he's like now we're up to it. We're here me and grove and ever yeah
You're on neck and slimy show the sass and grab each other's balls. Yeah
Yeah, pretty much
And then they have a big fucking owl that they pray to oh, yeah, the Molok owl. Yeah
Moloch the album, but Moloch was more of like a bull, but I guess there's an owl there.
Increasing a bull?
Well, and back in the day, it was a brazen, it called the brazen, not the brazen bull,
but it was like this, yeah, it was like this kind of horned bull figure, and then it would
like, they would sacrifice.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, you're right, you're right, you're right.
And I don't believe they really did that, because I can't believe that people would even do that in real life.
I mean, they probably did do it in real life, but who knows, but can you imagine the throwing your baby in the fire?
I just can't believe that people would do that. I thought that threw him down a
It was like a building and then with a pit in it and they just threw him in the fucking window and
That was Jezebel
Jezebel was thrown out she's she was her unix threw her through out of the window and then
And then she was trampled by horses eaten by dogs and then all that remained was a school in crossbones
Brutal dude. God damn. That's where the school in crossbones comes from
Harley dude
Which is that there was a I thought there was a old building back in the
Ancient days, whatever when I don't know if it was Moloch or whatever, but they would throw the fucking
Throw the baby inside the building and just let it just rot in there
Yeah, it's pretty brutal. I got pretty brutal like um
But I really can't believe they would do that. I mean, it's like
Yeah, I can I can believe I can do that
Well in China they used to like throw the date a girl they would throw it up home in the fucking river
Yeah, just throw it in the garbage
Oh, it's terrible
Yeah
Just fucked up. You have a crazy world
Well
Now we have like too many they have too many boys and and not enough girls in China
Yeah, but I think but it's like still I think it's like that's more like you only have one kid as a thing
And so it's yeah a child. I think they probably still do something like that, you know
Just not good
I'm so like out of it right now
Maybe I should just
Give it up tonight. I don't know
So, let me see the music of the chat one more time
Yeah, you can get up here. Okay
Look guys, it's 420
Yeah
420 I don't want to bore you because
Then you'll like say, uh, he's just boring person stuff. It's gotta be the best quote ever. Yeah, I mean it's a record
I would never say you're a boring person. Oh, thank you. Thank you
Yeah, it's been like it's hard to fucking maintain a goddamn chat for like hours. Yeah
And it's like, and especially because it's like my chat is like a little bit quieter than it usually is, like, it's like a little, a few less people talking, let's see, Jacob.
Yeah.
What really goes on between me and Grove is like, you know, it's like, they do this, well, Alex Jones broke into it, I think years ago, and he has like, there was like all this kind of scary soundtrack playing and then we do this thing called the cremation of care.
They stand in these little lodges. It's called the Bohemian Club and you know, you can't be like
Driving around the Yale Cop in 322. Yeah, that's the Skull and Bones if you go if you look at like famous
Celebrities who graduate from Yale. There's probably a good chance. They weren't Skull and Bones because it is like a power a
Power kind of thing, you know, it's like a powerful people do it and stuff
and so that's pretty interesting um yeah even as weird as they are i wouldn't say
they're even half as weird as um the uh what's the uh god damn what's the god
what's the like volcano the volcano god uh oh pele oh no it's the la the la
of the
what's up bro
bro
of the
direction of the
I don't know you actually share your picture like by putting it in the in the image
I can bring it up from backstage if you want to do that
But I don't know he means you want to have eggs though fried eggs the eggs look good
Put the picture on my profile, and it's just not uh, I know but you can also share
It's not yeah, it's okay. Maybe it'll take a minute for stream laps and grab a hold of it
the
Rice oil fresh a muttarell the fresh material
There you go, the semolina the semolina bread
Oh my god
Next to me
Ashpe this gracia
Ashpe
That's the knife, I mean.
Part two, two, nine.